<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_26" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 24</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 24</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stepped down from her carriage in front of Zane’s home. Thankfully, Adeline hadn’t questioned her when she said she wanted to take her own carriage to the earl’s house. It was scandalous, no doubt. A widow arriving alone to a bachelor’s dinner party.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But tonight, Brina didn’t care.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It would be a late evening. She would be one of the last to leave and she didn’t want Lyon and Adeline to feel they had to wait around for her. Too, she wanted time to be alone with Zane as they were last night.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She’d done a lot of thinking since he’d left her bed in the early hours of morning. And because of his gentle concern and insights she had come to terms with her fears of marrying again. Just as she had put away the hurt of losing Stewart and all the emotions that had followed. Sharing her burden of guilt for her past feelings seemed to lift it from her. Zane was right. She was young and devastated. It was time to forgive herself. And she had. She was ready to begin a new life of feeling free from her past and she was going to start by telling Zane tonight she would accept his proposal at the ball.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That was a wonderful feeling and had her smiling and humming all day.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her dark pink-colored gown had been made especially for this evening. A simple high-waisted gown with long sheer sleeves. At the last fitting she’d had the seamstress add an overlay of white sheer silk so the dark grape color wouldn’t look so stark. She’d also had the neckline lowered more than usual but not so low many eyebrows would be raised at the party. Her only jewelry consisted of an ivory-circled amethyst on a white ribbon at her throat.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good evening, Fulton,” she said when he opened the door. After handing off her cape and reticule, she followed him to the drawing room to find it empty. She was a little early, but not much. She thought for sure Zane would be down ready to greet his first guest. No matter. She would take a peek at the table to make sure her written instructions had been followed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The dining room looked warm and inviting. It wasn’t very large, but the staff had managed to seat twenty-four chairs around the table. A wide gilt-framed mirror bracketed by crystal candle sconces hung over the fireplace. On one wall hung a large tapestry of a classical garden with waterfall scene. The other had a life-size wall painting of a man who looked as if he could have been Zane’s father or the first Earl of Blacknight. His hair was as black as Zane’s, though longer. He had the same classically handsome features with dark blue eyes that held a hint of devil-may-care humor and a twitch of mischief showing around the corners of his mouth.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The long rectangular table was almost the length of the room and covered with white linen. A single silver candlestick had been placed in front of every other chair down the center of the cloth. Woven throughout the candlesticks were bits of greenery and small English tea roses.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The china and crystal gleamed. Even the candles hadn’t yet been lit. That would come a little closer to serving the first course. Zane would be at the head; she would be seated to his left as he’d instructed. As his hostess for the evening, Patricia would sit at the other end.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina smiled. It was going to be a good evening for Zane. And tomorrow evening would be even better. When he asked for her hand, she was going to give it to him in front of his family and everyone. He had proven he could be a gentleman, but she was going to marry him because she loved him more than she could have ever thought possible.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Just a few weeks ago she swore she could never love again. Zane’s gentle but constant pursuit had proven she could. He had challenged her, made her laugh, made her happy. He helped her understand she no longer needed to feel such heavy guilt for the anger and selfishness that had festered in her for so long after Stewart’s death. He was right. Grief could cause terrible feelings. They shouldn’t be compounding by continuing to relive them. In her eyes, she could never be good enough or ever do enough good to make up for what she’d felt at those terrible times in her life. All she could do was forgive herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And she had.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Fulton and his staff have done an amazing presentation.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">At the sound of a voice behind her, Brina turned and saw Zane’s sister, Mrs. Cranston standing in the doorway. “Yes. It’s as beautiful as I imagined.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Indeed. Very sweet and reserved, Mrs. Feld. Much like you. It was clever not to try and top the extravagance of the Duchess of Middlecastle’s table. She’ll be pleased it’s so simple.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina wasn’t sure what to say about that so she merely smiled and said, “I’m sure Zane didn’t mean to—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Cranston’s eyebrows rose almost to her hairline. Brina immediately recognized her mistake. Zane. She had used his first name. She should have known it was bound to happen sooner or later. And for most, it was an unforgivable error to refer to an earl in such a manner.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m sorry, Mrs. Cranston. I shouldn’t have referred to him in such a familiar.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You don’t have to worry about slip-ups with me, Mrs. Feld,” she responded in a matter-of-fact tone. “I am all for you helping my brother any way you can. I do believe you’ve been good for him and I wouldn’t mind having you in the family. I would have never believed anyone could help him settle down for a time but you seem to have. For a month, at least. Only time will tell if it will last any longer. It won’t be the first time we’ve thought he had changed only to find that he hadn’t. But, we’re always willing to hold out hope. Ah—I hear voices. Let’s go see who’s arrived. Perhaps by now even our host.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina had been almost to the point of tapping her foot in frustration before Mrs. Cranston left the room. It was no wonder Zane felt his family was such a challenge.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They were! How could his own sister be so unbelieving in him?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As she entered the drawing room, Brina looked for Zane. His uncles had arrived. So had Viscount Mountgate and Julia, Adeline and their husbands but she didn’t see Zane. Thinking he must be greeting someone in the vestibule, she headed over to speak to her friends.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Other guests continued to arrive, but Zane was noticeably absent. Unable to stop herself, she’d glanced at Mrs. Cranston who was in turn, glancing at her. The last to arrive were the Duke and Duchess of Middlecastle. After they entered, she went in search of Fulton and found him standing by the door.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Fulton, is the earl still in his chambers?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, Mrs. Feld, I’ve already told Mrs. Cranston, he hasn’t returned home, yet.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt as if something had slammed into her body and it almost drove her to her knees. “What do you mean? He’s not home?” It was a foolish question but nothing else would come to mind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s correct.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you know where he is?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The earl didn’t inform me of where he was going or when he expected to return.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Can you tell me how long he’s been gone?” Her breaths were so short she could hardly speak. “All day? The afternoon? When did he leave?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“More than an hour ago.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her heartbeat raced. “Then he’s coming back. He’s been delayed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Fulton remained quiet.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina walked back into the drawing room on shaky legs. Chatter was lively and if anyone was missing the host, it wasn’t showing to anyone but her and Mrs. Cranston.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yet.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But the minutes passed. Brina began to think maybe he’d had a carriage accident. She knew how dangerously he could drive. He was excellent managing the horses, but what if—. No. Then minutes later she was thinking perhaps he’d been attacked by footpads. What if he were lying hurt in an alley? Maybe she should ask someone to go look for him, but where would they start? Where would they go?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">So, no. She wouldn’t ask anyone to look for him. He wasn’t an errant schoolboy. He knew where he should be.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Have you seen Blacknight this evening?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina turned to see both Zane’s uncles standing beside her. In the distance she saw Mrs. Cranston heading toward them. Brina’s heart pounded and her throat went dry. They were going to be looking to her for answers she didn’t have.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not yet,” she said calmly when she couldn’t have felt more tense as Mrs. Cranston stopped beside her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s Uncle Hector stared at her and started tapping his cane on the floor. “I assumed he was in his chambers getting dressed, waiting late to make a grand entrance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Brina defended Zane. “I don’t believe the earl would do anything that pretentious.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Then where is he? If he’s not here, where?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know,” she answered, truthfully, sadly and bewildered that he wasn’t on time for his own party when he knew how important it was to do everything right this night. Why was his uncle giving her a difficult time about it? Didn’t they know how badly she wanted Zane to be with them right now?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What do you mean you don’t know? You are the one who planned this evening for him. Did you forget to ask if he’d be attending his own dinner party?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Now, Hector, there’s no call for that kind of talk. If we weren’t able to tame him, why should we think Mrs. Feld could do it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Enough of this,” Mrs. Cranston offered in a tone that let them know she was tired of the exchange. “I do believe my uncles are stressing you, Mrs. Feld. Don’t let them. Put a smile on your face.” She looked from one uncle to the other. “As we all shall and enjoy this evening. What you don’t realize, Mrs. Feld, is that this isn’t the first time my brother has snubbed his nose at Society or the family. He says he will attend an event and then he doesn’t. But don’t worry, we’ll see him Christmas Day. We always do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">No, Brina couldn’t believe he simply didn’t care enough about them or about her to attend. He had told her he loved her last night. She believed him. She felt it in his touch, his words. She had to believe he would come.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He will be here,” she said confidently. “There’s no need to worry. We’ll hold dinner. He will come.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But half an hour later, the crowd was restless. Glasses were empty again, murmurings of discontent had settled in. Like his sister, Brina kept a smile on her face. Adeline and Julia were worried for her and had tried to cheer her but nothing could take away the ache in her chest.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Twenty-three people waiting for a dinner that should have been served an hour ago. Brina had to tell Mrs. Cranston they couldn’t delay dinner any longer. She was afraid people would start leaving.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Something was wrong.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But what?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Within ten minutes everyone was seated, but Zane’s chair was empty. With great effort Brina smiled and chatted with the Duke of Middlecastle who was seated across from her and Viscount Mountgate, who was beside her. Thankfully, he didn’t seem to even notice that his hostess wasn’t occupying his seat as he kept a steady stream of conversation going, but the duke was not as forgiving. He kept turning his head and staring at the empty seat.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina couldn’t bring herself to give up on Zane. She was constantly glancing at the doorway. In her heart, she knew he was going to rush in at any moment and explain the terrible event that had delayed him. However, she was inclined to now agree with Zane that sit-down dinners with five courses were excruciatingly long. They started with steaming onion broth, followed by the beautifully prepared sole caught fresh from the coast of Dover. The breast of pheasant had been drizzled with butter and the lamb chops covered in a honey and fig sauce. The delicate fluff of sugary confection that was now being served should have been the crowning end to the meal, but the chatter and clink of silver and glasses could be heard all around the table that made it clear no one was in a joyful mood. There were no raised voices or bouts of laughter that usually graced the ending of such an elite slate of dinners.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">While dessert was being consumed, a man Brina didn’t recognize came into the room and whispered something to the duke. She couldn’t hear what was said but the duke’s eyes widened and swept over to Brina. He then cleared his throat and dug into his dessert. Brina’s heart beat so loud and fast she felt sure everyone in the room could hear it. Moments later, he leaned over and whispered to his wife. She looked aghast and whispered to the gentleman beside her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That’s when Brina heard. 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“He’s gambling at The Brass Bull.”</i></p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stomach twisted and she stopped breathing. For how long she didn’t know. Other whispers reached her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“And he has a woman hanging on each shoulder.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That wasn’t true. It couldn’t be true.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“No one is surprised.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“Perhaps Mrs. Feld is. Look at her.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt lightheaded and took in several deep breaths. That’s when she knew Zane wasn’t coming. She froze and watched in unspeakable horror the hushed words being passed down the table. After what seemed like an eternity, Mrs. Cranston laid down her spoon and rose.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">So did everyone else including Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Because of unfortunate circumstances we won’t be serving the gentlemen brandy or tea for the ladies. We’ve been pleased to have you join us this evening.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Chairs scraped against the floor and murmurings continued as everyone made their way out of the dining room and into the vestibule where they collected their wraps. Julia and Adeline flanked Brina and tried to shield her from others making their way to the entrance.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina,” Julia said, “Let’s stand over here and let everyone else say good-night to Blacknight’s family first. It will be easier if you are the last to leave.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Brina agreed, leaning against a wall in the corridor, watching Zane’s sisters and two uncles hurry everyone out the door.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know it’s not the time to talk,” Julia said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, it isn’t,” Brina agreed, feeling numb with disbelief.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know you never expected the earl wouldn’t show. What can we do to help?” Julia asked earnestly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina gave herself a mental shake and straightened. “Nothing. I am fine.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We’ll come over to see you tomorrow,” Julia offered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not waiting that long,” Adeline said firmly. “Lyon and I are going to take you home and I’ll stay with you as long as you want me to.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” Brina, said, confident she was doing a good job of holding herself together and showing no signs of the unbearable ache inside her. “No.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We are not leaving you to handle this hurt by yourself,” Julia insisted. “Adeline and I might be married but the three of us stick together.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. We do,” Brina said, not knowing where she found the willpower to be so strong sounding but grateful she had it. “Sometimes we must stand on our own. I planned this evening and I will see it through to the end. I need no help from the two of you tonight.” She smiled. “My carriage is outside. I’ll see myself home and see both of you at the ball tomorrow night when I accept my apology from the earl. Now, time for you two to get your husbands and go. I’m going to visit the retiring room before saying good night to Mrs. Cranston. I’ve not been there all evening and I simply must go before the ride home.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina reached over and kissed both of Adeline’s and then Julia’s cheeks. “Go on, both of you. We will talk later. I must speak to Mrs. Cranston and Lord Blacknight’s uncles alone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">In the retiring room Brina almost broke down and sobbed. How could he have done this after last night? After how he’d made her feel? After he’d told her he loved her? Wanted only her?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Alone as she was, it would have been so easy to let the hurt show. But instead, she replaced it with anger to kept her eyes dry until she could get home.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">How could he have done this to her? To his peers? To his family? Now, she finally understood why his family had no faith in him. All they believed about him was true. He wasn’t capable of giving up his carefree life to handle his responsibilities. She had only thought she made a difference in his behavior. She thought she had helped change him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But no. He was still the man she’d seen tied to a chair in Paris. And that was crushing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He’d never wanted to marry her. Perhaps he’d simply wanted to bed her—the widow no one else had touched. And by gambling and drinking tonight was his way of getting out of his wager with her and winning his own. But it really didn’t matter his reasons. The outcome was the same. Why couldn’t she have seen that? Why did she fall for his charming ways and his load of poppycock?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Why should she blame him? He wasn’t only doing what came natural to him. She was the one who had changed. Not him. She had fallen in love with a rake of the highest order.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When Brina walked back into the vestibule, Mrs. Cranston was the only one left standing by the front door.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Sylvester and Hector have already left,” Mrs. Cranston said. “I am leaving as well. I suggest you do so, too. The earl probably won’t be coming home before midmorning. And just think, my dear. You won your wager with him. The earl has violated the terms of your agreement with him. You’ll be getting that apology you wanted tomorrow night. That must make you feel good.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">If what she was feeling was good, she never wanted to feel bad.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Serves him right,” Mrs. Cranston continued. “Maybe that will take him down a peg or two. Do take some comfort in that. Most men hate to admit they are wrong.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She hadn’t lost him to a woman. There might have been women hanging on him while he was gambling but she lost him to himself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m sorry for you, dear.” She gave Brina a sympathy smile and placed her hand on top of Brina’s shoulder, giving it a quick, tight squeeze. “I know you hoped for better from him. I really thought he was changing, too. He’d just settled a lot of things in the family that needed his attention and everyone had seemed quite happy with his generous increase in allowances.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s good,” Brina answered with the tiniest of smiles. “So, there was some improvement. You know what they say. We must be thankful for small blessings.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I can’t help but notice Lord and Lady Lyon didn’t stay with you to see you home.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was no use hiding anything at this point. “Yes. I came in my own carriage. Dreadfully scandalous of me, I know. If you feel you must tell someone I will understand.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Cranston gave her a swaggering smile. “I like you, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you,” Brina whispered. “Now, I hope you don’t mind but I asked Fulton if I might leave the earl a note. He’s laying out paper and quill for me in the drawing room. I’ll write that, collect my wrap and be on my way.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“To The Brass Bull I hope to drag the earl out by his ear.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina gave a soft laugh. “Well, if I thought I was strong enough I might try it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m rather sorry it didn’t turn out better for you two, Mrs. Feld. I know I don’t show it, but I really do love my brother. I’ll say good-night and be on my way. Fulton will close up after you leave, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She turned, not giving Brina time to respond. Which was probably best. Her last words had stung. Brina had thought that after last night, after tonight, after tomorrow night she would no longer be Mrs. Feld.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina walked back into the drawing room and sat down at the secretary.</p>
    <bodydiv base="LETTER-A" class="- topic/bodydiv " outputclass="LETTER-ALTR-A">
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="SalutationSal">Dear Lord Blacknight,</p>
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">I will see you tomorrow evening at mid—</p>
    </bodydiv>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">No, that wasn’t right. It was already after midnight. Tomorrow was already here.</p>
    <bodydiv base="LETTER-A" class="- topic/bodydiv " outputclass="LETTER-ALTR-A">
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="SalutationSal">Dear Lord Blacknight,</p>
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">I will see you this evening for the apology you owe me.</p>
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="SignatureSig">Mrs. Feld</p>
    </bodydiv>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As Brina replaced the quill to its stand, she heard a door open and slam shut, masculine footsteps ran down the corridor. She looked up and Zane rounded the doorway. His neckcloth was hanging limp and untied. His hair was rumpled as if he’d just rose from sleep. He looked handsome, vibrant. Happy to see her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">How could he be so inconsiderate as to still make her heartbeat race at the sight of him?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank God, you’re still here.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Was that a smile of relief she saw on his face? Relief that she was still there? Anguish festered inside her. “That’s obvious,” she managed to say and rose.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was sure you’d be gone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She should have been. It was clear he’d been carousing. She supposed she did look like the dutiful, faithful lady waiting at home for him to return. “I’m sorry I failed to leave before you arrived,” she said tightly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know you’re angry but—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You do, do you?” She walked toward him. “Angry? Really? No, I’m hurt.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina, I’m sorry I—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You’re about five hours too late for such words, my lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She went to rush past him, but he caught her arm. “Look at me,” he said earnestly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” she whispered, keeping her head down. She bit back tears that collected in her throat but was unable to keep them from pooling in her eyes as she remembered how he had held and loved her. She choked down a sob. “I don’t want to look at you. I don’t want you to touch me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Listen to me, Brina.” His hand tightened on her arm.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She lifted her head, and then her lashes and what she saw made her want to forget who she was, what she had vowed. She was deeply, madly in love with him, but she was overcome with such grief.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s eyes were gleaming, too. A breathy sigh of despair pushed forth from her aching lungs. Only with the will of an inner strength she’d developed since being alone did she manage to give him a steely gaze and say, “Let go of me and don’t say anything.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His face was etched hard with indecision but finally, he dropped his hand.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t want your explanation,” she said past a thick throat.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He struck his thumb to his chest. “I deserve to be heard.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You don’t deserve any consideration from me!” she lashed out at him. “Gambling, drinking with women hanging all over you!”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes widened with outrage. “No!” he said bitterly. “Listen to me. Gambling yes, but there were no women and no drinking I swear!”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“As if that matters! What you did tonight was wrong. It shows you don’t care for me or anyone. I made a fool of myself to ever think you cared for me or that I could trust you. I did my best, but I was misled to think you had or could change.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s not true,” he demanded, angrily. “I’m not going to let you say things that aren’t true and get by with it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t have to say anything. Your actions prove it.” Brina bit back the tears again. “You have made choices like this throughout your life.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Let me explain, damn—,” He bit off the last of the word but swore under his breath as he raked his hands through his tousled hair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I thought nothing could ever hurt me as deeply as when my husband didn’t come back to me. But he didn’t mean to hurt me. He didn’t do it by choice. You did. He hurt me by doing something good for other people. But you. You knew exactly what you were doing. So, I am going to walk out of here with my head held high and no tears on my face.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina.” He whispered her name almost desperately.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not one more word. I can’t wait for you to apologize tomor—tonight at midnight, at the ball.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I came on my own because I wanted to be the last one to leave tonight. So you see, you aren’t the only one who can break the rules.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She kept her chin up, her shoulders straight, and looked straight ahead as she walked past him. Somehow, she managed to make it to the carriage and climb inside before a heaving sob of heartache left her mouth. A second and third came rushing out before she was able to stop the flow and hold the rest of her anguish inside her aching throat.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was nothing to compare to the hurt of realizing she was in love with him and could never be with him. He had chosen his wayward life over her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">How could she ever get over that?</p>
  </body>
</topic>