<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_13" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 11</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 11</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The décor of the small town house was opulent from the floors to ceilings. Grand crystal chandeliers hung in every room. Every piece of gilt fretwork and carved moldings were exquisite in detail and style. Rich colors of velvet draperies graced the frames of all windows. The cushions on the settees and chairs displayed the finest fabrics with classic English floral patterns.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina knew the home well. The hostesses for the evening had been her parents’ neighbors all her life. She’d been welcomed into their home many times.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">So had numerous other guests present at the soiree. The well-designed drawing room was packed with people, including a cellist and violinist who had been squeezed into a tight corner by the pianoforte. The chatter and laughter of the crowd often drowned out the beautiful music they were playing. No one seemed to notice. It was a party, and everyone was delighting in the merriment.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A buffet that looked as if it had been set for the Prince was in the dining room. Brina had only seen it as she passed in front of the open double doors. She hadn’t made it inside to sample any of the delicacies splendidly arranged on the white linen-draped table. There was always someone to distract her with conversation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline and Lyon had picked her up for the party and as soon as she entered Julia joined them but so did a host of other ladies all wanting to know how she was managing after her showdown with the new earl. She kept all her answers short and vague as possible, insisting she was doing extremely well and not letting any of the machinations of the past few days hinder her from work. The surprising thing was that most of them seemed to believe he.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">One by one the ladies started drifting away, including Adeline and Julia when the handsome Mr. Inwood came up to talk to her. They had found other people to talk to on the other side of the room.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Currently she had three handsome bachelors standing in front of her, vying for attention, making it clear they now considered her eligible to pursue. It was her fault, of course. She had opened the door to such attention by agreeing Lord Blacknight could call on her. Now, apparently every man thought he should be given equal opportunity to win her hand. Even the younger bachelors were trying to woo her. Brina wasn’t attracted to any of them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was a bit disconcerting to have heard tonight that in addition to Blacknight’s wager at White’s, many side bets were being arranged in gaming hells all over Town and many private wagers among friends, too. Brina considered all of it madness of the highest order. It was as if a raging fire had swept through the ton. The earl certainly knew how to get her attention and everyone else’s.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Unfortunately, she had unwittingly added kindling to the flames. She had no definite plans to make any demands on the earl until they started dancing. It must have been the touch of his hands, tilt of his head, or maybe it was the look in his eyes that made her end up giving in to the earl’s uncommon, yet persuasive assault to pay her court. There wasn’t anything she could do about it now but weather the storm and adjust being pursued. Not only by the earl but others.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It wasn’t that the earl didn’t need her to help him. He obviously did. He continued to prove he didn’t always do the proper thing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">By design, she was sure.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Like bringing horses to her house, and kissing her in the park where anyone could have seen them. Though, she couldn’t say she had overly objected much at the time. Oh, who was she kidding. She hadn’t objected at all. She’d loved riding the horse and welcomed the kiss with a passion she hadn’t thought possible anymore. And she hadn’t wanted it to end. So much for her declaration of no women for him—though in truth—at the time she’d said it she hadn’t been thinking of kisses. She was thinking about visits to a mistress for what men pay visits to mistresses for.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She felt a sudden uptick in her breathing. It was ridiculous. Just thinking about Lord Blacknight had—</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What is your favorite flower, Mrs. Feld?” the tallest of the gentlemen standing with her asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina blinked for a moment as she stared at his boyish face. “Pink,” she answered, trying to return her thoughts to the conversation at hand. “That is to say any pink flower. I would choose that color over any other in the garden no matter if it were a lily, peony, or rose.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I shall remember that. It’s a color I’m fond of as well. It would look beautiful on you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Suddenly Brina remembered the revealing pink gown she’d worn in Paris. “Thank you, Mr. Inwood, but I doubt I shall ever wear that color again,” she said softly. “I believe it’s more suited for ladies much younger than me.” She looked over at Adeline and Julia. She could really use their help right now but neither of them were looking at her. “However,” she continued when the bachelor seemed to expect her to say more, “I saw that flowers have been planted in window boxes on most every street. Have you noticed?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After that question, the four of them engaged in an extended conversation about the new flowers planted in Hyde and St. James Parks and various gardens for the upcoming May celebration. While continuing to converse, Brina kept glancing at Adeline and Julia hoping to give them the signal to come over and give her a reason to excuse herself from the young men. She kept spearing looks their way. All to no avail. It was as if they were both ignoring her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She glanced toward the doorway and not the first time since arriving. Right now she’d even welcome the earl to come and give her a reason to excuse herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Finally, deciding she must save herself, she conveniently moved the subject to horses. Something all gentlemen liked to discuss. Within a few seconds, they were robustly discussing a recent midnight horserace down Rotten Row and seemed happy to leave her out of the current conversation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was the perfect time to excuse herself, which she happily did and made a straight line to Adeline and Julia who were standing near the entryway into the sitting room.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What’s wrong with you two?” Brina complained, walking up to her friends. “Couldn’t you see I wanted you to politely untangle me from my new admirers?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You needed no such thing,” Adeline answered with confidence. “You can more than handle all three gentlemen at the same time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But we did keep check on you from time to time, in case you required us,” Julia added. “We were actually watching the door more and hoping that Lord Blacknight would get here in time to see all the beaus crowded around you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina coughed out a light laugh. “What do you mean? I’m not trying to make him jealous. I have no need for him to see me at a party. I need him to be at White’s tonight playing cards and drinking his drink until dawn. Were that the case, I would know this bargain we’ve struck is over and I could return to the peaceful, normal life I expected to enjoy when I returned to London.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Where is he?” Julia asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have no idea,” Brina answered, not wanting to admit that she had looked at the door a time or two, wondering if she might see him. “I haven’t heard from him since our ride in the park yesterday. We didn’t talk about which, if any, parties we’d be attending in the coming days.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After their kiss, Brina hadn’t been able to think about anything, so she’d suggested they pack up the basket, get back on the horses for a ride through the park. Which they’d done. Thankfully, he’d decided to be a gentleman and hadn’t mentioned the kiss when they’d dismounted in front of her house. She had hoped he wouldn’t. But there was no way he hadn’t noticed how utterly eager she’d responded to his ardent embrace.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He has no inkling you are here tonight?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know how he could. I chose this dinner because my parents would never forgive me if I hadn’t shown up at their neighbors’ party.” She looked at Adeline and smiled. “Thank you again for letting me come with you and Lyon. It would be tiresome if I were forced to have a constant companion. It’s much easier to just come with you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“One of us will always pick you up and be with you at every party you attend.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you,” Brina said gratefully.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Which,” Julia said, “leads me to ask what you and Lord Blacknight talked about yesterday afternoon?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina didn’t know. All she remembered was the glorious kiss that had made her breathless and warmed her all the way down to her toes. Most troubling of all was the way his touch had made her want much more than kisses and caresses from him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Those feelings she would keep to herself and not share with her friends.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Many things,” was all Brina answered, as she glanced toward the entrance. How could it be that she was watching for the earl, hoping to see him standing there looking for her among the crowd in the room? Just a week ago it would have been inconceivable that she would be watching for him or any man. Oh, why did he have to come into her life? She was settled. Happy. Now, she was—eager.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Was he a gentleman toward you?” Adeline asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course not,” Brina said without thinking. “Far from it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline moved closer again and whispered, “What did he do?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did he kiss you?” Julia asked, her eyes growing wide with curiosity.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina ignored her probing question and replied, “When he came to my house, he brought horses for us to ride to the park instead of a well-tooled carriage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline’s jaw dropped. “You can’t be serious.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia grinned with surprise. “You are serious.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course, I am,” she exclaimed softly, and then looked around to see if anyone was watching them. “I can’t make this up. He did have a proper refreshment basket with him, and I gave him a book of poetry. Blacknight is different. I don’t know what to make of him. He’s unsettled my life, me. It’s no wonder he’s had such problems with his family. I’m sure it’s because they’ve never known what to expect from him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But he intrigues you,” Julia offered as if to finish her thought.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, he does,” Brina said without any hesitancy. “Immensely so. I’ve admitted that and it distresses me that he does. I simply must stop thinking about him. Or talking about him. So, enough about the earl. I must keep my mind on other things. As I’ve told you, I want to give the girls art lessons once a week and teach them to paint. What do you think about Sunday afternoons? ”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m sure Sundays will be fine, but when did you mention this?” Adeline questioned as her gaze darted over to Julia for confirmation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia’s eyebrows rose and she lifted her hands as if to say I have no idea what she’s talking about.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Last week when you came over without your sons and Blacknight was there. Maybe I never actually got around to telling you exactly what I had in mind. The earl seemed to take up a lot of our conversation, but I did say I wanted to do something more with the girls and both of you said whatever it was you’d agree.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I vaguely recollect that,” Julia said with a hint of uncertainty in her tone. “But, Brina, it takes time to learn how to paint. Unless one has a natural talent like you, it can be a very frustrating pursuit.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know,” Brina answered, a bit disappointed Julia wasn’t as excited about the prospects as she was. “I think some of them might be gifted. It will be easy enough to tell as time goes on.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You’ll need paints, brushes, aprons, easels for them all. Not to mention that Mrs. Tallon will object strongly to this.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A server holding a tray of champagne offered them a glass but all three declined. While shaking her head at the man, Brina noticed one of the young bachelors she’d been talking to was watching her. He smiled when she saw him. She returned the greeting and turned away.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With the server gone, Brina continued. “I’ve thought about all of your concerns, including the head mistress. She won’t be happy about it. I’ll be gentle with her but make her see things my way. I realize I can’t just go over and set up an easel and palette for everyone. At first, I’ll use my own and my mother’s since she is out of town and hasn’t painted in years. Anyway, I was hoping the two of you would share your supplies. That will give us four. If I buy another that will give us enough to have one each to share between two girls.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stopped and waited for one of them to say something.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course, we’ll be happy to send over our painting materials,” Adeline said with a determined smile. “We’re in the school together and always will be. Whatever needs to be done for the girls will be.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you. I’ve received so many flowers recently, I took some of them to the girls. With Mrs. Tallon and her helpers, we gave them a lesson in flowers. We let the girls gently take the petals off some of the blooms and draw the parts of the flowers on their chalkboards. Doing things like that will help them when they start making flowers to add to dresses, gowns and capes.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What an excellent idea,” Adeline praised. “I’ll see to it my easel and palette are delivered to the school tomorrow.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ll do the same,” Julia agreed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, not yet. There’s no hurry,” Brina held up her hands. “I must speak to Mrs. Tallon first.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You will be a good teacher, Brina,” Adeline said softly. “You let us know what to do and when.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt compelled to add, “I know it might seem I’m over-stepping my boundaries but I do believe this will be helpful to them in how they choose and blend colors and where to place flowers, beads, and bows. You both have your sons to help keep you busy and content. I need something more to do, too.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina, we want you to find happi—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, don’t,” she said softly, cutting off Julia’s words. She then lifted her chin and looked around the crowded room. The tall, handsome young bachelor was still looking at her and smiling. The gaiety everyone was feeling showed on their faces and in their noisy chatter. She had long come to terms with the fact that life had to go on after her husband died, but she had to do more with her life than dress for parties and afternoon strolls in the park. Her life had to have more meaning than attending happy social gatherings like this one, and she was determined it would.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Suddenly feeling stronger, she looked back to her friends. “Don’t even hint that you are feeling sorry for me, Julia.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, I don’t,” she answered earnestly. “You know that wasn’t my intention.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s how it sounded. I need no one’s sympathy because I’m not unhappy anymore. I have a full life.” Brina gave her a faint indulging smile. “I know you don’t understand my need to be of assistance to others. Even the untrainable earl—who I’m determined to make into a better gentleman if it tatters my own reputation.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia reached over and touched Brina’s hand affectionately. “I will help you give them the lessons.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina squeezed her fingertips and smiled. “Never. You are terrible at painting.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The three friends laughed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait,” Adeline suddenly whispered. “Don’t either of you glance toward the doorway right now, but I think Earl of Blacknight just walked into the room.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina’s pulse raced with anticipation. She turned immediately to look at the doorway.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">So did Julia.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I told you not to look,” Adeline grumbled. “Now he will see all three of us staring at him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh,” Brina’s hopes plummeted. “No, it’s not him. It’s his younger cousin, Robert. They do favor, but then, all the Browning men are tall, have that thick black hair and are handsome.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Julia agreed. “It’s not the earl, but he might as well be. Every young lady in the room is gaping at him. I suppose they are thinking if they can’t have Blacknight, they’ll take his cousin.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I really felt strange for a moment when you said his name,” Brina offered, watching how at ease Robert seemed while saying hello to someone. “I wondered how Blacknight could know I was here with so many other parties being held.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s easy enough,” Julia suggested with a sheepish smile. “He could have followed you. It wouldn’t be the first time a gentleman behaved in such an ungentlemanly manner in order to know where a certain young lady might be on a given night.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Or,” Adeline countered, “We could have just assumed it was a lucky guess. Lyon says he’s considered lucky with cards. Maybe he’s fortunate in everything else, too.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Garrett told me that as well,” Julia injected. “He tells me the earl’s skill is unmatched when playing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline nodded. “Gentlemen consider it an honor to play with him and against him. In fact, Lyon invited him to join his weekly card game but now that he can’t gamb—” She stopped and her golden-brown eyes zeroed in on Brina’s.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">An odd feeling washed over Brina. “Lyon asked him to join his club?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. But he won’t be joining. He sent Lyon a note saying it wasn’t a convenient time for him participate.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Adeline,” Brina asked suddenly a little suspicious of her friends’ motives, wondering if they felt the need to watch over her concerning the earl. “Did you ask Lyon to invite Lord Blacknight to be a member of his club so Lyon could keep an eye on him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Absolutely not,” Adeline admonished. “I would never do that. First and foremost, I’d never try to interfere with Lyon’s card club in any way. Second, if I were going to do anything of the kind, I would tell you. Lyon invited Lord Blacknight because his skill at cards is legendary and most gentleman would pay for the chance to play with him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, I know you didn’t do anything like that.” Brina shook her head in bafflement. “I don’t know why I’m so prickly concerning him. It’s just the earl keeps me bristling with emotions I’ve not wanted to deal with for years. I don’t even want to think about the man, but I do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We understand,” Julia insisted softly. “It must be hard for someone as self-possessed are you are, but why don’t you face the fact that he appeals to you and enjoy it rather than fighting it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina glanced over to Mr. Inwood. There were no butterflies in her stomach, nor tightness in her chest or throat at the sight of him. But always with the earl, she found it difficult to catch her breath.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I never thought to look at another man with interest. It’s perplexing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And I have no doubt you have perplexed him?” Adeline delighted smile. “What gentleman wants to give up his cards or his wine?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Or his women?” Julia added with a satisfied smile. “I thought that was brilliant.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Indeed! It was superb,” Adeline agreed with a laugh.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Four weeks is a long time for a man to be so saintly. I couldn’t believe you were being so bold.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I surprised myself,” Brina said honestly. “But once we started talking the words just came tumbling out and the demands got more personal. I truly expected he was going to say no but he just kept saying yes.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Once you got started, you didn’t stop and it was so satisfying for us to see you getting the upper hand,” Julia told her. “You are usually too worried about being good to ever do anything so bad.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know,” Brina said with a laugh and shaking her head again. “I just kept thinking he’s going to say, ‘Enough of this! Forget the whole idea!’ and give up on courting me. I wasn’t making it easy on him, but he just kept agreeing to everything I said. Once I made the demands, I couldn’t back down.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And you shouldn’t have.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Right,” Adeline agreed. “If a man wants to marry you, there’s nothing wrong with making him work to win your hand.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Marry him.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You know I don’t want to marry,” she said honestly and probably should have added that she was definitely conflicted about him, too. But how much did she want to share with her friends? Especially when she wasn’t sure what exactly she was feeling and certainly not why she was feeling it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But you wouldn’t mind having him as a lover,” Julia stated as if it were already a settled fact between them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina opened her mouth to agree, but stopped when she saw Harper enter the room. If she hadn’t been so busy thinking about the earl she would have wondered if he had come when she saw Blacknight’s cousin. “Excuse me, I just saw Harper come in, and I’d like to speak to him before he gets caught up with all the beautiful young ladies here.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are you really going to brush us off just when the conversation was getting so interesting?” Julia asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I fear I am, but only for now. Not forever. We will speak of this again later in the evening.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With those parting words, Brina headed toward the entryway. Harper saw her, gave her a big smile and started walking to meet her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper Tabor was the kind of young man who walked into the room with a light step and friendly expression. Wherever he went, he always had the look about him as if he expected something wonderful to happen and he was going to be a part of it. His step was lively and sure, and his eyes were always full of warmth. He was of average height for a man, clean-shaven and thin. Light sandy brown hair was combed away from his face and fell above his collar in an attractive wave. He’d inherited the family trait of big blue eyes.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Harper,” Brina said with a beam of happiness she didn’t try to contain. “It’s so good to see you. I’m sorry I was out when you called on me yesterday. How have you been?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m well,” he answered, and gave her a cousinly kiss on each cheek. “You get lovelier every time I see you. How do you do it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina smiled at his flattering comment and couldn’t help but give his lip and chin a good look. All signs of bruising were gone. “And I think you are more charming every time I see you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he said with a twinkle in his eyes. “I’m only hoping for an invitation to dinner one night this week.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina laughed. “Consider yourself invited. I should have done so already, and I had plans to, but—” But she’d had the unexpected nuisance of the earl to think about and require her attention. “Why don’t you come late tomorrow afternoon and we’ll have an early supper together.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After a brief hesitation, he responded, “Tomorrow’s probably not good, cousin, but I will make it soon. I promised your parents I’d be around to check on you while they are out of Town and I will.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did you?” she asked with a feeling of delight. “Papa asked me to keep in touch with you. I don’t know about you, but I need no one checking on me, Harper. Just a pleasant visit will do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded. “Same for me and I’ll do that soon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why didn’t you go with my parents to see your mother? It would have been the perfect time. I’m sure she misses you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And I miss her, but I don’t want to leave London right now.” His gaze drifted from hers and scanned the room before he thoughtfully said, “I’ve left the nest, as they say. I’ll go, but not until summer comes around and perhaps I’ll even wait until autumn. It will do the sisters good to have some time together, don’t you think? If I were there Mum would want to divide her attention between the two of us. Besides, I didn’t want to miss the Season. So many new people are in Town.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And I see two beautiful belles huddled together looking at you right now and wishing you were speaking to them and not me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He looked over at them, smiled and nodded a couple of times. “They are lovely, aren’t they? I know the Season is for making a match, but I’m not looking to do that this year. Best I stay away from the ladies. But what of you? The reason I stopped by yesterday was to see how are you bearing the scandal Lord Blacknight brought to your door? You certainly don’t look as if it’s gotten you down. You look splendid.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She saw sincerity in his expression and it warmed her. “I’m managing well. Thank you for asking, Harper.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes engaged with hers. “You do know you can call on me, if you need to.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I do, but there hasn’t been anything the earl has said or done that I can’t—” Brina’s words fell away as she thought for a split second the Earl of Blacknight had come up beside Harper.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You remember my friend, Robert Browning, don’t you?” Harper asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Robert was probably as tall as Blacknight but thinner through the chest and shoulders as was the usual case with younger men. His hair was just as dark as the earl’s, and there was no doubt he had the same handsome features.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, of course I do. How are you, Mr. Browning?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, Mrs. Feld,” he said with a smile. “You always look so lovely and especially tonight.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina could tell both her cousin and Lord Blacknight’s cousin had been taught the art of flattery. She returned his smile and said, “That’s kind of you to say.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was visiting Lord Blacknight yesterday, but I didn’t stay long. He seemed busy. There were books and papers all over his desk.” He looked around the room as if he were searching for someone. “Have you seen him tonight?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.” She smiled again, deciding not to say more than her one-word answer.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Perhaps we’ll see him somewhere later in the evening,” Mr. Browning offered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina,” Harper said, “Robert and I are going to have something to eat before we go. Would you like to join us?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Go? You just arrived.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know. We’ve said hello to most everyone. Come dine with us. It will give us time to chat and give Robert a chance to get to know you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, do, Mrs. Feld,” Mr. Browning encouraged, his smile as genuine as Harper’s.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, yes, I will. I’m just surprised you don’t intend to stay and visit with—everyone. Your hosts and all the young ladies. I didn’t expect you’d rush away.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We must tonight,” he glanced at Robert. “We have a card game and don’t want to be late.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Cards?” she queried.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Mr. Browning answered for Harper. “I was introduced to a gentleman who’s starting a new club. We want to play a few hands and see if we think it’s a club we might be interested in joining.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Terribly rude of us to eat and run, I know,” Harper said. “We’re hoping to slip out without anyone noticing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper politely held out his arm to escort her into the dining room. Brina smiled and hooked her hand around his elbow.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Men and their cards. There was something about the two of them that made her uneasy. She couldn’t imagine what it could be. But something had her thinking that not all was quite right. And she wasn’t so sure Harper should be spending so much time with the earl’s cousin.</p>
  </body>
</topic>