<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_20" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 18</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 18</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It had been a good day and a long time since Julia had accompanied Brina to Pilwillow Crossings. As was expected, the two didn’t spend as much time together since Julia had married last year.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We’ll see you back here in an hour,” Brina waved and called up to the driver as the two friends stepped out of the carriage and stood on the pavement in front of Brina’s parents’ house in Mayfair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The landau rolled away at a jaunty clip and she turned back to Julia, and said, “Just yesterday I was remembering when I first started going to the abbey. The ride home used to seem so long. I was always afraid someone would see me there and tell Mama where I’d been. Now, everyone knows I go once a week. Mama still doesn’t want me to go, but like everyone else in the ton, she remains quiet.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Ladies of Society were encouraged to be benevolent to such organizations as abbeys, orphanages, and hospitals, but heaven forbid they ever be seen at one of the places. What others thought about her charity work no longer bothered Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I think it’s because you go about it so quietly and you don’t impose your will on anyone else,” Julia said with a reminiscing smile. “Memories of the times I went with you last year will be with me forever. It was good to see the sisters today. There was a time I truly worried you would decide to give up your life with us and join their order.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I came close, didn’t I?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia nodded.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s good they didn’t want me. What I do now is more manageable than joining them would have been. Thank you for wanting to go with me today to deliver the tea and bandages.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It was my pleasure to see Sister Francine again. Besides, I wanted to spend some time alone with you so I could see how you are really doing. We talk at parties, but we’re often interrupted and always the worry someone will overhear us. How are things going with you and Blacknight?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hearing the earl’s name swelled Brina’s chest and made her abdomen tighten and tremble with a heavenly feeling. Brina looked up at the sky and breathed in deeply. Puffy white clouds dotted the azure blue. The air was cool but still. The neighborhood was quiet and now that the landau was out of sight there were no carriage wheels or voices to be heard along the street or in the distance.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I kept thinking you would say something about him today,” Julia continued when Brina remained silent. “Did I make you uncomfortable by mentioning him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How could I feel uncomfortable on such a beautiful day?” She glanced at her friend and turned the tables on her by saying, “I haven’t said anything because you haven’t asked about him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia pursed her lips and seemed to think on that before answering, “True. I kept hoping you would so you wouldn’t think I was prying.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Ha!” Brina said with a laugh. “When has that ever bothered you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Always,” Julia said with a knowing shrug. “I know you’re a very private person and I do respect that. At times. But not today,” she added with a deliberate smile.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You know I would never think you were prying. Only anxious for me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good. I am. So tell me about him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina looked up at the sky again as the turmoil of what was happening weighed on her. “He continues to astound me and probably everyone with his lack of appropriateness at times.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, I’m not one to throw stones. As you know, Garrett forsook the role of a gentleman at one time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia gave Brina an esteeming grin. “Many ladies, young and old alike wish they’d been in the racing curricle with him that afternoon he drove so fast through Town.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve heard whispers of that as well. It was exciting.” 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">All of it.</i>
      “When he told me he disliked the tediousness of long, sit-down dinners such as the one at the Duke of Middlecastle’s house, I said he must give one himself.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia’s eyes widened with surprise. “You didn’t.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina laughed. “I did. The date’s been set for the evening before the last ball of the Season. There simply was no time before then. I’m working on the guest list. Hopefully, it will also smooth over some of the feathers he ruffled for not responding to the duchess’ dinner party and then attending.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“This was a clever idea.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not sure how clever it was. Though his sister will be his hostess, I am doing all of the planning which, of course, takes time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Have you seen him since the dinner?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Curls of pleasure tumbled in Brina’s stomach and she stopped walking. “I saw him briefly last night at the Windhams’ party and a couple of days ago we went for a ride in the park.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Hmm. Carriage or horse?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Horse,” Brina said and started slowly walking up the stone path that led to her parents’ front door. “I don’t remember enjoying riding so much. I’m glad he reintroduced me to it. There’s something peaceful and comforting about it. The animal is warm, gentle and very easy to guide.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And what about the earl? Is he all those things? Comforting, gentle and easy to guide?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stopped. “Not in the least,” she answered quickly, but frowned when she immediately remembered the gentle touch of his fingers against her cheek, the tenderness of soft kisses and caress of his hands on her breasts. Every time she had such thoughts, she wanted to be with him. “Well, he is gentle,” she corrected. And eager and passionate, too. “But no, he’s not comforting because he disturbs me greatly. Continuously. In many ways. And he certainly isn’t easy to guide—as everyone knows.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Sometimes a man can disturb you in a good way. Does he do that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Brina said casually and walked on up to the door. She opened her reticule and took out the key. She squeezed it into her palm as they stood under the overhang of the small portico. It had been a long time since she’d talked so honestly with Julia and it felt good. “His kisses that make me tingle all the way down to my toes,” she admitted freely.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh,” Julia whispered softly, clearly not expecting such a heart-felt answer from her. “You know I had wondered if the two of you were—kissing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How could we not. You know the attraction was there from the beginning. It’s so hard for me to understand,” Brina acknowledged, feeling free to express her struggles. “I’ve always been so adamant no man would ever interest me again. I truly believed that and for five years no one has. Now, I’m interested. Not for marriage, of course, but kisses and touches and all the rest of it. I can’t explain to you how good it feels to be that close to someone again. To be hugged so tightly, touched passionately and feel so wanted. No more than that. He makes me feel treasured. I could have kept kissing him forever.” She stopped and laughed at herself. “What am I saying? I don’t have to explain any of this. You know what I’m talking about.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia nodded understandingly. “Have you done more than kiss?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not really.” Brina struggled with her thoughts. “Not because I’m not willing. He isn’t.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia frowned in disbelief. “You can’t mean that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s true.” It had happened more than once but no need to tell that. “He reminded me that I had made him promise there would be no women and he included me in that promise.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia twisted her lips around a couple of times, trying not to smile. “He’s making you suffer from your own rule?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she exclaimed softly. “When I was in his arms, I wasn’t even thinking about our bargain. It was the farthest thing from my mind. Just enjoying how utterly wonderful he was making me feel. But, of course that’s not the only reason he disturbs me. It’s getting closer to the end of the Season and I haven’t heard one slip of gossip from anyone accusing him of gambling, drinking or anything else. That night at the ball when I was making all those demands, I truly didn’t believe he could make it through the night without a glass of wine or a card in his hands.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Garrett hasn’t heard anything either. I’ve queried him about what gossip is making the rounds in the clubs. He said Blacknight has been seen in the evenings, but he only talks with friends and watches others play their cards or billiards. If a man’s not going to drink or gamble there isn’t much reason for him to spend a lot of time at the clubs. The problem is that you don’t know what he might be doing in the privacy of his home. Who’s to say he’s not emptying the decanter every night?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You’re right, of course,” she said, with some ambivalence. He could be doing that, but it didn’t feel right to Brina that he might be cheating on their bargain in private. “I can’t accuse him unless someone comes forward with proof they’ve seen or heard of him breaking our bargain. And believe me, I know men have tried to catch him in the act. Imagine someone watching your every step.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The lock gave way, Brina pushed open the door and stepped inside. The house was cold and quiet as a mouse creeping across a floor. For a moment, Brina missed her mother and wished she’d been there to greet them. She shook off the soft feeling of love and placed her reticule on the side table.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My riding boots are in the wardrobe upstairs. I’ll get those first. My mother’s easel and painting supplies are in—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina heard footsteps and, at the same time, saw the shadow of a man coming down the corridor. Startled, she spun to see Harper walking toward them with his lively step, happy and jovial as usual.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Merciful heavens, Harper. I didn’t know anyone was in the house. You frightened me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t know I was in a frightful state, dear cousin. I’m sorry about that. Must be the wind.” He brushed a hand through his hair and rearranged it. “Is that better? Such a lovely surprise to see you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What are you doing here?” Brina asked, trying to calm her racing heart.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He seemed momentarily at a loss but then spoke up to say, “I stopped by to check on the house and make sure everything was all right.” He grabbed his cloak and swung it over his shoulders and fastened the hook at the neck before reaching down to give her the usual kisses on both cheeks. “Just as your father asked before he left.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina tried not to overreact but it was difficult not to be more than just a little surprised by his presence. “I do remember he asked you to check on me but not that he’d asked you to check the house.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Didn’t I tell you?” He queried, putting his finger to his chin and striking a thoughtful pose. “You’re sure? I thought I told you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.” And it seemed rather strange for her father to worry about the house. They lived in the safest section of Mayfair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m sorry.” He guffawed. “I didn’t make that clear he wanted me to look in on you and the house. Is there a problem? I don’t have to come over, you know. If there—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, there’s no problem. I’m just glad that I understand now. Please, yes, do whatever Papa asked you to do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper nodded, then turning to Julia said, “How are you Mrs. Stockton? Lovely to see you again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m good, Harper,” Julia replied. “It’s nice to see you, too. Did you find anything amiss?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Missing? No, no. Or did you say amiss? I didn’t look specifically.” He turned back to Brina and gave her a nervous smile. “I checked all the windows and the doors. They were locked. Everything seemed to be in order. You don’t have to bother to do that now if you don’t want to.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina tried not to worry about Harper’s strange behavior but he had her wondering if all he said was true. She’d never seen him act nervous and on edge. “I hadn’t even planned to check and make sure the windows were secure. I only came by to pick up my riding boots and some other things I need.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, I’ll not stay and hinder you. I’m sure you want to get right to it, so I’ll be on my way.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait. Before you go, there’s something I’d like to ask you about, if you have time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper looked at the front door and said, “Yes, of course. Anything.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why don’t I go up to your room and look through your wardrobe for your boots while you two talk.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you, Julia,” Brina said, and waited until she was at the top of the stairs before turning back to Harper. “Since you are here and we have the time, I thought I’d ask you about Lord Blacknight’s cousin, Mr. Browning.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper clasped his hands behind his back and kept silent. As if waiting for her to say more.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was wondering if perhaps you’d seen him in the past several days. The earl and his family have been concerned about him because they don’t know his whereabouts. They hesitate to ask because they don’t want him to think they are checking up on him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If that is all it is, I can put his lordship’s and family’s mind at ease. I know where he is. He’s been staying with me. I wasn’t aware he hadn’t sent a note around to let his family know he was with a friend.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina didn’t know why but she felt the need to add, “And he’s fine? I mean, he hasn’t been seen playing or drinking at any of the clubs, or that is not last when I spoke to the earl.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We don’t always go to the same clubs as the earl,” he said with an edge to his voice. “We’re not in the same class with our skills or our money.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Clearly there was a bit of jealousy in that remark that startled her but she let it pass. “All right, I’ll tell Lord Blacknight he’s well and staying with you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper studied on what she said. The more he studied, the more serious his expression grew. She was beginning to wonder if this kind of behavior was the reason her father had asked her to keep up with him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’d rather you not tell Lord Blacknight you spoke with me about any of this, Brina. I’ll see that Robert sends a note to his father or the earl that all is fine and let that stand.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why shouldn’t they know he’s with you?” she questioned, not appreciating his reticence on this subject.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You’ve always been like a sister to me haven’t you?” He smiled sweetly and suddenly seemed the Harper she knew. “And because you are, I’m going to tell you the truth of it all. This mustn’t go any further. Promise?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Did she have a choice if she wanted to know? She nodded.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“After a late night of more than a few ales and a pint of wine, Robert took a fall and banged himself around quite badly. Bruised his ribs and gave himself a cut lip and black eye. But he’s fine now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That news sent a chill up her spine. Brina was suddenly reminded of when Harper’s lip and mouth showed the same signs and her worry grew. “That sounds serious and painful. Why didn’t he just go home?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Who am I to say?” he answered with a wave of his hands. “He came to me and I took him in. And he is better. I don’t think he wanted his family seeing him swollen and in pain. Things like that can be embarrassing—for a young man to be so clumsy. They needn’t be concerned for him. He’s going to be fine. Best to get the worst past him before they see him, right? He’ll go home in a few days.” He took a step closer to her. “You keep this quiet and I’ll make sure his family knows he’s safe with a friend but I can’t have them coming to my place to see him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right,” she said, as a shiver of unease affected her whole body. Something wasn’t right about Harper’s story. She didn’t think a young man could fall and hurt himself that badly. “I’m glad I mentioned it, and I’ll stay quiet.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I knew you would. I trust you.” He gave her another genuine smile. “I’ll be off now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“One more thing before you go,” she said, hoping she wouldn’t sound as suspicious as she felt. “I wanted to know what happened about the card club you were looking to join. You seemed very excited about it. Did all that work out to your satisfaction?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not yet. Mr. Remick is open to my joining and considering the possibility. He’s quite skilled and is teaching me a few tricks about the games. I should be hearing from him soon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good,” she said, but really didn’t feel it was. “And, Mr. Browning?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper smiled with confidence. “He’s already been accepted. We’re finding it’s better to have our own club where we can play with people we know are safe.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Safe? That sounds disturbing and I’m not sure what you mean.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nothing,” he said with a quick smile and flippant tone. “It was an off-hand remark that meant nothing. Listen, I don’t want to keep you.” He kissed her cheeks again. “Tell Mrs. Stockton how good it was to see her again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not giving her time to question him more, he hurried out the door. Something felt wrong but she didn’t know what exactly. It just didn’t seem plausible Mr. Browning had a mysterious fall, and the word safe really had her troubled.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia came walking down the stairs, holding a pair of dark-brown boots. “These must be the right ones. They are the only pair in your room.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, they are. Thank you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia placed them beside the front door and asked, “Did you find out why Harper was here?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You heard him,” Brina said, more defensively than she intended, but Harper had her afraid to say anything about what she really felt. “To check on the house.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, no, there was more to it than that,” Julia said, not letting Brina off the hook as easily as she’d hoped. “Besides, Harper had something in his coat pocket.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What are you talking about?” She gave Julia a curious look. “I didn’t see anything.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Probably because you were so stunned to see him at all. I couldn’t tell what it was. He put his cloak on before he even reached down to give you a kiss. Didn’t you notice how odd that seemed?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina hadn’t noticed but she knew he was clearly hiding things about Mr. Browning and his card club and that had her curious as well as worried, but she didn’t want Julia to know that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What could he be hiding, and more to the point, why would he be hiding anything from us? I felt he was acting a little strange. Maybe even a little nervous but so was I. Neither of us expected the other to be here and it was quite unsettling at first.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It was that and more,” Julia insisted, refusing to give up stance on the subject.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You aren’t suggesting he was taking anything from the house, are you?” Brina said, not willing to go that far with her suspicions but agreeing there was cause for concern.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m only commenting on my observation. I know Harper had something in his pocket and it seemed to me he was trying to hide it with his cloak. I’m not saying he took anything from here. It could have been something he brought into the house with him, but whichever, he didn’t want you to see it and ask about it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Suddenly feeling warm, Brina unfastened her cape and laid it on the table with her reticule. She didn’t know what to think. Yes, it was odd Harper was in her parents’ home. It was odd that Mr. Browning had fallen and was convalescing at Harper’s home.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You may be right,” Brina admitted with some reservation. She’d known Harper all her life. She couldn’t start believing the worst of him. “But I’m not sure what I can do about a young man’s secrets, or habits. And I don’t want to believe he was here for any bad reason.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina didn’t like doubting Harper’s story but this was the second, no third time Harper wasn’t acting himself when he was with her. And it didn’t help her feelings that Julia had been suspicious, too. Something had turned Harper into a different person.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia folded her arms across her chest, “Then, we’ll leave it at that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Brina said more confidently than she was feeling. “Let’s do forget about this conversation with him and put our minds on something far more pleasant while we look through Mama’s painting materials.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You lead the way,” Julia said. “I’ll follow.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina started down the corridor. She wanted to talk with Zane about this. The earl might be a scoundrel and gambler at heart, but she had no doubt he cared for his cousin. He would want to know that Mr. Browning had been injured. Zane had proven he was quite fond of Mr. Browning, but how could she mention this to him when she’d promised Harper she’d keep quiet about where he was and the fall?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Besides, she couldn’t start relying on the earl. She had enough worries about what she was feeling about him, about the approaching end to the Season and what would be expected of her if the earl kept all her mandates.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Oh, what a troublesome man he was. If only he hadn’t come into her life and upset it just as she was getting her balance again.</p>
  </body>
</topic>