<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_5" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 3</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 3</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina Feld entered the front door of her house and caught the mouth-watering scent of fresh-baked bread, cooked fruit, and cinnamon filling the air. A pleasant change from the common smells of oil polish, beeswax, and burnt wood that so often lingered in the rooms. She could hardly wait to cut into one of Mrs. Lawton’s fruit tarts, spread it with butter and eat as many of them as she wanted.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Nothing invigorated Brina more than a brisk walk to Town when the sun was shining brightly, and the air was as chilling as dipping her bare toes into a deep winter stream. And having some of the girls from the school join her made it an especially pleasing day. Much to the girls’ delight, they had spent the morning in Town looking through the collections of merchandise at several shops. None of the girls had ever had a reason to venture inside a business establishment and it was a good learning experience for them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Their first stop had been at the largest linen draper in London. It sold a wide variety of different fabrics. Fanny hadn’t wanted to leave it. Next on the list was the haberdashery which was Mathilda’s favorite shop. The number of buttons, ribbons and lace the store carried was astounding to them all. The last place they went into was the milliner. None of the four girls were impressed with the shop. They all wanted to sew beautiful gowns and dresses trimmed with bows, flowers and beads. Not make hats.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It made Brina happy to see awe and wonder in their faces as they looked around the shops. She wasn’t sure everyone would be pleased with her decision to parade the girls downtown and then taking them into some of the stores, but she didn’t care. It was an enlightening and well-deserved outing for the older girls who now had two years of schooling behind them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Now Brina was eager for Adeline and Julia to arrive so she could tell them about some of her plans for the future. She wanted to give the girls’ painting lessons. Perhaps it was a bit frivolous for girls learning the seamstress trade to engage in a Society lady’s pastime.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But, so be it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina wanted to do all she could to see the girls had some refinement and enjoyment along with their arduous studies and the task of learning the seamstress trade. They were all doing so well with a needle now. She’d argue that painting could prove useful in teaching them where to place bows, ribbons, and add an embroidery of flowers on a dress.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Too, she had to invite Harper to dinner soon. She’d promised her father she’d stay in touch with her cousin. And she wanted to. She’d had a lingering concern about him. The last time she’d seen Harper he had a cut lip and the faint shade of bruising around his mouth. It hadn’t seemed proper to ask him about it. Perhaps her father had seen that, too and wanted Brina to make sure he was now doing fine.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper was a happy and mild-mannered person, but she supposed it was inevitable for a young man to get into scuffles from time to time and take one on the chin. Even well brought-up men like her cousin were sure to have disagreements that ended badly from time to time. It was just part of the male nature. And it was Brina’s nature to want to care for people and help them if she could.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Shedding her woolen cape, she draped it across a chair in the entry and started untying the bow under her chin. It felt wonderful to be in a home of her own. She loved her parents, but they were overwhelming at times. They doted on her, smothered her with affection and sheltered her with protection. For a time she had needed that, but she was glad to have finally left their home to make her own way in life. The two months she’d been living in the house in front of the school had been the most contented she could remember in years.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Now that her parents were off on their journey to Northcumberland to visit her mother’s sister, Brina felt as if she were truly on her own and it was a freeing feeling. The glorious spring weather had brought her many wonderful ideas. The list of things she wanted to accomplish for the girls’ school and the charitable work she did for The Sisters of Pilwillow Crossings were many and it was growing longer every day. She was going to rejoin the reading society, return to her painting and embrace the oy living life again after years of—</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Let me help you with those things, Mrs. Feld,” her housekeeper said, hurrying up the corridor toward the entrance.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you, Mrs. Lawton, but no need. I can manage this. It smells as if your special tarts are ready to come out of the oven.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And I have water heating for tea, but there’s something I have to tell you first.” She moved closer to Brina and whispered, “There’s a gentleman in the drawing room waiting to see you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A gentleman waiting for her? Brina laid her bonnet on top of her cape and started pulling on the fingers of her gloves. Because Mrs. Lawton whispered, Brina felt she must, too. “You know I don’t receive gentlemen callers.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I do,” the housekeeper said, softly but emphatically. “I told him you weren’t here, thinking that would be the end of it and he’d go away, but instead, he said he’d wait for you. He then took it upon himself to walk right past me and into the house. I didn’t know what to do but show him to the drawing room.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That doesn’t sound like something a gentleman would do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, he’s not 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">just </i>
      a gentleman, Mrs. Feld,” she continued in her whispered, but excited voice, her wide-eyed gaze sweeping over to the masculine cloak and hat that lay on a chair on the opposite side of the vestibule. “He said he was an earl and needed to speak to you, so he’d wait.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">An earl to see her? How odd. And which one? There must be close to half a dozen presently in London. Parliament was in session and the Season’s first ball was already behind them. But why would any of them want to see her? Unless . . . she studied a moment on the thought his visit might have something to do with the school in the building behind the house. She and her two friends had thought there might be protests from some people in the ton or the neighborhood when they started the small private boarding school, but that had been over two years ago.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did he say what he wanted?” Brina asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Lawton shook her head and picked up Brina’s cape and bonnet. “But of course I asked him,” she admitted without guile. “Not to be rude but wondering if I might assist him for you. He said it was of a private matter he’d take up with you. Who am I to question an earl further?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Titled or not, Brina wondered how she should confront a man who would all but barge into a lady’s house. She didn’t have more than a second or two before she heard the strong sure sound of masculine boots hitting the hardwood floor.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s all right, Mrs. Lawton.” She handed the housekeeper her gloves. “I’ll take care of this. You go finish preparing for Julia and Adeline.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The housekeeper quietly left and, from behind her, Brina heard a man say, “I thought I heard someone talking.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That same spark of awareness that she’d only felt one other time slithered through Brina. She went perfectly still.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Her</i>masked stranger.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Here in 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">her</i>
      house?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Was it possible? A touch of awe and fear raced through her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She had never seen the man’s face, not all of it anyway, but she recognized his voice. She’d never forget his tone barking orders at her to free him and then saying 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">thank you</i>
      in the most sensual manner she could ever imagine. With a kiss that still took her breath when she thought about it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The footsteps stopped close behind her. A dizzying wave of near panic swelled her chest. Her stomach quivered. Just as it had been in Paris, there was no escape for her. What was she to do? It was one thing to daydream about him, as she had, but quite another to come face-to-face with him again. Something she never thought would happen.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">On the glimmer of hope she might be wrong, she turned. Their eyes met and held. It was him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Merciful heavens. </i>He was more handsome and powerful-looking than she’d remembered. Thick, black hair was combed away from his broad, masculine brow and fell to the top of his collar at the nape. His cheekbones were high and well-defined. His narrow, high-bridged nose added to the rugged look of his lightly square chin and jaw. The fit of his fawn-colored coat across his shoulders was exceptional and emphasized his broad, muscular chest. She was intensely aware of the strength and command that emanated from his body. Her pulse raced and her muscles coiled tightly at seeing him again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">In that moment, somehow she knew they’d been destined to meet again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded once. “Mrs. Feld, I am Blacknight.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her breath caught and swirled in her chest as she stood spellbound by who he was. The way his gaze swept down her face and slowly back to her eyes sent her senses reeling. It was almost too much to take in. Unbelievably so. She had rescued the man who was known far and wide as the black sheep of the Blacknight family.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She’d heard rumors of his wild escapades for years. His father had died when he was a babe and his mother and school masters had never been able to tame him into a respectable gentleman. Just weeks ago, he had become an earl and head of the family that had all but disowned him for his ruinous behavior.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina managed a belated curtsey as many thoughts became an incoherent jumble in her mind. Had he known who she was that night in Paris or found out later? That was over three months ago. What was he doing at her house now?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have heard of you,” she said cautiously, not wanting to let on that she recognized him until she knew for sure whether he remembered her. There could be many reasons for his visit and she didn’t want to presume anything.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t believe we’ve been formally introduced.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” she whispered softly. “We haven’t.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He tilted his head in questioning before a hint of a smile played at the corners of his mouth. “But, you do remember me?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Oh, yes.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wasn’t likely to forget a man who was dressed only in his shirt and trousers and tied to a chair. Or his shocking embrace and unforgettable kiss once she’d freed him. And truth be told, she’d caught herself wondering from time to time if she ever crossed his mind the way he had hers since he fled the room.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was best to start with the most reasonable question. “How do you know my name?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“By chance. I recognized you walking down the street with the girls this morning. I asked my uncle about you. I could never forget you, Mrs. Feld. Or what you did for me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The kiss he gave her came searing across her senses again as it had so many times. And then another horror struck her. What must he be thinking about her now? She was known throughout the ton as the widow who’d never given up her widow’s weeds. Yet, he’d seen her clothed in a voluminous pink satin gown. How had she lowered her defenses and allowed Aunt Josette to talk her into wearing the lavish costume? Clearly the mask had not hidden her identity as her aunt had insisted.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Should we talk about that evening in Paris?” he asked when she remained quiet.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why would we?” she answered quickly gathering some measure of control. Lifting her chin and shoulders, she hoped she didn’t look as stricken as she suddenly felt.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Perhaps because we both know why I was there, but I have no idea why you were at the ball.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina didn’t want him to know her reasons. Motives that appeared logical at the time, now seemed foolish. But, what was he thinking? That she led two different lives?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t think an answer to that is necessary.” She silently inhaled deeply to steady herself and took a step back from him. “We were at a masquerade. I believe the purpose of such evenings is things that happen there are not talked about later.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes narrowed but held steady on hers. For a moment, she thought he might question her further but, thankfully, he merely nodded acceptance of her statement.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If you’re here because you fear I might tell someone about what I did for—what happened at the ball, you can rest assured I haven’t spoken a word about that night to anyone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He chuckled softly, and she found even that quite inviting. Every little thing about him made her take notice. How could that be? She didn’t want to be attracted to him or any man. She had helped him when he needed it and that was all. That was enough.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not worried about that, Mrs. Feld. You could tell the whole of London how you found me, and no one would be shocked or think it out of the ordinary that you stumbled upon me in such a compromised state.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What he said was probably true. She had heard talk and knew how some in his family viewed him. However, they would be surprised to learn she was there and dressed as she was.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As if reading her mind, he added, “On my honor and the Blacknight family, I will never disclose to anyone when, how, or where we met the first time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She believed him and gave a silent thank you.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I hope you were able to accomplish your mission on your nephew’s behalf.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Robert’s my cousin. And, I arrived just in time. I hauled him over to Vienna and, within the week, he’d found someone new to bestow his affections on.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, of course. I recognize the name Robert Browning. I’ve met him at parties. He’s usually with my cousin, Harper Tabor, who I’ve always thought of as more a brother than cousin. Neither of us had siblings. I suppose it’s good your cousin’s heart wasn’t broken for too long.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was sure that would be the case.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina cleared her throat softly before saying, “Well, thank you for stopping by to let me know he is doing well and that you know who I am. It will make it easier between us now should we meet again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl made no motion to move but remained in his relaxed stance, though his expression was of a more serious nature. “I do have another reason for coming over that has nothing to do with our previous meeting. Something more important.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His words intrigued her, causing her chest to flutter again. For a fleeting moment she wondered if he might have another daring rescue to attend. Whether or not he intended it, everything about him was seductive. A fact that made it difficult to shy away from him as was her usual course with all gentlemen.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her gaze settled fully on his. “What could that be?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s something I felt obligated to tell you so it wouldn’t come as a shock when you hear it from others.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Tensing, her mind flew back to the extraordinary evening in Paris. “Do others already know about Paris? Will there be gossip about us?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The seriousness left his eyes. An engaging smile prefaced his statement, “You worry too much, Mrs. Feld. I’m sure no one in London knows about that evening unless, of course, you told someone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Me? No. Certainly not,” she said, a bit indignant that he should even think she might tell on herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina hadn’t even mentioned the incident to her best friends, Adeline and Julia. Though, she had been tempted more than once to ravish them with details about her unexpected adventure and the kiss that had stolen her thoughts ever since. Now that she knew who he was, she would be even more tempted to tell them of her discovery in that chateau.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But there was no need to let him know that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Then our secret is safe.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For now, she thought.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I placed a wager in the betting book at White’s this afternoon, and after doing so, I realized it was only fair that I be the one to come over and tell you about it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina looked at him with almost as much inquisitiveness as she had the first time seeing him and smiled. “Why would your wagers be of interest to me, my lord?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Because this one concerns you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was something challenging in his eyes. A curl of suspicion and nip of intrigue teased her chest as she watched his eyes rake down her face again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t understand. Whatever are you talking about?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It appears that I am in great need of something specific to show my family I can be responsible and not see the earldom of Blacknight come to ruin. My family is in a near state of panic because I have become the earl. The misfortune that happened wasn’t something any of us could have foreseen. Me least of all. Be that as it may, it comes with certain expectations.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">No doubt. They must be shaking in their collective boots. His reputation of a gambler was well known. He certainly knew how to pique her curiosity. “Again, my lord. I’m finding that none of what you have to say has anything to do with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My uncles are convinced that a suitable bride would go a long way toward helping change me into the respectable head of the family I need to be and settling down all the strained nerves of the Blacknight lineage. I knew if anyone could do that for me it would be you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Me?” Her voice remained calm though she wasn’t certain she was. “You can’t be serious.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wholly serious. I wagered that you would accept my proposal of marriage and we’d announce our engagement by midnight at the last ball of the Season.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A light-headedness flashed through her briefly. Brina had no idea if she could believe he had actually done such a thing. “What nonsense you speak of.” She smiled, and then laughed a little, even though there wasn’t a trace of humor in his face. He was sober, his eyes were steady and clear. Still, she added, “That’s preposterous, my lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Presumptuous, I’ll admit to. Why would you think it preposterous I’d want to marry you?” he asked with soft intensity to his tone and his expression.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With wary amusement and a determination to remain unruffled by his admissions, she offered, “Let’s start with the fact that you don’t know me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know all I need to about you. You helped a stranger when he was in desperate circumstances and expected nothing in return. That speaks well of you, Mrs. Feld. So do my uncles. You are loyal, principled, and you’re even more beautiful without your mask.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She felt uneasy about his praise and tactfully refrained from making a comment about it. “But what of you? Making a wager at a gentleman’s club is not the proper way to propose to a lady and let her know you want to marry her.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Which goes to my point,” he offered, realizing her not even her painstaking sensibilities bothered him. “I need you by my side to help me become respectable. I need to know how to say and do all the proper things expected of an earl. You could do me the honor of accepting my proposal of marriage right now. If you will, the bet would then have no relevance, and I’d be well on my way to reassuring my family that I’m capable of doing something to please them and that all was not lost when I became the earl.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">This wasn’t a foolhardy trick he was playing on her. He was serious. Because of that, she had to be serious, too. “I have no intentions of marrying anyone,” she said willfully. “Now, nor ever. When your uncle told you my name, he should have also told you that. It’s not a secret.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded slowly. “Though it’s been a few years, I remembered your story. I know how you became a widow, about the school behind this house, and the friends who helped you start it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. Perhaps what you don’t know is that I am quite content in my unwed state. I don’t know why you would do something so wild and reckless as to make a wager such as this. It’s most extraordinary. Why not be sensible and simply pick from any number of young ladies who will be entering the marriage mart this week and would be more than willing to marry you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not a sensible person, Mrs. Feld, but I never make a bet I don’t plan to win.” He paused before continuing and took a step closer to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not sensible? How many people would admit to such a thing? But it must be true. Look what he’d done. Brina stared all the more intently at him, refusing to give in and enjoy the gentle way her abdomen rolled and tightened in response to his nearness.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You have all the qualities of a good person that I don’t have,” he offered. “We are a perfect match.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Anger began mixing with shock. Her courage strengthened. “What?” Brina bristled but stood her ground. “How can you say such a false statement so innocently? We are not a perfect anything.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I believe we are.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” she argued forcibly. “We’re complete opposites.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Which will make for a very interesting life between us. I am the blackguard of the ton and you are an impeccable, saintly widow who’s loved by all.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Saintly,” she whispered as if the word were vile.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It pierced her like a dull dagger. She felt the familiar weight of heaviness in her chest whenever she was reminded of her past. It pained her that anyone thought her such a good person. She wasn’t. Grief, she’d found could lessen, but guilt was a much heavier burden to lighten. It was a weight that never truly went away. She looked up at the earl, knowing he had no idea the haunting memories his words sent rushing back to her. Memories she decided long ago would never go away.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Some may think that,” she said softly. “But let me assure you, I am not flawless. Others may not know it, but I do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His brows drew together in concern. “My words troubled you. I didn’t mean for them to.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His perceptiveness unnerved her, and she lowered her head so he couldn’t see more of her pain. She was beginning a new, stronger and better life that was free of her past, her hurts, and her faults. She wasn’t going to let this rogue and his shenanigans done for his own purposes upset her plans to move forward.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I need you to leave, my lord,” she said, shaking off the bewildering feeling of his sudden appearance in her life and his revelation of what he wanted. “You have no right to come into my life and disrupt it in such a fashion. I want nothing to do with any of your nonsense or wagers. I have my friends, the girls at the school, the women at the abbey, and other responsibilities that need my attention.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I need your help, too, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But I don’t need you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He remained calm but seemed to study on her words for a moment before he shrugged. “Whether or not you will agree to marry me at the end of the Season doesn’t need to be settled now. Just the fact that you will allow me to court you so that you can help me with all the proper things an earl should do will help appease my family’s disposition.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, so that is it,” she whispered, suddenly more irritated than troubled and not afraid to let it show. “What a beast you are! Once again you expect me to come to your aid and free you from a problem you’ve gotten yourself into. Well, I can’t help you with this one.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His stead gaze didn’t waver. “You are the only one who can.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t be ridiculous. If you want to become a better person and act like an earl, hire someone to teach you. You don’t need to court or marry anyone to learn how to put aside your bad behavior and say and do the right things by people, or to be a proper gentleman. You are the reason you misbehave and no one can fix it but 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">you</i>
      .”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am not doing this simply because you will be a mere convenience for me.” He lowered his voice. “There’s more to why I chose you and you know it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” she whispered, cautiously, unsure what he might say.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“There is the matter of attraction between us.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A warmth of fluttery sensations swirled in her lower stomach once again. His words were softly spoken, almost beguiling her with their honesty. Despite her anger at what he’d done, shivers of anticipation tightened her breasts. He moved even closer to her, invading a space she never allowed gentlemen to enter. With the tips of his fingers, he gently lifted her chin. His touch seared her with the desire to fall into his arms when what she should do was jerk away from him. It was impossible to keep her insides from trembling with expectancy as she looked into his deep blue eyes and thrill to his warm touch.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You feel it as surely as I do,” he said huskily.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes. She did but she didn’t know why. He was considered a rake by everyone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You know what it is,” he continued in that seductive tone that washed over her like healing warm water. “That unidentifiable feeling of interest that stirs, swells, and draws us to another person. It feeds us, fills us, and eventually overtakes our thoughts, our senses, and our lives. It makes us want to know everything about the person.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know what you are talking about,” she insisted, dismayed that she knew exactly what he was describing. “There is no such thing,” she fibbed to the rogue with only minimal regret. If a man was so uncouth to say such things to a lady, she shouldn’t be expected to answer truthfully.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Deny it if you must, but it’s there.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina moved her face from his touch but put no distance between them. “Even if I were to consider your outrageous proposal, which I’m not, what would be the benefit to me other than to have my named tarnished as much as yours?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If we were to marry, a home. Children.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes, most ladies wanted that even above love from their husbands. She smiled and tilted her chin up again, confident in her answer. “I have a home, my lord. You are standing in it. I have children. Ten of them I can see every day in the school behind this house.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Then I agree there’s not much I can offer you.” The inflection in his tone was conciliatory but not defeated. “No doubt a gentleman would take you at your word and not impose on your sensibilities further. However, we know I’m far from a gentleman. And because of the brief time we spent together earlier in the year, I know that you are cautious, but also curious. Intelligent, but eager to learn new things. And I believe you are more free-spirited than you want anyone to know. If nothing else, I can promise it would be an adventure filled with passion if you were married to me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With each word he spoke her breaths grew shorter and deeper. She believed that, too, but couldn’t hint to him that was true. She couldn’t let this rogue upset her well-planned life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked him boldly in the eyes and stated, “I am not looking for adventure or passion.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her a quiet look of disbelief. “Our kiss was brief but passionate. You would have loved it if I had taken you with me that night in Paris. I started to offer.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Had he?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was tempted to grab your hand and sweep you along with me. I held you so tightly you must have felt my hesitation after our kiss. But I had to move fast. Unfortunately, your skirts would have slowed me down as I raced through the streets.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes. How had he known she’d thought about insisting she go if she freed him?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But unlike him, Brina knew when she made a mistake. Attending the masquerade was one. She wasn’t about to make another one. Her life was settled now. She wouldn’t be drawn into this man’s unacceptable lifestyle and certainly for no other reason than he needed her to make him a better person for his family.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am not interested in your wagers or your adventurous games. My advice is that you should take back your wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He made no move to leave. “No gambler ever withdraws his bet, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Perhaps not a gambler then, but a gentleman realizes when he’s overstepped propriety and rectifies it. And if that were not enough to tempt you to do the right thing, you’re an earl now. Surely that should give you the clout you need to call back your ill-conceived wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I want you, Mrs. Feld. I’d much rather win your hand after a hard-fought battle than as an easy coup. I am a gambling man. The bet holds and I plan to win.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A chill rippled down her spine. Her composure seemed shaken as she digested his words. The way he looked at her, for a moment she thought he might catch her up in his arms and kiss her as he had in Paris. All the things she’d felt when his lips touched hers washed over her again. It had been divine. His arms had been strong. They wrapped completely around her. His chest was hard and warm. She thought she’d never feel those things again but now he was so close she only had to—</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are we interrupting anything?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">At the sound of her friend’s voice, Brina stepped away from the earl and looked toward the open doorway. Julia and Adeline stood just inside looking quite perplexed, glancing from Brina to Blacknight. They had never seen her alone with a man. Especially one standing so inappropriately close to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, not at all,” Brina said, hoping she didn’t sound as nervous and as breathless as she was. “Nothing. We weren’t doing anything—but talking. I’m glad you’re here. So glad. The earl was just saying good-bye.” She took in a deep breath and steadied herself. Being caught with the Town rake practically had her stumbling over her words. She picked up the earl’s coat and hat from the chair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Blacknight bowed and said, “Lady Lyon. Mrs. Stockton.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia and Adeline curtseyed and returned the greeting.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s a pleasure to see you both again,” the earl continued, “But as Mrs. Feld said, I was just leaving.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He took the things Brina held out for him and leaned in close to her ear. “It’s been a long time since I’ve had to pursue a lady, Mrs. Feld. I’m looking forward to it, but don’t be mistaken. I intend to go after you rigorously and win your hand. I’ll see you at the grand ball Saturday evening.”</p>
  </body>
</topic>