<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_12" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 10</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 10</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane walked through the front door of the earl’s home shedding his outer clothing and stopped suddenly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What was he thinking? It was his home now. He was the earl. Not his uncle, nor his uncle’s son, nor his older cousin. But him. They were all gone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Damnation!</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Why had all three of them been riding in the same carriage together that day anyway? Why hadn’t someone inspected the damned bridge over the canyon since there’d been weeks of torrential rain? Didn’t they know Zane was ill-prepared to take over for them? This wasn’t supposed to be his lot in life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He wasn’t supposed to be the earl.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He rubbed his hand across the back of his neck. He needed a drink.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Huffing another silent curse of frustration, he felt something, reached into his pocket, and pulled out the book of poetry Mrs. Feld had given him. He scoffed a laugh and wondered if she would take him to task if she knew he was swearing like the devil in his thoughts.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Probably.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He laid the book on the side table but then picked it up. The corners worn. She’d read it often. Maybe he’d give it a try. After all, he had pursued her in an ungentlemanly manner. Consciously, maybe even willfully. She hadn’t deserved it, but he wasn’t sorry he had done it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">In return she’d given as good as she got.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She was uncommonly headstrong for someone who had the look of a fragile night fairy with her glistening blonde hair, big bright eyes, and fair, delicate-looking skin.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He hadn’t planned to kiss her in the park, but it was a damned good thing he’d thought to exempt kissing. She’d been particular with the rules set forth. Her passion had been just as strong when in his arms as it had been when she laid out her demands for acceptance of his proposal. He had no doubt that she would claim victory if he so much as sniffed a brandy and that strength challenged him to be stronger. That passion inside her is what drew him. He’d sensed it that night in the chateau and ever since he’d wanted to taste her lips once more.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For the better part of half an hour during the afternoon, he’d watched her be composed and measured in everything she said at the park. Her beautiful lips smiling at him, her graceful hands had laid clasped in repose on her lap. She’d been the personification of everything he’d heard about her. Kissing her had awakened an aching need inside him that he still carried.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After dropping his great coat, hat, and gloves onto a chair in the entryway, he slid his scarf from around his neck and gathered the center of it into his hands to press into his face. The flowery scent of her perfume had held in the wool, teasing him with her fragrance.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He inhaled again, deeper, letting the memory of her in his arms wash slowly through him once again. It had an eager, rousing effect on him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Thoughts of her sparkling eyes, the wind grabbing at strands of her hair and blowing it across her soft cheeks drifted pleasantly through his mind before suddenly he remembered how still she’d become when he mentioned her husband.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His question had surprised her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It had surprised Zane, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was no real reason to ask about him other than it had suddenly crossed his mind she might be thinking about him when she mentioned the chocolate. Plenty of men and women enjoyed a dash of brandy in the sweet liquid. Evidently, she hadn’t been. That pleased Zane and he wondered if she always looked as if she was barely holding back tears when she spoke of her husband, or if it was just that he’d so unexpectedly asked about the man. That couldn’t have been easy for her, yet she’d handled his surprising comment well.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The tragedy of becoming a widow must have changed her to some degree? He wondered what she was like before that happened. She hadn’t been ready to talk about Mr. Feld with Zane. Without her doing that, he couldn’t get an idea of how deep her wounds of loss were now that time had passed. He wanted to know even though he was very sure of one thing—it made no difference to him. It was too her credit that five years after Mr. Feld’s death, she still was moved by talking about him. That she had great respect and admiration for him was evident. That was just one more thing to admire about her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He also knew Mrs. Feld wasn’t indifferent to his touch. It was who she was today that had him caught in her unintended snare. How could he not be drawn to a lady who had stayed respectful of her husband’s memory, wanted to teach girls the beautiful art of painting, and helped nuns take care of unfortunate people?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane closed his eyes, letting the memory of her fill him again. His mind drifted back to their kiss and the feel and taste of her cool, enticing lips beneath his. Her hands had moved with hunger up his chest before they settled in womanly comfort around his neck. Their lingering kiss in the park had proven what he’d known since Paris and she had to believe now as well. She was just as attracted to him as he was to her. So, to her question, hell, no. He didn’t want to stop being bad. He wanted to tumble her onto the bed and press—</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Multiple footfalls sounded down the corridor and the familiar tapping of Uncle Hector’s cane. Zane looked up to see his Uncles Syl and Hector coming toward him at a jaunty pace.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“There you are,” Uncle Sylvester called. “Finally home, I see.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How did it go?” Hector asked in a jovial tone as he stopped in front of Zane and leaned on his cane.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Was she cordial?” Sylvester echoed with an enthusiasm he didn’t try to keep hidden either.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane blinked. “What are you—were you two waiting here for me to return?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course,” Uncle Syl replied as he stopped in front of Zane. “You didn’t expect us to leave, did you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s eyes narrowed and he frowned. “Yes, I did.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">These two men were unbelievable. Their counsel with the family and helping him learn the affairs of his estates was appreciated. He really did need their help with those things, but sometimes they were a bit overwhelming. He didn’t need them playing the role of nursemaid.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester pressed his hands down the sides of his coat and took a proud stance. “How would we find out how your afternoon went if we’d gone home?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You wouldn’t,” Zane argued.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s what we thought, so considered it best we stay in case there was anything we could help with.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Tell us all about it,” Uncle Hector encouraged.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Zane said in a rather forceful tone. “I have no intentions of sharing anything of my afternoon with Mrs. Feld with you two or anyone else.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His uncles glanced at each other as if they were facing a grave situation they didn’t know how to handle before centering their attention back to their nephew.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I take it that means it didn’t go well.” Hector emphasized his words with a sudden hard rap of his cane to the floor.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It went very well, Zane thought, but felt no inclination to satisfy these two ninny grumps.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He probably didn’t watch his language as closely as he should have,” Uncle Syl offered. “Ladies don’t like to be spoken to in an ungentlemanly manner.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s difficult for most of us sometimes,” Hector supplied. “But we learn to do it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I suppose it will take time,” his brother mumbled quietly as if he didn’t want Zane to hear him. “We may be expecting too much, too soon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did she at least enjoy the ride in the new curricle your uncle had built last winter?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That caught Zane’s interest. “The earl has a new carriage?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Uncle Syl informed him. “Quite a pricey one from what I heard. I’m not sure he had it out more than a time or two before the winter weather took a turn for the worse.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why haven’t you told me about this before now?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hector and Sylvester looked at each other. It appeared neither of them had thought to mention what was by all accounts considered a younger man’s transportation and something Zane would want to know about.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We’ve had more important matters to discuss with you than a sporting carriage,” Syl argued.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane would make sure to take it out for a jaunt first thing tomorrow morning—before his uncles arrived.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“This afternoon with Mrs. Feld is in the past,” Hector continued in a disappointed tone. “Nothing to do about that now. Best to move forward and do better. What dinner party will the two of you be attending tonight?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What do you mean?” Zane questioned.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s the Season, my lord,” Uncle Syl said in an irritated tone where Hector left off. “There are several parties in Mayfair and other places about Town. Didn’t you arrange to meet with Mrs. Feld at one of them—at a certain time?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.” Tonight hadn’t crossed his mind. He’d been too busy enjoying the afternoon. Their conversation, their kisses, and the way his kiss had caused her cheeks to flush as she melted against his chest.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Uncle Hector’s cane made another sharp click on the floor. His gray, full eyebrows seemed to grow together tightly right before Zane’s eyes. “Then how will you know where she will be and at what time so you can be there as well? If you are going to pursue her, my lord, you must 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">pursue</i>
      her.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Tension started in the back of Zane’s neck.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester made a motion with his hands as if to calm the more excitable Hector. “Don’t get too riled about this. It’s easy enough to remedy. He can send over a note to her and ask where she plans to be at half past nine and meet her there.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s a bit late in the day for that. She may not answer him now that he didn’t ask her at the proper time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, no. It’s not.” Uncle Syl looked at Zane. “I’ll help you compose the note. I’m quite good at knowing the right things to say to a lady on occasions like this.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">This was maddening. Uncle Syl had never married. How could he know what to say to a lady? The only thing Zane wanted to do was pour himself a glass of claret, relax by the warm, crackling fire in his book room and reminisce on the afternoon with Mrs. Feld. Thinking about her was certainly much more pleasant than listening to his uncles blather or reflect on their priorities.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Making the circle of parties during the Season wasn’t something Zane had ever enjoyed. Which was why he’d never spent much time doing it. He didn’t see the sense of playing this game with Mrs. Feld. She was a widow after all. Not an innocent maiden who always had to be guarded. If he wanted to see her why couldn’t he just go to her house and spend an evening with her?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Because of rules, manners, and Society’s strict code of acceptable behavior. Blast them all.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His uncles continued to look at him, waiting for a response. “I will figure out something for later in the week.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Later?” Hector exclaimed as his chin bobbed and the cane tapped. “You have four weeks to win her hand and you are talking about later?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I will pursue Mrs. Feld in my own way, uncles. I need no instructions or rules from either of you on that. She has already given me enough to follow. Now, have Fulton get your coats and go home. We are through for the day.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, yes, we’re going,” Uncle Syl said, once again giving his brother the signal to be calmer. “Before we do, I wanted to tell you that a friend of yours, Mr. Robins dropped by to see you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Harry was here? Did you entertain one of my guests?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, not at all. Naturally, when we heard someone at the door, we came out of the book room, thinking it might be you. At that point, we had to speak to him, but he decided not to wait when he found out we were already waiting.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That was best, Zane thought. Harry wasn’t the kind of man who would find favor with his uncles. Nor them with him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He was kind enough to tell us what he wanted.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane couldn’t believe what he was hearing. “Did you ask him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not exactly,” Syl said, his brow rising.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What someone wants with me and why they came to my door is none of your business,” Zane said, in a tone that would have let an ordinary man know he had stepped over the line. He couldn’t be sure these two would know that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, we couldn’t agree more,” Uncle Syl agreed with so much pride his chest puffed. “But we are happy he relayed to us that the bets at White’s were up tenfold today.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But unfortunately, not in your favor it seems,” Uncle Hector added. “Hardly anyone thinks you will win Mrs. Feld’s hand. We expected that but are pleased everyone wants a stake in the outcome of your wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane shook his head. Not only did he have to deal with these two, it seemed as if he’d become both an earl and a saint almost overnight. If not for Mrs. Feld’s requirements, he’d be swearing like a drunken idiot at these two and downing all the liquor he could get his hands on.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Out of the corner of his eye, Zane saw movement down the hallway. “Fulton,” he called. “My uncles are leaving. Get their coats.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, yes, of course, we’re leaving,” Uncle Hector said, pulling down on the lapels of his tweed coat. “We have things to do. But one more thing before we go. Did you consider whether you’ll grant your cousin Pelroy the right to build a home on the south end of Blacknight? He only wants a small cottage by the stream that runs through that hollow.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Zane answered irritably. “You just made the request this morning. As I told you and all the family a few nights ago, I’d rather know all that I’m in charge of before I start giving grants away. Everyone keeps what allowances they have but that’s all I’m willing to do for now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“In that case, I’ll tell him it’s still under consideration. And what about Ivan?” Uncle Hector continued as if Zane hadn’t said what he’d just said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane searched his memory for someone in the family named Ivan and came up blank. “I’ll let you know later.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, do. Your Aunt Beatrice would appreciate it if you’d see fit to buy him a commission in the army.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Now, Zane remembered. Ivan wasn’t a Browning. He was Hector’s wife’s sister’s son. All these requests could make a strong, stable man dizzy. How would he keep them all straight? He would find a way, and Zane would grant his aunt’s wish. He was wanted to help any man ready to take up arms and fight for England. “I’ll set time aside in the coming days to go over all the requests.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Fair enough,” Sylvester answered. “There will probably be more later in the week. Now, we’ll see you tomorrow morning. Bright and early as usual.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I wouldn’t have it any other way,” Zane murmured tightly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Leaving his butler to see his uncles out, Zane strode down toward the book room. The tapping of Hector’s cane echoed down the corridor. He didn’t know if it was that, his uncles’ unwanted presence when he’d returned, or the need for a drink that gave him a headache.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Rounding the doorway, he saw the mountain of ledgers still on his desk as he’d left them. A fire burned. The room was warm, quiet. What he really wanted to do was have a drink. A quick one followed by a long one, and then pick up his coat and gloves and head out to one of his clubs for a game of cards.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But he’d promised the prim widow he wouldn’t. He was going to play by her rules if it killed him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">All he wanted to do was forget the stack of ledgers, about the fact that he was now the earl. That it was his responsibility to consider and answer when his family wanted something.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Damnation, he didn’t want to do it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Life had prepared him to be a gamester not an earl. Which suddenly reminded him that the first thing he needed to do was write a note to Lord Lyonwood regretting that he would not be joining his card club. He would have thoroughly enjoyed the chance to sit around the table and match skills with any one of the men in that club.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He supposed he’d have to do some things the way Mrs. Feld, Society, and his uncles expected him, too. But he didn’t have to like it, and it sure as hell wouldn’t keep him for wishing he had his old life back.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane seated himself behind the desk, determined to put his nose into the account ledgers and keep his uncles and Mrs. Feld off his mind. He wanted to concentrate only on what was before him—the Blacknight Earldom and all its entities.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Later, obviously much later, Zane rose from the desk to stretch. Sometime during the late afternoon he had shed his coat and Fulton had come in to light the lamps and stoke the fire. Without thinking, he walked over to the side table and started to pour himself a nip of the expensive brandy that had been poured into the decanter just yesterday. But as his hand reached for it, he remembered his promise.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">No drink.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He slowly withdrew his hand. It had taken a strong will for her to have the nerve to challenge his way of life and she did so only because she didn’t think he could change. She’d said as much. She expected him to fail and have that drink. And she had good reason to believe that. He wanted a drink. But difficult as it would be, he had to match that iron will of hers and show her he could keep his commitment. He turned away from the brandy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Only a day had passed and already he knew it wasn’t going to be easy living up to Mrs. Feld’s standards. Long developed habits were difficult to break.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What was he to do tonight? Spend it watching others play. He could do it, though, as he found out last night, it wasn’t as enticing as it used to be when he was eager to learn all he could about cards and billiards. Blast it, Hector was right. He should have asked Mrs. Feld which parties she would be attending and planned to meet her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane walked over to the window and looked out. Through the tops of the trees and tall yew hedge a few lights flickered from windows of his neighbors’ houses. The twinkling sparkle reminded him of Mrs. Fe—Brina’s eyes.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes, he liked thinking of her as Brina. She wasn’t a Mrs. anymore. As she had so reverently pointed out there wasn’t a Mr. Feld. She wasn’t married.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Excuse me, my lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, Fulton?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mr. Robert Browning is here and wanted to know if you were available to see him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, tell him to join me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane didn’t know if he’d ever get used to the formality of being an earl. But he would try. For the family. He’d never minded Robert seeing him in a casual state when they were in Paris or Vienna, but things were different now. Zane strode over to the corner of the desk, picked up the coat he’d discarded earlier, and was stuffing his arms into the sleeves when Robert walked in.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The strapping twenty-two-year old man with a head full of dark-brown hair and laughing eyes stopped and bowed. “My lord. How gracious of you to receive me without benefit of a prior appointment.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane acknowledged him with a smile and they both laughed. Standing on ceremony with his cousin after all the time spent together in Paris and then Vienna wouldn’t happen anytime soon. They’d been too at ease with each other during their travels. In the meantime, it was good to know someone in the family was all right with him still being Zane.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It looks as if you are settling into your new role as earl quite well,” Robert offered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m adjusting, and glad you stopped by.” Zane leaned a hip against his desk and pointed toward a chair. “Sit down.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you, but I wasn’t going to stay long. I know how busy you are. I overheard father telling Mama that you had a lot to learn—well, yes, I will sit, but only for a minute.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t get nervous, Robert. I know what your father is saying about me. Hector is not a shy man, and especially not with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, he isn’t,” his cousin answered as he made himself comfortable in the upholstered chair. “In case you haven’t heard, I wanted to let you know that wagers similar to the one at White’s concerning you and Mrs. Feld are being made in other clubs in London.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Zane muttered with no small amount of interest. “I hadn’t heard that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Making a wager in the prestigious White’s was one thing—a gentleman’s right. He hadn’t expected the wager would become commonplace and Brina’s name would be bandied about other clubs and gaming houses in Town. He hadn’t thought through all the ramifications of his ploy before he’d acted on it. And, Brina’s deed, with all her conditions for him, was bound to have had an impact on what was happening, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not that he blamed her for anything she’d done. He admired her for fighting back. He did take issue with how clever her tactics were.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve been introduced to her, but I can’t say I know her. She’s quite beautiful.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">She is stunning.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Another reason I stopped by is that I was hoping you could spare me another one hundred pounds. There’s a game at The Brass Bull that Harper and I have been invited to join tonight. My pockets are too light right now to get into the first game.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Robert’s words disturbed Zane. “You don’t need to be involved in a high stakes games at your age or the amount of your allowance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve been assured the games won’t be steep initially, but of course, it really depends on the number who join. But Mr. Remick wants to make sure we can cover bets.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And Harper?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“His pockets have always been plumper than mine. He’s an only child and his father has been generous. I think his uncle—Mrs. Feld’s father helps him from time to time as well.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Is he a good player?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’d say we are even.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good,” Zane said and looked at his affable cousin. He liked the cheeky lad, but they were home now. Robert was Hector’s responsibility. “I gave you an extra hundred at the family dinner last week. You should still have more than enough to see you by until your allowance releases again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know.” He moved to the edge of his seat. “And I don’t want you to think I’m not grateful for your generosity. I am. All it takes is a few bad hands to get behind. You know that. Either luck is with you or she isn’t. It’s only a matter of time before my fortune turns bright again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane regarded Robert more carefully. One of the first rules of gaming that he tried to instill in his cousin was that sometimes fortune didn’t return. Some people were not meant to be gamesters. A hand or two of cards after a dinner party or on a rainy afternoon at one of his clubs was all the playing some gentlemen needed to do. He was thinking Robert might be that type person.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When Robert arrived unannounced in Paris, Zane hadn’t expected or wanted to become the young man’s caretaker, but out of respect for Hector he had taken him under his protection and started schooling him in the games. It appeared his cousin wanted to keep it that way even though he was under his father’s roof again. Robert was studious at times but more often than not, he was given to bouts of imprudent, impulsive gambling rather than taking it slow, steady, and judicious. At the time, it had suited Zane to tutor his cousin and keep him out of trouble, which he found out included matrimony.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had no other pressing priorities during his travels.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Now he had too many. He would never again have the carefree life he enjoyed before he became the earl. And he was finding out that he no longer had the patience, time, or the inclination for such tutelage. Robert was going to have to understand and rely on Hector for fatherly advice and his extra funds.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve tried to explain to you how important it is for you to get out of a game before you lose all you have,” Zane stated, trying not to sound as if he were giving a lecture. “You always save enough to play for another day. That’s how you learn to be good at gambling. Remember we talked about when your money runs low, you go.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know.” Robert’s expression was sincere. “I remember everything you taught me. A gamester shouldn’t hesitate. He needs to know how and which card to play as soon as it hits his hands. I do try to gain skill and play your way every time, but so often, it seems, what I have becomes less and less each night until it’s gone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We went over this when we were in Vienna. You either get better at remembering the cards that have been played, how to use what you have, or you don’t play as often or as deep.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I do,” he said convincingly. “If you’ll just let me have a hundred for tonight, I promise I’ll be more careful with it. I’m sure it was just the excitement of being back in London with old friends. I wasn’t giving enough attention to the game.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane considered Robert’s request. Unlike the other night with all his family members asking for favors, this was something his cousin would have asked whether or not Zane was the earl. Money wasn’t something Zane had ever had to worry about. In addition to the allowance from the previous earl, Zane’s grandfather on his mother’s side had left him an inheritance that had served him well over the years, and he’d been careful with it and never abused it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“This is what I’m going to do. I’ll loan you the money. No more handouts. A man, no matter his station in life, needs to gamble with his own money and pay back his own debts. So, consider this another lesson in how the game is played. The money will have to be repaid, and there will be no more forthcoming. Do we understand each other on this?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, of course and I agree,” he nodded, rose, and looked as if he’d turn away without saying more but suddenly turned back. “It’s just that sometimes it’s difficult to leave the table. Especially when there is something on top of it that you want, and you think you can win it all with just one more shot. It’s hard to walk away.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane knew exactly what Robert was saying but wasn’t thinking about cards. His cousin’s words brought Brina to his mind. She was the treasure he was trying to win, and he had to be as clever with her as he was expecting Robert to be with cards.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The most important thing he had to remember was Brina expected him to fail.</p>
  </body>
</topic>