<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_4" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 2</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 2</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The road to perdition was easy compared to the road to redemption. Zane Howard Veldon Dormer Browning, eighth Earl of Blacknight, should know. He’d traveled on both in his near thirty years of life. His name alone had been enough to make him want to find his own way and not be subject to long-held traditions and stiff manners he cared naught about following. Why work so hard to become the standard bearer for gentlemen when just being a man came so naturally?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And was infinitely more enjoyable.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The first thing Zane had done when he arrived in London late yesterday was to pay his respects to the Dowager Countess and offer sympathies. Her sorrow and grief were still evident and enormous. Out of regard for her suffering, he hadn’t stayed long.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The second thing he’d done was find a distraction. That had come in the form of spending all night at 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">The Brass Bull Gaming House</i>
      . The sun had come up hours ago, yet he and three other men still assembled around a table in the private card room. Raucous laughter and lively scores played on the pianoforte from the night had settled down. He could now hear sounds of horses, carriage wheels, and occasional chatter from people passing by filtering in from the open windows below. The streets outside were busy with Londoners going about their usual daily lives—as was Zane.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But he couldn’t forget that things had changed for him now. For the better or worse was yet to be known.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Two months ago, one of Zane’s uncles, who was the Earl of Blacknight at the time, his only son and a cousin who had been in line for the title, were killed when the bridge over Blacknight Canyon gave way and their coach tumbled to the bottom of the dry ravine. In the blink of an eye, the succession of two heirs to the earldom were gone and Zane had become Earl of Blacknight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After the horrific news finally reached him in Vienna, he and his errant cousin, Robert, had left immediately for London. Their journey had been long, beset by an enormous amount of late winter snow and followed by torrential rains that flooded roads, streams, and villages.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Movement from one of the players brought his attention back to the cards in his hands. He blinked his dry eyes several times to clear his vision. It had been a while since he’d spent all night playing cards and enjoying a bottle of fine brandy and female companionship. For his overindulgence, he now had a pounding throb at his temples.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He’d already decided he was on his last shot of the morning when he sensed someone standing not too far behind him, watching his back. None of the players at the table had given whomever it was a bother of a glance, letting Zane know the person wasn’t a stranger to the small private club. He had a fairly good idea who it was—dear old Uncle Syl. Someone must have told the old bachelor Zane had made it to London.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester Browning, his father’s next to the youngest brother, had taken it upon himself to not only be Zane’s conscience but an unsolicited advisor after his mother passed. Uncle Syl had taken up Zane’s mother’s mantra and urged him to mend his roguish ways and settle down to the quiet, respectable life of a gentleman and start a family. As if there weren’t enough well-thought-of Brownings populating England already.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It wasn’t that Sylvester was an unlikable fellow. He wasn’t, and there had never been any harsh words between them. Zane got along reasonably well with him except when his uncle’s hovering was irritating—like a bee that wouldn’t be swished away. The two of them had often matched words but they were always civil. His straight-as-an-arrow uncle wouldn’t know any other way to be.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When the last card hit the table, Zane scooped up his considerable winnings from the night, pushed back his chair and rose while bidding his fellow gamesters a good day. He dropped the coins into his small leather pouch and cinched the opening tightly. Only then did he turn to confirm his suspicions. Not only did Sylvester wait there for him, his father’s youngest brother, Hector was there, too. Zane muttered a curse to himself. Both were staring stone-faced at him, their collars and neckcloths pulled tight as their expressions.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Uncle Hector was something of an oddity in his father’s family. Unlike the rest of the tall, powerfully fit-looking Browning men who sported thick black hair and clean-shaven faces, Hector was of average height, portly, with thinning gray hair and a bushy beard. He also used a cane to help him walk and to nervously tap the floor when he was flummoxed. Sylvester, on the other hand, had all the Brownings’ handsome physical traits but wore the same stern expression whether he was happy, ill-tempered, or hungry as a goat.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It had been a long time since more than one of Zane’s family had deemed it necessary to seek him out at the same time. He was fairly certain the last occasion was when he was set to duel a stranger who’d had the poor judgment to call him a card cheat. That early frosty morning Uncle Syl had tried desperately to intervene and convince the young blade of Zane’s expert aim and beg him to offer a public apology for the slander. There was no reasoning to be had between the two swill-headed rounders, but out of deference for his uncle’s well-intentioned pleas, Zane had only grazed the man’s shoulder with a clean shot.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Uncles,” Zane said with a nod, swallowing his dissatisfaction as he swung his coat off the back of the chair and dropped his coin purse into one of the side pockets.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They bowed and said, “My lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane gave a near silent chuckle of derision and shrugged uncomfortably into his coat. Being addressed as a title was going to take a bit of getting used to. Especially when it was coming from family.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Shaking off the drum of buzzing in his head, he cleared his thoughts and made eye contact with first Hector and then Sylvester. “I’ve already spoken to the dowager. My condolences to each of you and the entire family.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Enough time has passed now and most everyone is getting back to normal,” Uncle Syl remarked. “We’ve been worried about you and Robert.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was no wonder. Until Zane had an heir, Robert was next in line for the title.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We made the journey as fast as we could after hearing the news.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Robert told me when he made it home last night,” Hector added. “I appreciate that you returned with my son. Last I’d heard he’d joined you in Paris to enjoy the winter balls.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hector’s son was doing a bit more than that. Robert almost married a most unsuitable woman. If Zane hadn’t stopped him—with the aid of an intriguing young lady he hadn’t yet forgotten. And oddly, he hadn’t wanted to. It was pleasing to remember the warmth of her in his arms and taste of her on his lips. He hadn’t been able to forget the strength she’d showed in questioning and studying him before making up her mind to help him. She was sagacious and beautiful. Usually when she crossed his mind, he wondered if she were still in Paris or if she’d returned to England.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He’d never been to Vienna,” Zane answered, seeing no reason to elaborate on what had happened with the French woman. “That’s where your letters caught up with us. We left straightaway.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Now that you’re here, there’s no time to waste. We thought it best if we joined you for your first meeting with your solicitor as Earl Blacknight,” Uncle Sylvester informed him, and then quickly added, “that is, if you don’t mind?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane would have rather waited until later in the day or even perhaps a few days before settling into his new role, but the unsmiling expressions on his uncles’ faces kept him from saying that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not at all. I have much to get caught up on. I might as well get started.” He motioned for them to precede him out the door and down the stairs.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“After your meeting with him,” Uncle Syl said, and started down the steps first. “You’ll need to do something to calm the family.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Everyone has been in a state of shock,” Hector added before following his brother out the door, but at a much slower pace. Because of his hip injury years ago, Hector was always slow descending the stairs. “There’s been no small amount of hand wringing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That was understandable. Losing three family members was a terrible blow that Zane wasn’t even sure time could heal. But good lord, he had no idea what to say to them to ease their minds and he doubted they wanted to hear from the family rogue anyway.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Few, if any, in Zane’s family would be happy that he was now the earl. Since his mother passed a few years ago, he was more apt to have a long stay in Paris or Vienna than to gallivant around the English countryside in summer or attend the London Season. However, he always made it home for Christmastide.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Much to the chagrin of his family.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Now, for the first time in several years, he was in London during the full bloom of spring.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had no memory of his father, and his fondest remembrance of his mother was how much she revered Christmas day. She made sure everyone in her household shared her devotion as well. Church in the morning, family and neighbors around the table for a feast in the afternoon, and games of chess or cards by the fire in the evening. Some argued his paltry involvement once a year with their large and extended family should count for nothing, but Zane paid their grumblings no mind. Christmas Day with family was a code of gentlemanly honor and conduct he wouldn’t forego.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Besides, returning home for the holiday gave his well-married sister, numerous aunts, uncles and more cousins, from both sides of the family than the King had horses, a reason to whisper and roll their eyes when he came walking into the manor as if he’d only left the day before. It also gave members of the ton an opportunity to trot their eligible daughters out for him to make their acquaintance. Which he always did. No man should ever pass on a chance to meet a young lady. It mattered not to the elite of Society that he was the black sheep of the family. He was from the house and linage of Blacknight and all the privilege and prosperity that went with it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester stopped at the first landing and waited for his younger brother.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We’d like to suggest a dinner at your house tomorrow evening,” Uncle Syl called up to Zane. “We talked to your butler this morning and he assured us the staff is quite capable and there will be no problem getting everything prepared.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane grimaced. “I don’t have a butler.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course you do,” Hector said irritably. “You have a complete household staff waiting for you at your new home, the Earl of Blacknight’s house is now yours. You need to move in immediately. It’s the proper thing to do. The dowager is moving out today.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait a hellfire minute,” Zane said, his jaw hardening with conviction. He knew being the earl was going to involve situations he wasn’t prepared to deal with. “I don’t want her to move out of the house. Especially not at this time. She just lost her husband, son, and nephew. It’s too soon to disrupt her life.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nonsense. She knows propriety, expects this and understands,” Uncle Syl said calmly. “She’s been planning for it. It’s your house now. She’s ready to leave and has only been waiting for you to return. I’ve made arrangements to have your personal items moved from your town house today.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” Zane asked, biting back another oath as he started down the narrow stairs mumbling to himself, “I’m quite capable of handling my own belongings and all of my affairs.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Uncle Hector stopped and tapped his cane on the stair. “You’re an earl now. You don’t need to be distracted by insignificant tasks when you have more important things to do and there are plenty of people to handle such things for you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And it’s good you’ve made it here as the Season is beginning, as well,” Sylvester added, completely ignoring any reference to Zane’s comment. “You can use my tailor. He has excellent style and will have you fixed up with all you need for the parties and balls in no time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had no desire to trussed up like a preening dandy. “I’m quite set with all the clothing I need.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good. We’ve been thinking on all this while we waited for you to return. The best thing you can do to settle everyone’s frayed nerves is to show that you’re ready to settle down and take your new responsibilities seriously. We hope you will avail yourself to every moment of the Season and choose a bride. There are three young belles making their debut who should be of special interest to you. One of us will make sure you’re introduced to them at the first ball you attend.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane grunted. What did he need a bride for? He had no problems when it came to women willing to share his bed. For that reason, he stayed away from respectable young ladies of the ton. He learned early in adulthood that they were raised to assume a kiss meant a wedding would follow. It had always suited him to find his pleasure elsewhere. Doing that kept everyone safe.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He knew nothing about being a proper earl and even less about being a husband. It was best he deal with one before considering the other.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Scouring the parties in search of a bride is not on the list of things I need to attend,” he stated flatly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You’ll learn to manage both,” Uncle Syl said and trotted on down to the bottom of the stairs. “Men always do. Choose wisely and she will be a blessing not a curse.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That sounded odd coming from a man who’d never married.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s your duty now,” Uncle Hector explained. “It will prove to everyone you intend to not only be a responsible earl but a good caretaker of the family by producing a legitimate heir.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m quite sure I have no heirs of any kind.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All the better,” Hector agreed. “After the shock we’ve all had, you must protect and preserve the title. The best way to do that is to marry a proper young miss who can give you as many sons as your grandfather had.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The buzzing in Zane’s head and roar in his ears returned with a vengeance. He rubbed the bridge of his nose with his thumb and forefinger, determined not to let his well-meaning uncles frustrate him. He couldn’t comprehend the responsibility of one son much less five. What normal man could?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Blast it, Uncle, I think I should get used to the idea of being an earl before I take on such an ominous role of being a husband or a father of five.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“There is no time for you to dawdle about this,” Sylvester added in a decisive tone, obviously wanting to have his say in the matter as well. “The Season is upon us. Why not take advantage of it and go ahead and choose a bride?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I think my time will be best spent at Blacknight. I can skip the Season and go straight there and learn what I need to know about the earldom since I’m not familiar with it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hector stopped again. His eyes narrowed, his shoulders rolled forward a little and his chin bobbed before he started speaking. “You spent the first ten years of your life living at the estate. How can you say you aren’t familiar with it? Besides, you don’t have to be. That’s what you have solicitors, accountants, managers, and a host of other people for. You’re an earl now and you have more than yourself to think about. You’ll best serve the family being right here in London for the greater portion of the year. This is where most of the business is conducted that concerns the title and its holdings.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What Hector is also trying to tell you is that the Blacknight property and holdings are considerable. You now control the purse. The magnitude of the estate isn’t something you can learn overnight. Your cousins are afraid to spend a penny—we all are, not knowing when the next allowance will come or 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">if </i>
      it will. Your Aunt Beatrice is so distraught she’s having fainting spells. Your Aunt Lorraine has developed a rash of red whelps all over her face, and you didn’t even bother to let your sister know you arrived back in Town yesterday.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane grimaced. He wasn’t in the habit of letting family know his whereabouts. “How do you know that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I went to see her this morning looking for you. She was glad to hear you’d made it back safely, by the way, but Patricia now assumes you’re upset with her.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not upset with anyone.” It was always the same in his family. No peace, no privacy, and no quarter ever given to him no matter the situation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Everyone’s worried you’ll be making changes,” Sylvester said flatly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Changes?” Zane questioned, still trying to make sense of the fact he wasn’t going to his peaceful home for a few hours of much needed sleep.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You have all the family in a dither about what kind of earl you’ll be. How generous you will be to everyone. Naturally, the whole family—nieces, nephews, cousins—are anxiously waiting to see what you’re going to do about their allowances, their houses, carriages and what all. And there’s your mother’s family to consider as well. They’ll be wanting to hear from you as to what you plan for their futures. Our older brother was generous to your mother’s family, too.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Somewhere in his past Zane had heard this. And, the previous earl, his father’s oldest brother, had always been more than generous to him. Which was surprising since Zane had tarnished the family name on more than one occasion with his wild ways.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I see no reason to make changes to any of that,” he said, finally deciding to sail past Hector and join Sylvester at the bottom.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That should please everyone greatly for now, but it’s up to you to tell them. You can’t neglect your duty. But more importantly, you need to show them you’ve changed now that you have the title.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Damnation, Uncle Hector,” Zane said irritably, his head pounding as if a hammer was slamming against both sides of it. “You are acting as if I have to do everything in one day.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It would be a good start to the recovery of your reputation if you did. Spending the whole of your first night back in London at a gaming hell will not reassure the family you have their best interests at heart or the peerage you will work with them when you need to.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had little doubt about that, but still argued, “That’s what bachelors do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not for you. Not anymore. Hence the need for a wife to help rein in your raffish ways, settle you down, and facilitate you being respectable and reliable to all who now look to you for protection, sustenance, and guidance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t neglect the dowager. After seeing her, was I to pay a visit to everyone in the family?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That would have been a splendid thing for you to have done.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The corners of Uncle Syl’s mouth tightened, and Hector’s chin bobbed as he worked his mouth. Staring at his uncles’ current agitation, Zane could only imagine the shock swirling through his tight-as-a-bow-string family that he was now the earl and in charge of everyone’s allowance, their homes, and their way of life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The devil take it,” he whispered, his head continuing to throb. He hadn’t asked for this responsibility. “Make sure everyone knows I’ll be hosting dinner tomorrow evening and I’ll listen to everyone’s concerns.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course,” Uncle Syl said calmly, making it clear that was exactly what he wanted Zane to say. “I’ll take care of that for you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You’ll also need to start making amends for all the times you insulted half the members of parliament,” Hector added, tapping his cane once again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had to draw the line somewhere. “If I offended them it was because they deserved it and half of them weren’t members at the time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, but their fathers were, and you knew they would be one day. It’s never too late to start making friends instead of enemies. It will serve you well.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have friends.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And they are all rakehells like you.” Sylvester sniffed and pulled on the tail of his coat and lace at his cuffs. “The less you see of them the better. They have no reason to change. You do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Uncle Hector made it to the bottom and Zane grabbed his cloak off the peg near the front door. His uncles were reminding him why he spent so much time away from London. The more family you had the more worries you had. Without deliberation, he towered over Hector who held open the door for him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I will accept my duties as the earl, Uncle, but don’t expect me to fall in line about everything you suggest or to be as pompous as most earls are. I don’t have the stomach for it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course you do,” Hector said without so much as a blink of his eyes. “You just don’t know it yet.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Speaking of your stomach,” Sylvester added quickly, “White’s is on the way to your solicitor’s office. You could probably do with a generous plate of food and tankard of hot ale after being up all night.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m all right,” Zane muttered as he fastened his cloak at the neck and passed under the doorway.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The brisk morning air felt good hitting his face. He breathed it deeply into his lungs, hoping it would help further clear his head of the brandy and lack of sleep. The problem with what his uncles were saying was that Zane didn’t want his life to change. Being the black sheep was easy. It was what he was used to. He was good at it. Changing into the earl was going to be hard and the damned truth of it was he didn’t know if he could do it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Stopping to settle his hat on his head, he glanced across to the opposite side of the street and was caught off balance by the glimpse a tall slender young lady walking down the pavement. His gut tightened. He quickly blinked several times.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was her. The lady from the masked ball. He was certain of it. The tilt of her head, gracious lift of her chin, and sway of her shoulders as she walked were unmistakable even though she was now dressed in sensible clothing. He might have been ocean deep into his cups, bound, and with his mind only on stopping Robert’s foolish stunt, but he hadn’t failed to take detailed notice of the one who freed him that night in Paris.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And he hadn’t failed to remember her often.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s gaze followed the lady as she passed his line of vision, not paying him nor anyone else she swept by the slightest bit of attention. Her short cape was fashionable enough but a drab shade of mulled wine. A black bonnet covered most of her hair, but he saw the telltale sign of a silvery blonde chignon at her nape.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">At the ball, some of his rescuer’s face had been covered by her demi-mask, but there were things about her he’d never forget. The faint rustle of her soft skirts when she’d knelt beside him to untie the scarf. The sweet spring flower scent that wafted from her skin. Eyes so blue he could have looked into their depths for the rest of the evening. Everything about her was still vivid to him right down to her soft ivory complexion.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was a man after all, no matter his pressing situation that night. He was more likely to forget his name than her brief appearance in his life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Watching her now, he could feel the lingering pressure and taste of her soft lips beneath his. Had he imagined it or had she actually given into the kiss for a second or two?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Because of her, Zane had caught up with Robert and hightailed it to Vienna with the impulsive blade. Zane wouldn’t have minded staying in Paris and finding out who she was from the hostess, but he had to get Robert out of Paris for a while. He couldn’t trust the randy buck not to try again to marry the French woman.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you know who she is?” Zane nodded in the lady’s direction as his uncles flanked him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t go setting your top hat for her,” Uncle Syl immediately warned. “It will do you no good. She’s one lady you won’t be adding to your queue and no one would appreciate you trying.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Tension expanded in the back of Zane’s neck. “Who is she married to?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No one,” Hector answered. “She’s a widow. Mrs. Brina Feld. Her husband was killed when the 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Salty Dove</i>
      sank. A shame for someone to be widowed that young.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Bits of newsprint and gossip flashed through Zane’s mind. “I’ve never met her, but I remember the tragedy. Many drowned. It happened four or five years ago.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“At least.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Is she someone’s mistress?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Only her own as far as anyone knows,” Uncle Hector added. “See those girls walking behind her?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded but hadn’t noticed the dutiful children trailing behind her like sheep following their shepherd until Hector mentioned them. There were four of them. All were dressed alike and walking as purposefully as Mrs. Feld.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“She and two other ladies started a boarding school for those girls and others like them. It’s a charitable endeavor and only for the daughters and sisters of workers who had worked on the 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Salty Dove</i>
      .”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">So, she was available and obviously had a very charitable heart. Not only for men who found themselves in a literal bind and in need of help but children, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He remembered she’d been curious but cautious when she’d come upon him in the chateau. She’d been strong in holding him to account for his predicament before she fearlessly untied him. Once she’d settled in her mind that he was trustworthy and not a footpad wanting to make off with the family silver, she’d acted in good faith and released him. That act of courage and kindness wasn’t the sort of thing a man would forget.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m remembering some of that story,” Zane offered, as more memories of the catastrophe and the aftermath came rushing into his mind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The other two ladies have since married. But don’t let that give you any ideas about Mrs. Feld. She might be only twenty-four, but she’s worn her widow’s weeds every day since she heard the news about her husband. No one believes she’s going to shed them and marry.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Feld had been at that masked ball wearing a provocative pink gown. Not widows’ weeds. She wasn’t dressed as a widow at the masquerade. She’d worn a gown made from a tempting shade of bright pink satin. It shimmered and glistened in the firelight whenever she moved. The low neckline emphasized a fair amount of her small but delectable bosom. A large pink sapphire had rested seductively in the hollow of her throat. Smaller stones dangled from her earlobes. Her lips were full, beautifully shaped, and rosy as a late summer bloom. In her gloriously blonde hair, she’d worn a coronet of leaves alternately painted gold and pink.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Today, she looked every bit the widow his uncles described. Prim and proper as a lady could get. What was the personification of a perfect widow doing in Paris at a masquerade in the dead of winter dressed to catch the attention of every man who saw her?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane didn’t know. But he wanted to.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hector harrumphed and disturbed Zane’s musing as Mrs. Feld rounded a corner and walked out of sight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“She’s shown no interest in any man’s attentions. Probably because it’s hard for any man to compete with a hero.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Damned hard Zane thought, but it didn’t keep another surge of interest from slamming all the way through him. “Was it her husband who saved the lives that day?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Indeed,” Sylvester answered with conviction. “Not more than a handful of people survived the wreck of the 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Salty Dove,</i>
      but they all told of the bravery of Mr. Stewart Feld helping passengers find pieces of wreckage they could cling to while in the end he couldn’t save himself. Word is she’s never allowed a man past her front door since. It’s doubtful that will change considering the amount of time that’s passed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded slowly, as if in agreement, but thought if that claim were true, it sounded like a challenge to him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If one has made it,” Uncle Hector said, “he’s kept it a secret, and that’s not easy to do in this Town.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was true London Society laid claim to few confidences. “No doubt many have tried,” Zane offered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And failed,” Sylvester declared as if that should end any hope Zane might harbor of pursuing the widow Feld. “That’s why she’s garnered so much genuine affection in most circles. I suggest you set your sights a little lower if you want to be happy with the outcome of your search for a bride. Mrs. Feld is adored by many in all walks of life. Not only is she beautiful and prim to a fault, she’s the epitome of all a widowed lady should be. Devoted to the memory of her husband and kind to those in need whether they be Society or not. She’s not likely to look twice at a man who is more apt to have a card game end in a back-alley duel at sunup than to have a Sunday afternoon ride in Hyde Park with a lovely lady.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His uncle certainly wasn’t trying to spare his feelings. That was fine with Zane. Both were probably right about their assertion of him and Mrs. Feld, but he would just as soon find that out for himself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But what was the best way to go about that?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane looked down the street again and saw the roofline of White’s. He was a member of the famous gentleman’s club but seldom went there. The place was so deeply steeped in traditions Zane would rather avoid so he usually stayed away from the place. And there was the fact that he’d been thrown out more than a few times. They didn’t appreciate or tolerate raucous hellraising from young men out to have a good time with their drink, games, and general fooling around.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The prestigious club was known as much for its wager book as for the exclusivity and civility of its members. Men of otherwise good character would wager on the oddest of things. From whether a man’s wife would bear him a son or daughter, to what time of day a certain man would die. There was no bet too humorous or too grisly to lay down.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And that book is what gave Zane an extraordinary idea.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">At first thought, it seemed an impossible, outlandish, and mostly irresponsible idea.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But it immediately sparked his interest, and he couldn’t deny he wanted to accept the challenge of it. There was a thing or two he needed to consider. First and foremost is that he would be competing with the memory of Mrs. Feld’s husband. That alone gave him reason to have second thoughts. There were some things that should be too sacred to disturb.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">By all accounts, the man was a true hero.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The only thing Zane had ever done worthwhile was save the life of every man he’d ever dueled. He could have easily shot to kill, but he never had. He’d never actually challenged anyone to a duel. And there were those who thought even that wasn’t noteworthy and a fact that was often lost in the telling because Zane accepted every challenge thrown at him. And he couldn’t agree with them more. There was little heroism in duels, even if he did aim to miss.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He’d been uncommonly drawn to her when she’d swept into the room at the French chateau and looked at him the first time. He knew immediately she was an English beauty, elegant and refined and not one of the many ladies there looking for the unrestrained sexual behavior that usually went on at such a ball.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His uncles certainly thought highly of her, too. Who wouldn’t? A beautiful young lady who’d maintained unblemished widowhood for five years was deserving of respect and extremely enticing at the same time. He was up to a new challenge. What better way to get his uncles and neurotic family off his back than to solicit help from the one lady who had no plans to marry?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But, if he wanted to get past Mrs. Feld’s front door, he would first have to get her attention. He looked toward the roofline of White’s again and thought of that book.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane didn’t know anything about being a proper earl, and the hell of it was he really didn’t want to learn. But if there was one thing he knew, it was how to get a lady’s attention.</p>
  </body>
</topic>