<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_21" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 19</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 19</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane placed his cup back into the saucer and set his empty plate to the side of the breakfast table. If not for Brina’s unusual terms, he would still be in bed at this hour. Thanks to her, he’d already had a rousing early morning ride in the curricle, followed by over an hour of fencing at his club. Now, he’d just eaten scrambled eggs, toast, and a thick slice of ham as if he’d been famished.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Since he was no longer staying up all night playing cards and sipping on a brandy, he found his energy level during the day had exceedingly improved. It was amazing how much one could get done in a day—when he went to bed with the chickens—as he’d heard someone once say.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">However, all the good things that were improving his life couldn’t keep him from missing the stinging taste of a brandy, the satisfaction of winning a hand, or curb his desire to have Brina in his bed. His gaze strayed to the window overlooking the side garden. It didn’t seem to matter what he was thinking. He found a way to bring his thoughts back to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had never had to be proper about anything in order to win a wager. Skill had always accomplished it. He either won or lost on how tightly he stayed focused on the game before him and how well he read his opponent and the cards he’d laid down. It was difficult for most players not to show any emotion when they were in a well-matched game. Sometimes it was something as simple as squeezing the cards a little too tight with their fingers or breathing in a little too deep. The trick was to study enough men to know the small signs. Over the years, he had learned to discern when someone wasn’t playing fair, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And Brina Feld wasn’t playing fair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Whether or not she was doing so intentionally, he’d yet to completely settle in his mind. He didn’t think so, but there was a little qualm of doubt that surfaced from time to time. Especially when she was so pliant and eager for his every touch, willing for him to thoroughly satisfy them both. Was she just trying to get him to break his promise? She had only accepted kisses. He had no doubt her passion for him was real but he had no doubt her desire to win their wager was real, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">One thing he was sure of, he couldn’t get her off his mind. Most especially when he imagined her lying in his arms, coming to life beneath him. Those images wouldn’t leave him alone. Day or night. When he was with her, it was almost impossible to hold back his desire. When he held her, felt her shiver, and sensed the beat of her heart racing along in time with his, it thrilled him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He had no doubt he was the first to awaken the sensual desires left dormant since her husband’s death. That pleased him. Zane wanted her to experience every one of them to their fullest. He was sure she wanted that, too. As desperately as he did. And they would have, except for the minor consequence of their bargain. He was caught in an unfortunate cat-and-mouse game with her when what he wanted to do was strip off her clothing, lay her on the bed and kiss her softly curved body until he was rigid with pain. And then make love to her all night.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Grunting, he pushed away from the breakfast table and made himself more comfortable by placing the ankle of one leg on top of the knee of the other. Thinking about her so early in the day was not doing him any favors. Best he get her off his mind in a hurry. He picked up 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">The Times </i>
      and unfolded it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A quick glance at the headlines told him amazing things were happening all over the world. The East Indian Company was going to establish a settlement in Singapore. Zane remembered talking with Garrett Stockton about that possibility at a party the first night they met. The adventurer had been to Singapore and agreed that it was a long way from England. Zane wouldn’t mind going there some day. He enjoyed getting to know people whose cultures were different from his. But he would have to think on making the voyage. He wasn’t sure he’d enjoy so many long days at sea before reaching the land.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes scanned down the rest of the front page. America was still trying to purchase Florida from Spain, and a steamship named 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Savannah</i>
      had crossed the Atlantic in 26 days. The world was getting bigger and closer together every year. Reading those articles should keep his mind off Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For a few minutes.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shook out the newsprint and started on the article about the ship but had barely gotten two or three sentences into it when he sensed Fulton standing in the doorway.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Excuse me, my lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane lowered the paper and looked at the butler. “Yes?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Your uncles and sister have arrived and are wondering if they might join you here or in your drawing room.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Hells bells. </i>He hadn’t heard them at the door. They usually came in chattering so energetically they could be heard all over the house.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It seemed the earlier he rose in the mornings, the earlier his uncles arrived. And Patricia with them today, too. That didn’t bode well. She was usually reserved for only the most important issues. Obviously, something was going on in the family they assumed needed his attention.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He wasn’t looking forward to that happening. Again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Have them come in here, Fulton, and see if they’d like tea or something to eat.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, we don’t need anything, my lord,” Hector said, coming from behind Fulton.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He’d even missed the familiar tap of his uncle’s cane on the wooden floor. Zane must have been really deep in thought about Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester and Patricia followed Hector into the breakfast room. They all stopped at the head of the table, greeted him properly and then proceeded to stare down at him with disapproving expressions.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He refolded the paper, laid it aside, and rose. “Please, sit down and join me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester remained staunch with his shoulders and back straight as a board, not moving a muscle. Patricia continued to stare at him but stiffly folded her arms on her chest and drummed the fingers of both hands on her forearms. Uncle Hector cleared his throat and bobbed his chin as he stared at Zane with great condemnation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For a moment or two he had no idea what he might have done to warrant the rebuking stares, but then, by chance he noticed the sleeves of his shirt. Times like these were what reminded him of how much he disliked family gatherings.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Zane said with a little more force than he intended. “I can bloody well sit alone at my own breakfast table, in my own house without wearing my coat.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, of course you 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">can </i>
      do it, my lord,” Patricia said dryly, her tone almost as stiff as her frame. “The point is that you 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">shouldn’t</i>
      .”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And why would you want to?” Sylvester asked, obviously feeling the need to straighten his own perfectly tailored suit. “It’s most undignified to present yourself that way.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You need to remain respectfully clothed at all times for the benefit of your staff if not for yourself,” Hector added to make sure he wasn’t left out of the condemnation for what they considered such careless behavior for the mere satisfaction of being comfortable. “Besides, you are no longer alone. You have three guests.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” Zane argued defiantly. “This is ridiculous. You aren’t guests. You’re family. And I doubt any of your or my staff would faint or go running to the gossipmongers if they saw me without my coat.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why take the chance?” Uncle Syl asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane fumed and continued with his steely expression. He hadn’t asked to be the earl but now that he was should be able to set his own standards in his own home. That should be the one place he could relax and be himself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yet, all three remained unyielding in their posture along with Hector agitatedly tapping his cane. Frustrating as it was, Zane only had two viable options. He could extend and hold out and ignore their bluster about 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">his</i>
      rights in 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">his</i>
      house, or give into their demands, find out what they wanted, grant it to pacify them, and send them on their unhappy way as quickly as possible.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was Sunday for heaven’s sake. Each one of them should have been in church, not pestering him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right,” he declared in a nonconciliatory tone, swinging his coat from the back of his chair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">This was why he didn’t know if he had the fortitude to be a good earl. This was why his uncle, his uncle’s son, and Zane’s cousin should have never been riding in that carriage together, should have never died and left the unimaginable task of dealing with this family to him. He simply wasn’t good at it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He would never be patient enough. He had been quite happy with his life as it had been before the title fell to him. Damnation, he wished it hadn’t.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It wasn’t in his nature to want to please people. He wanted to enjoy 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">his </i>
      life 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">his</i>
      way and allow others to do as they wished. No doubt the previous earl and the previous two heirs would have loved sitting at the breakfast table buttoned up to the neck, wearing a coat that fit like a glove, but was a hell-of-a-lot less comfortable.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After shoving his arms through the sleeves and settling it properly over his shoulders, he walked over and held out a chair for Patricia. She smiled graciously, seeming perfectly happy now that he had donned his coat, and seated herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane and his uncles then joined her around the table.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We wouldn’t usually bother you on the Lord’s day, but your Aunt Beatrice is in a dither. Her daughter, Thelma wants to marry Mr. Aldrich Clark,” Uncle Syl said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That didn’t seem like earth shattering news to Zane. “Patricia told me she unfortunately didn’t make a match last year so I would think that’s good to hear she found someone to her liking,” he answered, thinking this was easy enough to handle. “I give my permission.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Patricia’s gasp, Hector’s grunt, and Sylvester’s harrumph left Zane no doubt it wasn’t the answer they wanted.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you know who he is?” Patricia asked in what could only be considered a scathing tone because he’d said something so incomprehensible.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane sluffed it off as he always had. If he got upset every time he displeased his sister or his uncles he’d be in a perpetual state of agitation. “I don’t personally know him, but if she wants to marry him why should I have any objections?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“His sister ran away from home over a year ago to become an actress,” Uncle Syl replied, as if that was the most horrible thing to have happened in London in years. “And we have it on good authority she was actually seen on stage at one of the theatres.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Patricia sighed heavily. “It was devastating to all the Clarks. Not just his family, as you can imagine. You must go to Thelma and explain why he’s not a suitable match and insist she needs to choose a different man to marry.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">No. He wouldn’t do that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane looked at the three stern faces staring at him, remaining silent as he pondered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He could easily tell them how unreasonable they were sounding but he had set a precedent with Robert—though his sister and uncles didn’t know about it. Was it unfair to allow Thelma to marry when he had prevented Robert from doing so?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But there was a difference. Robert was planning an elopement to a woman almost twice his age, and without an ounce of social standing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Thelma’s case was different. Even so, he knew he had to handle this delicately.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We are all in agreement that Clark is a well-respected name in the ton, are we not?” Zane asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, yes,” Patricia answered as if she adored every one of them—except Aldrich, of course. “Quite so.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Then what Mr. Clark’s sister has or hasn’t done is no reflection on what he might or might not do. Thelma shouldn’t be punished for what someone else has done. Tell Aunt Beatrice that as long as he has adequate allowance to take care of her daughter in a style that’s fitting, I see no reason to interfere.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But what about the children?” Uncle Syl asked, looking at Zane as if he’d lost his mind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane returned the expression. “What children?” Zane asked. “Does Mr. Clark have children by a previous marriage?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Uncle Hector said, jumping into the conversation with a strong tap of his cane to the floor.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester raised his hand to assuage and settle his brother’s irritation. “The ones Thelma will have if she marries Mr. Clark. His daughters might have the same predisposition as his sister and think it’s fine to defy one’s family to run off and be an actress.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What do you know about children?” Zane asked. “You’ve never had any. You don’t know how they might behave.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s not to say I don’t know about such things as bad blood in headstrong children, my lord. And how it can be passed down from family to family much like freckles.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Freckles?</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What the hell was he talking about? Zane snorted. “I know nothing of the kind. And furthermore neither do you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well I do,” Patricia injected herself into the conversation. “I have children. And you know I take your side whenever possible, my lord. I always have, but there is such a thing as bad blood.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His sister had never taken his side in anything.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A long string of silent curses entered Zane’s mind as Fulton quietly walked into the dining room and placed a small silver tray in front of him. A note. Probably an invitation to another party. He started to wave the butler away but on second thought realized it didn’t matter what the correspondence was. It gave him a much-needed reason to be diverted from his family.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Excuse me,” he said, rising from his chair. “This might be important.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He walked over to the window, broke the wax seal and opened the note. Glancing down at the signature, he felt a jump in his heartrate and smiled. It 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">was</i>
      important.</p>
    <bodydiv base="LETTER-A" class="- topic/bodydiv " outputclass="LETTER-ALTR-A">
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="SalutationSal">Dear Lord Blacknight,</p>
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">If you are not otherwise engaged this afternoon, I might be available at half past three for a ride in a carriage.</p>
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="ClosingClos">With regards,</p>
      <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="SignatureSig">Mrs. Feld</p>
    </bodydiv>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She was asking him to take her for a ride. A lady asking a gentleman? Surely that couldn’t be proper, but blast it, if he didn’t love it when she wasn’t proper. Zane looked over at his uncles and sister. They continued to be in deep conversation over poor Thelma’s love life and children she’s yet to have.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">At least there would be a bright spot at the end of the day for him and he’d do his best to see that Aunt Beatrice’s daughter had a bright end to her afternoon as well. It they wanted him to be the head of the family, damnation, he would.</p>
  </body>
</topic>