<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_23" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 21</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 21</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The gown was gorgeous.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stopped to stare at it. The round neckline was low but wouldn’t be considered shockingly racy. The high waist and short capped sleeves were banded with beaded velvet ribbon of the same bright shade. The skirt flowed in wispy waves of short curled flounces trimmed with the same exquisite ribbon. The late afternoon sun was at the right angle to shine on the beading. It sparkled, twinkled and called to her hidden desire to permanently shed her widows’ weeds and wear something soft and beautifully feminine again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And then, of all things, she imagined herself dressed in it, walking into a a glittering ballroom in London, the skirt swishing from side to side and around her legs with every step.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Toward Zane.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">An intense swelling of something she didn’t quite understand filled her chest. Right then, all she wanted him to do was sweep her up into his arms and never let her go.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He smiled reflectively. “That looks like—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, I know,” she interrupted him and answered simply. Beautiful as it was, the gown wasn’t something a widow should wear. And it didn’t matter how many fantasies she had about Zane and love and all the rest of it. She would remain a widow.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina turned and started walking again. Faster this time, feeling as if she needed to get away from that gown, that color, and Zane. He was making her want things she shouldn’t want; feel things she shouldn’t feel. The all too sudden and real fear was that she had already lost her heart to him and it hit her with such force she was finding it difficult to manage.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was nothing she could do. She couldn’t marry again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane easily kept up with her hurried stride. They walked in silence for a few moments before he asked, “Why don’t you want to look at the gown?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s not for me,” she answered in a clipped tone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why? You looked glorious when you rushed into the room wearing that color in Paris. I remember thinking that fate had an evil sense of humor. Sending in the most beautiful lady I had ever seen, and I am bound to a chair.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His words took the edge off her tense feelings and her footsteps slowed. She laughed softly. It was wonderful the way he could change her outlook with just a few words. “You were so angry that night I’m surprised you remember what I was wearing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I told you. I can’t forget one thing about you. That night will be with me always.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Me, too,” she said, returning to her more somber state. “I’ll never forget the shock of hearing you say, ‘come untie me’.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The hint of chuckle in his chest was soothing to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was desperate,” he admitted without reservation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So was I?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You never told me why you were at the ball,” he said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We decided the reason for the mask was so people didn’t have to talk about what happened or why they were there.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But you know the reason for my presence. I want to know everything about you. Being there, dressed as you were and now knowing who you are puzzles me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her steps slowed and she stared at the backs of the three men walking in front of them. She supposed there was no harm in telling him since he already knew about her connection to the abbey. “I foolishly thought that since I had looked into a life of celibacy and servitude that I should look into a life of entertainment and debauchery.” She continued to amble along the street without looking at him. “Does that surprise you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. It sounds like a very human reaction.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The minute my aunt left me on my own I knew I wasn’t made for that kind of life any more than I would take to life at the abbey. When I entered the room you were in that night I only wanted a safe place to hide until it was time to meet my aunt and leave.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did something happen after I left you in the room?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, I locked myself inside and thought about you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That caused him to glance at her. “Me? Why?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was wondering if you were kissing her? The woman who tied you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina,” he said her name on a husky breath as he looked deeply into her eyes and shook his head. “Don’t ask about my past.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why can’t I be as curious as you? It’s not like I don’t know you’ve been with countless women. You are known as a scoundrel and rake as well as a gambler.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Who has mended his ways,” Zane emphasized. He stopped and so did she. His eyes stayed steady on hers. “For you. I’ve not thought about kissing anyone but you since I saw you walking down the street the day after I arrived in London.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked into his eyes and felt a horrible, overwhelming sense of loss because she knew she couldn’t have him. “I’m not available. I’ve tried to tell you that I am committed to being—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he said earnestly. “I don’t want you to be a widow, Brina. I don’t want you to be Mrs. Feld. I want you to be my wife, my countess, Lady Blacknight. I am committed to keeping my word and you must be—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The sudden squeal of youthful laughter startled Brina and Zane. They looked down the street. Not far from them, a boy the age of nine or ten and thin as a sapling was jumping up and down in a jubilant way and in a singsong voice saying, ‘I won again. I won again.’ His friend, younger by more than a couple of years with full cheeks and a chunky build stayed huddled against the side of a building holding cards in his hands.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Thankful for the children’s interruption, Brina said, “It looks as if they are having a good time with their game. I like to see children who are happy and playing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not sure what’s happening,” Zane said, seeming to study the boys intently.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What do you mean?” she asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Only one of them appears to be happy. Wait here.” He started walking directly toward the boys.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina wasn’t about to wait. She was as inquisitive as he was. Catching up to him, she asked, “What are you going to do?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m going to talk to them.” He looked over at her and smiled. “Don’t worry, I’m not going to join their game.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She returned his smile with a rueful chuckle. “I think you should.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The two boys weren’t wearing the best of clothing, but it didn’t appear they were street urchins who’d been left to their own care by unfortunate circumstances. They were clean and too well-fed not to have family. Brina scanned the area but didn’t see anyone else who was paying attention to the boys.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As she and Zane neared the pair, Brina drew closer to Zane. He immediately knelt down to be on the smallest boy’s level. Startled, the youngster shrank away from him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t be frightened,” he said in a calm voice and tone. “I only came over to talk to you because I heard you playing. Who’s winning?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am,” the tallest boy spoke, looking at Zane. “He’s not a very good player.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane eyed the cards the younger child held and then picked up some of the ones that lay on the pavement and looked at them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What do you think you’re doing, Mister?” the oldest boy asked, staring at Zane with a menacing expression. “We aren’t causing anyone any trouble. Those are my cards you have in your hands and I’ll thank you not to take them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane shrugged. “I’m not going to take them from you. I’m going to give your friend a lesson in card playing.” He looked up at Brina and repeated, “A lesson. So his next game will be a fair one. Don’t you agree every game should be fair?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The youth rolled his small brown eyes from side to side and wiped his forearm under his nose before declaring, “Of course I do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded and gave his attention back to the youngest boy. “What’s your name?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“William,” he answered shyly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What’s his name?” Zane asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Claude.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We don’t need you in our game,” Claude pipped up in a high-pitched tone. “We aren’t doing anything wrong. You have no cause to bother us.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane ignored him and kept his attention on William. Big green eyes stared back at him. “Do you mind if I see your cards?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s all right,” Brina said, stepping closer to William. “You can trust him. He doesn’t want to keep them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Timidly, the little one handed the cards to Zane. “Do you see this smudge on the card right here?” He pointed to the top left corner.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">William nodded.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s the ten of hearts. So, if you saw this card in his hands,” he motioned with his head to the taller kid. “What would you think?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He’s holding the ten of hearts.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s right,” Zane said with a nod. “It would be a big help to you winning if you knew what cards he was holding, right?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t know that smudge was on the card,” Claude defended. “I swear I didn’t.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane continued to ignore him. “This card has a little dot of red right there,” he pointed, and this one has the edge frayed. “See them?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The youngster nodded again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The next time someone asks you to play a game, check all the cards over carefully for markings and if there are any, don’t play. Do you understand?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I had no idea the cards had markings,” Claude injected dramatically. “Found them in the rubbish. Thanks for letting me know, Mister. That was right kind of you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">William scrambled to his feet, one chubby hand made a fist and the other he held out, palm up as he glared at his friend. “You cheated. Give me back my money.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I did not,” Claude declared.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina was about to speak up when Zane said, “Give him back the money you won off him.” Zane rose to tower over the older boy. “Go on, do it? All of it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shook his shoulders a time or two, shoved his hand into his pocket, produced two pence and returned it. William’s round cheeks filled out more with his wide smile before he turned and ran away.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane gave the cards back to the older kid. “Take your marked cards and peddle them on boys your own age.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Claude slipped the cards into his pocket and said, “Hey, Mister, do you and the lady want to see some kittens? I’ll show you where they are for three pence.” He held out his hand.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stepped closer to him. “A kitten?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Two of them.” He held up two fingers. “Soft as the hair on a baby’s face my mum always says. And the momma cat is friendly.” He continued to hold out his hand.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane looked over at her. “You want to see them?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She felt a leap of delight. “I’d love to if you think it will be all right. I haven’t seen a kitten in—well a very long time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How do I know you won’t take my coins and run?” Zane asked the lad.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I give ye my word,” Claude said, lifting his chin proudly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane reached into his pocket and pulled out a small coin. “I’m going to give you one. “If you really have a kitten you can show the lady, I’ll give you the rest.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina slipped her hand around Zane’s arm and smiled. It felt good to touch him. He laid his hand over hers and gently squeezed. They followed Claude a short distance down a side street before entering an alleyway. At the end of it was a small, run-down shed. The door was missing, and the roof had caved in. Claude scrambled underneath the two steps and out of sight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">All was quiet for a few moments and then she heard several soft meows and then his hand shot out from under the step holding a small gray kitten with the biggest, most beautiful gray eyes Brina had ever seen. It’s belly, neck and paws were white as snow.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane reached down and plucked the kitten from the boy’s hand and gave it to Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She took the squirming ball of fur and immediately put it up to her neck so she could feel its softness and warmth. The kitty pawed at her chin and wiggled. Its meow was so faint she almost hadn’t heard it. She felt such joy just holding the thin, soft as a tuff of cotton body close to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you want me to bring the other one out,” Claude called from underneath the dilapidated porch.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, of course,” she answered the lad.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane looked at her and for a moment she could have sworn he saw the love she was feeling for him shining in her eyes.</p>
  </body>
</topic>