<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_17" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 15</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 15</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He could have killed you!” were the first words out of Harper’s mouth when Brina walked into the drawing room.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">How did he find out and then get to her house so quickly? Brina had hardly been home half an hour. In fact, she was quite sure the blush from all Zane’s kisses and caresses in the carriage hadn’t yet left her cheeks.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Remaining calm, she said, “If you are talking about the carriage ride, I suppose you’ve never driven a curricle fast through Town.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course I have,” he insisted tightly. “But never when a lady was with me. From what I’m hearing, the earl was exceedingly reckless and showed no regard for you or your safety.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her cousin’s statement was pointed and damning. It wasn’t easy to rile Harper. His nature was happy and easy going. What happened had obviously perturbed him greatly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, heavens, Harper,” she said dismissively. “You are making way too much of this. The earl is six or seven years older than you and has had more practice. Who knows? By the time you are his age perhaps you will have been reckless with a young lady as well.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he answered firmly. “There are some things a gentleman doesn’t do. But, lest I forget, the earl is no gentleman.” He walked closer to her, his face contorted in anger. “I want you to stay away from him. In fact, I think I should pay a call to him and insist upon it. Your father would do it if he was here. I intend to do it for him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt her hackles rise. “Now, wait a minute, Harper. I don’t need you speaking for me to Blacknight or anyone else. And, not that it’s any of your business, but I will tell you, I am the one who encouraged the earl to go fast. He was quite reluctant to do so.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You want to make excuses for him because you don’t want me to do my family duty and protect you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I make excuses for no one, including you,” she said, lifting onto her toes so she could look him eye-to-eye.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I let it slide when he made the wager about marrying you. Men have a right to place their bets and wagers as they see fit and what he did at White’s will cause you no real harm. This was different.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked aghast at him. “Really?” How could he say that? Unless Zane started drinking, gambling or carousing, she could very well end up married to him. And for the first time, she realized that idea thrilled her as well as terrified her. If her cousin really wanted to help her he could encourage the earl to gamble.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper’s eyes narrowed to serious looking slits. “I don’t think you are comprehending that he could have crashed the carriage and harmed or killed you. What I should do is call him out as a matter of honor.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Stop talking such madness,” Brina insisted hotly and turned away from him before sharply turning back to face him again. “I won’t hear such foolishness. What is wrong with you? Who is putting such nonsense in your head?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He eyed her curiously. “No one. Why would you suggest that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Because it’s so unlike you to be this upset over anything. Besides, I am perfectly capable of taking care of myself.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not with him, you aren’t. Robert was with him in Paris and Vienna. I’ve heard stories about him. About the two of them that I’m not at liberty to talk about.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt a shiver shake her. She had experienced one of the earl’s and Robert’s stories. And it was just as exciting as the ride they’d had today. She didn’t need Harper to tell her anything about Zane. She knew first hand exactly who he was.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He is a bachelor,” she said, knowing she was defending him and realized she wanted to. “What he has or hasn’t done is of no concern of mine. Or yours, for that matter.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I want him to leave you alone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">No.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For better or worse, she was bound to Zane right now. She didn’t want to give up the thrill of being with him. She couldn’t tell Harper that but he wasn’t in a mood to listen. And it was so unlike him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But she had to take control of this conversation and settle Harper down. “Then let me be blunt and tell you the truth,” Brina said, somehow remaining calm. “Someone was following us and spying upon us. I didn’t appreciate it. I asked Blacknight to lose the carriage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper’s lids hooded his eyes and lifted his chin. “What do you mean?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Exactly what I’m saying. The earl is being following—we assume that someone who has a large amount of money placed on one of the wager’s at White’s or one of the other clubs is following him in hopes of seeing him take a drink, play cards, or—whatever. I felt violated by such an act as having my privacy invaded.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was really anger she’d felt but wanted to use the stronger word of violation in hopes of quieting Harper even more. And his expression quickly changed to one of concern.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You’re serious?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. He was driving a poorly maintained cabriolet. Speeding up and slowing down when we did, and taking every turn we took until I insisted we must lose him. Blacknight finally acquiesced to my wishes. So if you are going to be mad with anyone. Be that way with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Lawton quietly walked into the room and put a tea tray on the small table between the two settees.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Look,” Brina said. “Mrs. Lawton brought the tea. And she has tarts.” She turned to the housekeeper. “Apricot or figs?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Figs, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good. Thank you.” Brina looked at her cousin again. “Sit down, Harper and I’ll answer all your questions.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Two cups of tea and half a dozen tarts later, Harper was calm and back to his usual cheerful self. She had no idea why, but she kept thinking that something else must have wound him tight and that what happened with the earl had set him off.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After telling him as much as she could about the afternoon with Blacknight, she’d changed the subject to one she knew he would like—cards. He was eager to talk about a new club he and Zane’s cousin Robert were thinking about joining. Thankfully, that had him parting on good terms but she’d been unsettled about how his life seemed to be revolving around card games and clubs and the parties of the Season all but forgotten. There should be more of a balance between the two.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Long after he left, she couldn’t shake the feeling that something wasn’t right. But what?</p>
  </body>
</topic>