<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_28" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 26</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 26</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane stood near the entryway and watched for Brina. Everyone else in the ballroom watched him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He’d purposefully arrived late. Very late. Midnight wasn’t far away. He’d scanned the crowd twice. Brina wasn’t in the room. He wondered if she just hadn’t arrived or if she were waiting out of sight in one of the alcoves. If she had arrived with her friends, Lady Lyonwood and Mrs. Garrett were no longer with her. He spotted them across the room with their husbands. They, like several others, were trying their best not to stare at him. Perhaps Brina was feeling the same way he was. That tonight wasn’t something she wanted to be a part of.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He could understand that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yet, he was the one who started this with his wager, she expanded it, and he would finish it this evening.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As promised.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The hell of it was that he was a different person now. Because of Brina he no longer saw the mischievous humor of trying to get a lady’s attention by making a wager. Brina had helped him see a lot of things differently. And he liked to think he had helped her see some things differently, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not that it mattered to her now.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Usually, the last ball of the Season wasn’t well attended. For various reasons. By the time it rolled around all but an ardent few in the ton were tired of the endless parties. The young ladies and gentlemen who had already made a match were more interested in making plans for their own wedding parties. The last ball also signaled Parliament had ended its session. Once the House of Lords and House of Commons finished with their business, they were eager to forgo the last party and travel to their summer estates to escape the approaching heat in London and begin their summer house parties.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But this year’s was different.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was a crush.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The orchestra played, but few danced. Most stood in little groups chatting with whomever happened to be by their side. Zane had no doubt that everyone far and wide knew he had gambled last night and tonight at midnight he had to give an apology to Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And he would.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Whether or not she attended to receive it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He huffed out a rueful chuckle when he saw his uncles and sister had spotted him and were heading his way. The day before he thought he’d settled into his new role in life. Earl, provider and protector of his family. Lover, and soon to be husband of Brina. But somehow, one good deed changed all that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He couldn’t argue with Brina that he’d had a choice whether or not to hurt her where Stewart had not. Damn, but that pierced his heart as surely as the blade of a rapier. When she’d told Zane he had hurt her more than her husband it had torn his heart to shreds. He knew how deeply she felt emotions. He knew he couldn’t, 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">wouldn’t</i>
      hurt her anymore. That was why he had waited at her house on and off throughout the day. He had wanted to demand she see him, force her to listen and make her understand he’d done the right thing. Not for her, but for Robert and Harper. But in the end, he didn’t want to cause her more pain.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He’d give the apology. It’s all she wanted from him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sins of his gambling past had finally caught up with him. He now realized what a mistake it had been to try to teach Robert to be a well-seasoned gamester when they were in Vienna. Few people ever became really good at it, but Robert was a Browning so there was a chance. At the time, Zane needed something to take Robert’s mind off the French woman. And it had, but gave him a far bigger problem.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The American crimp who’d held Robert and Harper in his makeshift prison had been one good card player. For a time, it looked as if Zane wasn’t going to win enough money to pay their debts before his time was up. He simply wasn’t winning enough games. Brina and the dinner party kept coming to his mind, causing him to lose focus in the beginning. He was doing all the things he knew not to do. Sweat, hold the cards tight, blink too rapidly, and so many little telling hints of what he held in his hand.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But those same thoughts of Brina and getting back to her eventually calmed him. His skill and intuitive nature took over and just before the hour Remick had given him, Zane had won more than enough to pay Robert and Harper’s freedom.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Remick reluctantly conceded and assured Zane the young men would be released. Zane wasn’t about to let the crimp out of his sight until he had the young men in his hands and they were safe from being thrown onto a ship bound for the Orient. That’s when Zane pulled the knife Harry had slipped into his pocket and forced Remick to take him to Robert and Harper.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Only after he had the young fools with him and seen they were not too badly hurt did he let Remick go; with the warning he not ever peddle his skills or his crimping in London again. He had been certain word that he’d been seen gambling at The Brass Bull had made it to his house.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">News like that travelled fast.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He had been equally confident everyone would be gone by the time he made it back home. However, Brina was still there.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For one very good reason. To let him know she had won.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s about time you got here,” Uncle Hector said. “Not that it’s pertinent to this evening but I had a note from Robert this morning saying he was going to visit one of his Aunt Lorraine’s son’s in Dorset. I thought it was sudden. Did you know about that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not any particulars,” Zane said. “I’m sure he’ll write once he gets there. Young men like to travel.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Now that we have that out of the way,” Uncle Syl said. “What happened to you last night?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We know what happened, Uncle,” Patricia informed him dryly and rolled her eyes toward Zane to ask her own question. “What I want to know, dear brother, is if you have spoken to Mrs. Feld today?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No?” Hector said, stomping his cane. “Why not? You have some explaining to do and today was the time to do it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not to mention an apology,” Patricia added.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, you can’t do it now,” Sylvester said calmly. “She’s not here. Who can blame her? She probably wouldn’t listen anyway. You didn’t make it to her dinner last night. She obviously isn’t going to make it to your apology.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, she should,” Uncle Hector insisted. “They were almost engaged. There’s still hope this can be settled for a good outcome. She was doing such a fine job helping you be more of a gentleman. Until you strayed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What I want to know is what happens between Zane and the widow,” Patricia said, keeping her eyes on his face.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">widow</i>
      . Zane grimaced and gave a silent growl. How he’d come to detest that description of her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Maybe all is not lost,” Uncle Syl said in a placating tone. “Perhaps if you tried writing her a poem? Ladies love poetry. You know, something about flowers, moonglow, and how beautiful she is might go a long way to soothing her and help her overlook your lesser points.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A poem?” Patricia asked in an unbelievably indignant voice. “At this point, a poem is not going to win her hand.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If romantic words won’t ease her disposition,” Syl countered, “tell her in no uncertain terms that she will sit down and listen to you because you are an earl. Though we don’t know what they were, I’m sure you had good reasons for your behavior last night, and she needs to accept them without further ado.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And thinking like that,” Patricia remarked sharply, “is why you never married.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hector stomped his cane again. “Everyone is growing restless. It’s time for you to speak. While you are apologizing, you might as well extend your regrets to your peers as well for missing your own dinner party. Most of them are here.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">When hell freezes over, Zane thought.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I think it best he never mention it again but go forward from here,” Patricia said, offering her bit of advice. “No matter how you decide to handle what you are about to say, we will stand with you.” She gave him a sincere smile. We are family.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane gave his sister a nod of appreciation. “My actions are my responsibility.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was no clock to chime the midnight hour, but Zane agreed with Hector. Every gentleman in the room was ready to go to White’s and other places they may have placed a bet to either collect their winnings or pay their debts.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was time to end this even though Brina wasn’t present.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He started walking toward the center of the room. The place quietened. Everyone stepped aside, giving him plenty of space and once he stopped, they formed a wide circle around him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had recollection of telling Brina he’d give a grand speech, but he wouldn’t. It would be two short words. He started to speak but saw her rush into the entryway. It felt as if his heart stopped beating for a few seconds and then suddenly thundered like the sound of a hundred galloping horses in his chest. She was wearing the bright pink gown they’d seen in the shop near the abbey. Just as he’d known that afternoon, she looked glorious dressed in it. It shimmered with every step she took and so did she.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Watching her made losing her all the harder.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Some in the ballroom must have noticed her, too. The quietness just moments before turned to murmurings. The whispers got louder. Her chin was demurely high, her shoulders softly confident. She was breathtaking as she walked down the three steps into the room and started toward him. His admiration for her grew. She wasn’t ducking out. She wasn’t going to stand on the other side of the room from him or cower near the door. No, damnation. Not her. She was going to come right up to him and make him look her in the eyes when he apologized.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Good.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was glad she decided to make him pay for hurting her. The crowd parted for her as they had for him, and she stopped in front of him. All he could think for a moment was that she was the most beautiful person in the world, and he loved her with all his heart. If there was anything he could say or do to win back her love he would do it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With the same poise she always had, she curtsied before looking at him with serenity settled in her lovely features. “Permit me to go first, my lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He bowed. “A gentleman always let’s a lady go first.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">How was he going to live without her?</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you,” she answered softly. She turned away from him and addressed the room. “I know that all of you gentlemen here tonight are far too proper and kind to wager on anything concerning a lady. Especially something as delicate as a lady—a 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">widow’s </i>
      hand in marriage. I appreciate your restraint in that matter and your resolve not to resort to gossip about it either. You have set the standard for all gentlemen.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane kept his eyes riveted on Brina. That was odd. What was she doing? She knew almost every man in the place had wagered on his proposal to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There were more than a few clearings of throats, and men looking down at their toes in hopes of hiding their guilt.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But,” she continued. “If you have friends or acquaintances who wagered that I would reject Lord Blacknight’s offer of marriage tonight, please tell them they lost.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane felt a jolt of hope. Had she said what he thought she had? He took a small step toward her as a roar of cheers mingled with some jeers sounded around the crowd.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“However, however,” she hastened to quiet the crowd with a loud voice and movement of her hands. “If you happen to have friends or acquaintances who wagered that I would accept Lord Blacknight’s proposal, you can tell them they also lost.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s heartbeat suddenly thundered in his chest again. The cheers and jeers turned to rumblings of discontent and confusion. Zane had no idea what she was talking about and judging from the mutterings neither did anyone else.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“How can she accept proposal if she rejects it?” someone asked.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“What does she mean?” asked another.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“What about his apology?” another commented.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina seemed to hear the last question, as she glanced in the direction from which it came before saying, “You see,” she continued, still addressing the crowd. “I do not wish to hear an apology tonight from Lord Blacknight, but I would like to ask him to answer one question.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The room fell silent as she turned to him. She looked up at him with her big bright eyes and held out her hand to him, and said, “Lord Blacknight, will you marry me and be my husband?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane felt as if his heart would beat out of his chest as his fingers closed his fingers around her hand. He took it to his lips, and kissed it. He smiled, and said, “I accept with pleasure.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He then did a very ungentlemanly thing and swooped her up into his arms and kissed quickly but soundly in front of everyone before setting her back onto her feet.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina looked up at him and smiled as gasps and sounds of horror echoed, mumblings and rumbles of confusion continued to circulate around the room. Her eyes squinted a little in mock concern. “Must you always do the wrong thing, my lord?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His gaze swept down her face as his hands tightened on her back. “I do believe I still need training from you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s chest swelled with love. “Gladly.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You are amazing, Brina Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Love for him shone in his eyes and she laughed softly. “Thank you. So are you, Lord Blacknight.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded. “You realize you just conquered every man in this room and cancelled all their bets by asking me to marry you, don’t you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The gathering scattered and gave them the floor. The orchestra started playing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The gathering scattered and the orchestra started playing. She looked around the room and smiled triumphantly at the grumbling crowd before settling her attention back on him again. “Of course, I do. It’s what they deserved, but I only wanted to conquer you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina knew how to go straight for his heart. He nodded. “I surrender to you,” he whispered softly before asking in a teasing tone, “You also realize that I won. I got you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, you did. I think I like it when you win. Dance with me, Lord Blacknight. We just got engaged.”</p>
  </body>
</topic>