<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_10" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 8</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 8</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As soon as Brina had awakened and remembered the earl was taking her for a ride, she felt a humming of excitement deep in her chest. At the time, she’d immediately put the sensation down to the chill in her room. Later she told herself it was common nerves. When it continued, she assumed it was because she was annoyed with herself for becoming overwrought at the ball and had started making all those demands on him and that she would marry him if he complied.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She didn’t know what emotion had taken hold and caused her to literally put herself at risk. That was certainly reason enough to give her a case of the jitters, but she shouldn’t still be experiencing the troubling stirs. By the time summer arrived, she’d be twenty-five. Plenty old enough not to allow a rake like Blacknight make her feel as if she were a young belle getting her first ride in a landau with a handsome man.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It wasn’t the best day for a ride in St. James Park but Brina would manage. Skies were gray and the air was cold. A gusty strong wind had whistled around the corner of the house all morning. Just two days ago she’d heard birds chirping and the sun blazed hot on her cheeks when she was in the garden. Spring had seemed to disappear overnight and left a winter’s day in its place.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina prepared for her outing with the earl by donning a thick-fabric chemise, a heavy forest green carriage dress with matching velvet pelisse, and fine woolen stockings. At the last moment, she changed from a low-heeled pump to her most comfortable pair of walking boots in case they decided to stop the carriage and take a stroll.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Should I go up to your room and fetch your black cape, Mrs. Feld?” the housekeeper asked, handing her the wide-brimmed bonnet banded with satin ribbon.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, I should be fine. I don’t expect to be out of the house long this afternoon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina knew if she were too cold, it would be a good reason to cut short her excursion with Blacknight. She wouldn’t admit to actually planning it, but a shiver or two from her should make him recognize her discomfort and suggest the need to return home.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After tying a bow under her chin, she started pulling on her gloves, wanting to be ready when the earl arrived. There was no reason to prolong the afternoon by inviting him inside and offering tea. It would have been a proper thing to do, and necessary if she’d still been living at her parents’ house. They would have insisted on saying hello to the new earl. Though Brina was quite sure they wouldn’t be pleased Lord Blacknight had placed a wager at White’s stating she would accept his proposal by the end of the Season. Hopefully they wouldn’t know until it was all over. By now, her parents should be safely ensconced at her aunt’s estate in Northcumberland and far away from all the gossip.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina adored her mother and father. They had always been good to her, but she was glad she no longer had to depend on their unwavering support. After Stewart’s death she needed them close.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And not without good reason. The shock of losing her husband and the denial that persisted far too long had provoked unhealthy emotions she was still trying to recover from.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A stirring from the past teased Brina’s mind as she tightened the gloves around her fingers. She tried to brush the unwanted memories away, but they lingered like cold morning fog on a gray day.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For a time, Brina thought she might be going insane. Perhaps she even had a little. For a time.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She’d loved her husband and considered it an act of faithfulness and honor to refuse to believe he was dead. Afterall, they’d only been married three months when she was told the sea had taken him. There were reports he’d saved the lives of several people by helping them grab onto pieces of wreckage. He was young, strong. Surely, he’d saved himself, too. He had to be somewhere. Injured perhaps and just hadn’t been found. Days turned into weeks. Months passed. He didn’t return.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina finally had to accept he wasn’t coming back.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was dead, and she had stopped living. She couldn’t cope with the deep, pulsing sadness of losing him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But then, when she felt she couldn’t bear the pain and anger of loss any longer, she met Julia and Adeline that sad day at a square near the docks at London’s Harbor. It wasn’t a place widows of Society should ever find themselves, nevertheless it was where the few personal belongings that had been recovered from the sinking of the 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Salty Dove</i>
      had been displayed. The items were lined up in rows, available for family members who wanted to look through and retrieve loved ones’ final possessions.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Seagulls had squawked all afternoon. The smell of putrid water hung in the air. Lonesome, distant sounds of riggings clanking against wooden masts would never fully leave her mind. Nor would the suffering families of the stewards, attendants and other workers on the ship. They had gathered and huddled there, too that day. Mostly women and children poorly dressed. They hugged, talked softly, and comforted each other.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That was the day Adeline had the idea of starting a school for the unfortunate children who were left fatherless by the downed ship. Polite Society would take care of their own but who would take care of the workers’ offspring? The three Society widows decided they would, and the inception of The Seafarer’s School for Girls had been born.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And it had saved Brina’s life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Would you like for me to ask your maid to bring you a different pair of gloves?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” Brina blinked back the past and looked down at her hands. She had put on the gloves and now taken them off. Shaking her head, she smiled at Mrs. Lawton, happy to have a reason to put the unwanted memories to bed once again. “No, no. They fit fine. I was simply distracted for a few moments.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A tap sounded on the doorknocker. Brina’s stomach tightened. She started pulling on her gloves again. “At last, he’s here. There’s nothing like getting something started so you can look forward to the finish.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Lawton headed for the door. Brina slipped the ribbons of her reticule over her wrist and settled them at the top of her gloves. She then scooted from behind her housekeeper, intent on rushing outside but the sight of the earl looking so splendid and dashing in his dark-blue coat, fawn-colored trousers, and quilted beige waistcoat, she had to stop and drink in the sight of him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Reality came swift. It hadn’t been nerves or annoyance she’d felt all morning. It was guilty excitement at the thought of seeing and spending time with him. His towering height and perfect physique sent a thrill of desire flashing through her, and she simply wanted to enjoy it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">From the moment she’d first seen him she’d been attracted and despite her valiant efforts, that hadn’t changed. But right now, she had to reign in those feminine emotions and stay calm.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My lord,” she greeted him, and curtsied.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He took off his hat and nodded. “Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She stepped outside. “You’re right on time and I’m ready.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes narrowed and he hesitated. “You might need a cape. It’s windy today.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I should be warm enough.” She smiled to herself and started down the stone steps toward the street. The closer she got to the pavement the slower she walked. No carriage was parked in front of the house. There were three horses and a groom standing in front of one of them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A feeling of suspicion rose from within her. She stopped and turned to stare at the earl while her brain tried to focus on the situation she saw unfolding before her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“These are horses,” she said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He regarded her closely as he came up beside her. “Well-schooled mares. I picked a gentle one for you. You do ride, don’t you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina was so astounded she wasn’t sure she could speak at first. Her breath seemed to clog at the base of her throat. “Yes, I do,” she managed to say. Not well, but she could manage a horse. Somewhat. “Why did you bring horses?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You look concerned,” he said, though his tone was light, making it clear he was anything but concerned that she could not handle the task he’d brought to her. He casually folded his arms across his chest. “I said we’d go for a ride in the park.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The Earl of Blacknight had to be the most unbelievable man in all of London. And England. The whole world. And he was standing in front of her. Pursuing her. Tempting her with intriguing charm.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“This is not what it means when you ask a lady to go for a ride.” Brina sucked in a deep, soundless breath of exasperation. “It means you will bring a curricle to her door, or perhaps a shiny landau with the top down. You don’t bring horses. How could doing something like this have even entered your mind?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He remained at ease and offered her only a trace of a smile. A smile that teased and irritated her at the same time. And that she was more than a little perturbed didn’t seem to bother him at all.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s not a problem,” he said so smoothly his words washed over her as if they were a goose feather trickling against her skin. “I’ll return to the stable and get a proper carriage for you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, no.” Brina shook her head, walked over to the smaller horse and rubbed down her long brown nose. “I don’t want you to do that. I haven’t ridden in a long time. I’ll manage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The mare nudged her hand gingerly so Brina patted her firm neck. The animal nudged her again. She was friendly and Brina warmed to that immediately. Blacknight had made a wise choice.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Only if you’re sure,” he said with conviction.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked over at him and twitched a smile. How could she stay upset with a man who brought her a horse to ride. A man who continually surprised her? It was frustrating that he was so stimulating. She had a feeling he wasn’t nearly as oblivious to the rules of gentlemanly behavior as he claimed and others liked to think.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The groom placed the two-step stool down by her, and the earl reached for her hand. His grip was firm and reassuring. Within the bounds of propriety, he’d helped her position herself perfectly in the side saddle with her booted feet properly settled in the stirrups.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He held onto the leather ribbons as he gazed into her eyes and said, “You look very capable sitting up there, but would you like for me to lead your horse?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She tried to feel annoyed at him, but there was just no way she could. She was delighted to be in the saddle again. Riding was an enjoyable pastime and the thought of doing it again made her feel good and excited to get started. “No, I’ll be fine,” she answered, feeling comfortable and holding out her palm. “It may have been a few years since I’ve ridden, but I don’t’ think I’ve forgotten how to guide a horse.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He placed the ribbons in her hands. “And you’re right. You don’t need a cape. I brought a blanket for us to sit on and enjoy refreshments when we get to the park.” He walked over to the groom’s horse and pulled a gray wool blanket from behind a basket. He laid it over her lap and said, “Hold on to this end to keep it from falling off.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you,” she said, tucking the heavy fabric around her waist and under her hip. Giving her the blanket was not only mannerly of him but thoughtful of her comfort as well.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If at any time you feel you can’t control the horse let me know.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina could tell he was playfully teasing her as the mare hadn’t so much as snorted since Brina approached. She gave the earl just enough of a smile to let him know she understood exactly what he was doing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I fear the only thing I can’t control is you.” Or the way she felt when he was near.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He chuckled and climbed atop his horse with the ease of a man who was well-seasoned to a saddle and knew how to handle the animal beneath him. Brina gave a gentle kick to the horse’s flank with her heel and they started down the quiet street.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After passing only a few houses she felt exhilarated. She was enjoying the ride immensely and wondering why she hadn’t done it for so long. The mare had a smooth gait and ambled along at the right pace, giving her time to get used to being in the saddle after a long absence. From atop the horse she could see more of her surroundings. Her perspective of the houses and trees was different than when sitting inside a carriage or taking a stroll.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When more than a few moments of silence had passed, she offered, “You do know that even if we were going to ride horses, we should have arrived at the park in a carriage and had the groom waiting there for us?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If I’d done that you would have missed some of the enjoyment of the afternoon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She scoffed with confidence. “You can’t fool me. What you mean is that you would have missed the amusement of seeing how startled I was at what you had done.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That, too,” he admitted without qualms.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Even with the dreary cold day, he still had a twinkle in his eyes. How could she ignore that? When he wasn’t being a rake he was so charming. And that was what she had to be careful of.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How are you doing?” he asked. “Warm enough?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She was actually doing wonderful as she was sure he expected. A cape would have kept the chill of the wind from blowing down her neck, but she was fine with the heat of the horse beneath her legs and warmth of the blanket he’d politely placed on her lap.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You brought the horses on purpose, didn’t you?” she asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shrugged. “I thought you might be getting a little tired of doing the same thing each day and ready for something different.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A prickle of something she couldn’t describe skittered over her. It was alarming how well he seemed to know her. She’d wondered how he’d known she wanted to flee down the stone corridors and tunnel beneath the Paris chateau with him. Now how had he known she needed to do something she hadn’t done in years but use to enjoy? Something as simple, peaceful, and enjoyable as riding a horse.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina had shied away from any closeness to men for years. Now, this one, with his bold wager and her demands he had found a way to insert himself into her very private life. For now, there was nothing to do about it but cope.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Their pact was sealed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You must have known I could ride or you wouldn’t have chanced bringing the horses.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wouldn’t I?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Well, perhaps he would.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If you didn’t know for sure, it was very brazen of you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He remained silent so she asked, “How did you find out?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Must you know all my secrets, Mrs. Feld?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His voice was calm, and as easy as their ride. She had to be careful with him. There were so many things about him that tugged at her senses and brought them life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m curious,” she conceded and added a mischievous smile when he turned his head and looked at her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I asked your cousin, Harper, when I saw him. He was with my cousin, Robert last night.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Really? I didn’t see Harper at the ball. He must have arrived after I left. But it was already late by then. Did he look all right to you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. Why do you ask?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My father asked that I stay in touch with him, invite him over while he and my mother are away visiting his parents in Northcumberland. I’m afraid I haven’t done that,” she paused long enough to reprimand herself once again for not having yet done so. “I’ve had other things to attend to, and it’s only been a little over a week since they left. It was just odd my father asked me specifically to stay in touch with him. Almost as if he was concerned about him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Does he have reason to be?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, I’m sure not. Not having a son, Papa has always been attentive to Harper. I’m just feeling quite guilty I haven’t reached out to him yet. I’ll do that tomorrow for sure.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He looked as if he were doing quite well last night. I left the ball shortly after you. I saw him and Robert at a club and they were making a good showing at the tables.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A carriage came up behind them suddenly and quickly whipped around, passing them at a fast clip. The driver, a young buck, was obviously desperate to get somewhere. Though Brina was annoyed by the man’s lack of common courtesy, neither Blacknight nor the horses they were riding gave the incident notice.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So, you went to a club after the ball,” she stated in a more pleased manner than she intended. But really, she was. How could a gambler stay away from the games? This is what she had expected him to do.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s my usual habit.” He looked over at her and flashed a bit of a grin.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. I know but it is good news to hear you are at your clubs where there is much gaming, drinking spirits, and other pursuits.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A soft chuckle rumbled from his chest. “Don’t get your hopes up, Mrs. Feld. You’ll not hear anyone say I had a drink or played a game. I merely walked around and talked with those who were partaking in both and enjoying themselves.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She gave him a confident lift of her chin. “I’m not worried, my lord. If not last night, nor tonight, or even tomorrow. Some night. Soon. It will only be a matter of time until you give in to your nature and old habits and have a howling good time at the tables with a glass of the finest brandy.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Perhaps you are the one who should be careful, Mrs. Feld.” He gave another short laugh. “When you say things like that it only makes me want to prove you wrong all the more.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She turned her head away from him as if to be dismissive of his warning but, of course, she couldn’t stay silent after his comment. “I know how men like their vices. Tell me, did you have a headache this morning?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. From not drinking.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She suppressed a grin because she knew he was looking at her. “And how did you sleep?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well—once I managed to stop the shakes.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A genuine, playful laugh fell from her lips and she faced him again. “You are teasing me,” she chided lightly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“As you are me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It felt good to enjoy his humor. She could tell by the way he looked at her he knew how much she was enjoying herself. The awareness that always seemed to be between them heated her cold cheeks and caused a ripple of what she could only describe as desire to curl and wind its way slowly through her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So, what did you do at the club if you weren’t having a brandy and a game?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He looked away from her. “I watched a couple of old masters play billiards and some of the younger ones roll dice and play cards. I don’t always have to participate to enjoy whatever game is being played. One way to get better at anything is to watch how others do it well. It helps to discover their weaknesses and strengths and then apply them to your own game.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. I can see where that would be beneficial.” And she needed to study him. At times like this, when she was enjoying him, she had to remind herself they were in a fight. And she had to win.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They rode in silence for a few moments before her more solemn-self returned, and she turned to him and offered, “Obviously, I’m a little more troubled about our hastily-made arrangement than you are. You can take it lightly.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He arched his eyebrows and quickly said, “I take nothing lightly, Mrs. Feld. Least of all you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her shoulders lifted and her chin tilted up as she looked at him with a questioning glance. “That is a matter of opinion. It’s true I have more to lose than you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That is also a matter of opinion,” he answered calmly as his horse snickered and pulled against the bridle. “There wasn’t a man in London who woke this morning without knowing what I agreed to last night. Your demands are rigid.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina gave him a satisfied smile. “As I intended.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She believed it was only a matter of time before the seemingly strong-willed earl tired of his new life and gave up the fight in favor of his nature.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They came upon the one busy street to cross before entering St. James Park. Instead of stopping the horses and waiting for traffic to clear, as she expected him to do, Blacknight motioned for her to follow him. He inched his horse into the lane of traffic and said, “Tighten your reins and keep the mare directly behind mine. She’ll stay calm as long as you do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t worry about me, my lord. I’m doing quite well, and can handle her. You take care of yourself and your horse.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He threw her an admirable grin before giving his attention back to the matter at hand.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The carriages, wagons, and other horses stopped as he commanded by lifting his arm and maneuvered them across the street, safely onto the other side where they entered the park. Only a few people were milling about. It was no wonder with the day so blustery. Some were walking and others rode in open carriages. A handful of people were seated on blankets. Small sections of St. James were thick with small trees and undergrowth. Some of the terrain appeared wild and woodsy while other areas resembled open grasslands where trees where spaced far apart.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Lord Blacknight led them to a flat area near the beginning of a heavy growth of bushes sprouting their spring leaves. He stopped beside a large tree where they would be blocked from the worst of the wind by the wide sturdy trunk.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina kicked out of the stirrups while he dismounted. After throwing the blanket to the groom, he reached up for her. She expected him to take her hand and gently help her down. Instead, he clasped his strong hands firmly around her waist and in one quick puff of breath and fluid motion, he lifted her out of the saddle and down onto the ground. His grip was firm, capable but yet somehow seemed to be caressing. A thrill of warmth shuddered through her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His hands lingered only a couple of seconds before he released her and offered reasoning. “It’s so much easier that way.” A quick glance from one side of the park to the other. “And, it doesn’t appear as if anyone close by took notice. Your reputation should be intact.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Trying to forget about the heat of his touch and nearness, she gave him a perturbed glance and looked around the park for observers, too. It appeared he was right and no one was paying them any attention.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s not my reputation so much as it’s 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">not</i>
      something you should do—putting your hands around a lady’s waist is highly improper. Since it’s already done, I don’t know what I can do about it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His brows rose and he gave her a curiously genuine smile before saying, “I was enjoying our conversation so much I had forgotten that part of our bargain is for you to help me know what I should and shouldn’t do. I like the way I do it better.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. I believe that. And that is what I’m relying on. Yet, in fairness to our wager and my pledge, I must let you know when you’re being improper.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He leaned in close to her. The corner of his mouth twitched engagingly. “I haven’t been improper yet, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His words were low, husky and revealing. She suddenly felt breathless with anticipation. Yet, she stood there. Quiet. Hardly breathing, wanting to ask him to show her what he considered improper. For a dizzying moment she wanted to tempt him to go further with his statement and show her what he meant.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Instead, her good sense returned with a gasp of indignation and she asked, “How can you say that? You kissed me in Paris. You involved me in a shameful wager which prompted me to act accordingly with one.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As if to calm her, he gave her an irresistible smile and in the same low voice answered, “I would do it all again for the chance to be with you. I regret nothing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His honesty flushed her cold cheeks and caused ripples of desire to shoot through her. A hint of enchanting devilment sparked in his eyes and much to her obvious distress she enjoyed it. It appeared they were both enjoying this afternoon tete-a-tete.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And that could only mean trouble for her and she hoped he took a drink soon.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The horse nudged Brina’s back, breaking her concentration. She stepped away from the earl. Being around him wasn’t going to be easy. He made her smile, laugh, and feel things she thought she’d never experience again. It was going to be difficult to deny herself such tempting emotions.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They walked over to where the groom had spread the blanket and placed the basket. Brina settled herself on one side and the earl on the other. The gray clouds were beginning to scatter but the wind was still brisk as a winter day. It rustled the budding leaves on the trees and whipped at her bonnet. In the distance, she heard carriage wheels rumbling and shouts from children playing. Yet, even with the sounds there was always something peaceful about being in the park.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After taking off his hat and gloves, Lord Blacknight unbuttoned his overcoat and pulled the dark beige scarf from his neck. He extended it toward her. “I think it’s large enough you can use as a shawl. It will keep you warmer now that you don’t have the blanket for cover.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you,” she whispered and took it from his hands. There was a softness in his voice she couldn’t refuse. His gentleness and thoughtfulness were astounding at times.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wrapped the wool high around her nape, spread its width over her back and shoulders, tying the ends across her breasts. The fine wool fabric held the fresh scent of his shaving soap. It was heavenly. She breathed the scent in deeply. Heat from his body clung to it and soothed her chill instantly, making her want to sink and cuddle into it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Let’s see what my cook prepared for us.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He moved the basket closer and opened it. A large napkin was the first thing he took out and lay in front of her. Next came two teacups and saucers. After taking the stopper out of a pewter bottle, he put it to his nose and smelled.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good. It’s chocolate. I was afraid it might be tea.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Afraid? That’s an unusual comment coming from you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A poor choice of words to be sure.” He carefully poured some of it into a cup.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you not have an appreciation for tea?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was only thinking of you. My cook serves tea warm but chocolate she makes piping hot. So, it should still be warm for you on this chilly afternoon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His consideration warmed her as much as his scarf. She supposed there were times she judged him too harshly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He handed her the cup and she sipped. “It is. I thought you were going to tell me she usually adds a splash or two of brandy to your chocolate but not your tea.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl looked at her over his cup, his expression gentle but probing. She quirked her head as if to question him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Is that the way your husband liked it?” he asked.</p>
  </body>
</topic>