<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_7" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 5</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 5</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane walked through the wide double doors and into the spacious entryway of the Grand Hall where the premier parties and dances of the Season were always held. Its marbled floors led to the famous ballroom as well as secret little alcoves and candlelit corridors that were perfect for romantic rendezvous between young ladies and courtly beaus or star-crossed lovers.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After shedding his black velvet evening cloak, he came face-to-face with his older sister, Patricia. She’d undoubtedly been waiting for him to arrive.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Smiling in her usual impatient way, she curtsied and said, “My lord, I’m glad to see you actually came tonight. I wondered if you would.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good evening, Pat. You’re looking lovely this evening in your sky-blue gown.” And she was. She was eight years older than Zane but not one year of it showed in her face or appearance. Patricia had inherited the regal good looks of most the Browning family. Tall, slender, and with hair and eyes dark enough to give a mysterious appeal but light enough to remain approachable. “I told everyone at the dinner last night I’d be here.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She reached up to accept the kiss he gave to her cheek. “Yes, I know, but wasn’t sure I could believe you. No one else was either. Must I count the times the family expected you to join us for an event and you never arrived?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Probably not,” he answered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s downright unchivalrous of you to actually attend and prove us all wrong for the first time in years.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But this time necessary, I think you’ll agree.” He handed his cloak and hat off to the attendant, but unfortunately not his gloves. For such a formal evening as this, they must be worn. Otherwise he might accidently touch a young lady’s bare arm. Zane considered it more useless Society rules.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“After what you did to the gracious Mrs. Feld this week, I certainly do. The wager you placed was shocking to everyone in the ton. If you thought it would make anyone think you had settled down and were ready to take on your responsibilities, you are mistaken.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You can’t say I didn’t try,” Zane offered with a wry smile.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Patricia smiled, too. “It was quite clever of you. Of course, it didn’t fool any of us for a moment. We know you have a better chance of winning a foot race with a horse than taking Mrs. Feld’s hand to the altar in marriage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane chuckled as music and chatter from the large ballroom drifted toward him when they started walking.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m flattered by the abundance of confidence you have in me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m only being realistic,” Patricia offered without conceit, reaching up to push a pearl-tipped comb farther into her dark tresses. “You should be, too. Men have been trying to put a dent in Mrs. Feld’s armor for years now. You’re not likely to be the first even with your generous good looks, title, and ingenious exploit to gain her attention.” She gave him an appreciative smile. “I’m not surprised you have the courage to try. You always have been a devil when it comes to behaving badly.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You know I can’t resist a challenge,” he said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nor a wager it seems. No reason you should, but climbing a steep hill is a challenge. What you are trying to accomplish is folly.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Folly can be quite enjoyable,” he reminded her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“For a time, anyway.” Patricia answered in a somber tone and nodded to a couple who walked past them before giving her attention back to Zane. “If only Cranston were up to a little folly I should welcome it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You mentioned last night he was ill. How is he today?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Miserable. The cough lingers and he’s a dear about it. Kind enough not to want it to bother anyone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ll drop by and say hello to him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That should cheer him up. He’s rather pleased I’m now the sister of an earl.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane smiled indulgently.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know if you’ve heard, but some of the matrons in Society are upset with you for placing the wager, though none of them would dare say a word to you about it. Now that you’re an earl. They’ll all want to remain in good standing with you no matter what they say behind your back.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ll consider that useful information I don’t need,” he answered dryly. He hadn’t expected anyone to approve of what he’d done. And he wasn’t sorry for it. He had no doubt Mrs. Feld would make it a lively chase.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Patricia smiled. “I don’t know Mrs. Feld well enough to say, but apparently there are those who do consider her saintly because of the work she does for The Sisters of Pilwillow Crossings.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The abbey?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. Not many have the courage to go and offer assistance for the charitable work they do. Including me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">An unusual twinge of guilt tightened his chest. “Does she support it as she does the girl’s school?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“One would assume. Quite frankly, not many really want to know. They’d rather pretend she doesn’t go there at all. As I said, I don’t know her well, but I’m never above prying if—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Zane cut in and said firmly. He would find out anything he wanted to know about Mrs. Feld without his sister’s help.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Patricia smiled knowingly. “As you wish, my lord. I had some flowers delivered to her by the way. I thought I should do something nice to let her know not everyone in the family has your propensities to be uncivil.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you.” What else could he say? It hadn’t crossed his mind to give Mrs. Feld flowers. He was glad Patricia had.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane wasn’t surprised the older ladies of the ton found his wager abominable. Men on the other hand were entirely different creatures. They might say he’d done an abhorrent thing but most, if not all, the members of White’s he’d talked to had already put down their money. The great majority collected was against him winning her hand. That was a little unexpected. But, he hadn’t heard of anyone, including his uncles thinking it beyond the pale to have put up the bet, except of course, Mrs. Feld.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Remembrance of her teased his senses and aroused an eagerness to see her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I meant no harm of any kind to Mrs. Feld,” Zane offered. “Unusual wagers at White’s is commonplace. I hope no one is thinking she was a willing participant in the wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Gracious no.” Patricia gave a polite nod of greeting to someone behind Zane. “The ladies are all jealous as thieving mice because you didn’t go after them or one of their daughters. Who can blame them? At least with one of them, you would have had a chance to win their hand. I’m sure some of them will try to lure you in anyway. Now tell me, have you given any thought to the request I made of you Tuesday evening?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">So, they were finally getting around to the reason she was waiting in the atrium for him to arrive. He thought back to the family dinner his uncles had arranged. What was it his sister had wanted?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If you’ll remember,” he said, stalling for enough time to recall her particular wish. “There were two dozen family members there and many appeals were made to me by everyone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, but I’m your sister. Surely that gives me some measure of special consideration in the long list of favors you were asked to grant.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t mind financing your travel, Pat,” he offered as her request finally popped into mind. “Go, if you want, but why the devil do you want to go to the Americas?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The experience, of course. Besides, a visit there is all the rage right now. I don’t want to be the last person in the ton to see what it’s like. I’ve heard summers in Boston are quite nice and some have even bought homes—the Chesters, the Graves and the Mickletons. I’d like to assess the place for myself. So, thank you. But, of course, once I see their fashions I might need to have some dresses and gowns made. You understand, don’t you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She was thinking about clothing, of which she had plenty, while he was still trying to go through the immense number of account books concerning the holdings for the entailed property in order to understand exactly what he was supposed to be in control of. Zane was finding out quickly that he was used to a much more leisurely day than that of an earl with many properties and businesses. His uncles arrived early and stayed late. The solicitor and two accountants spent most of the day with him as well.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And that was only the half of it. In addition to his families’ requests, he’d been bombarded with various gentlemen who wanted to know where he stood on the politics of London, England and the rest of the world including America. He’d never had a reason to take sides in parliament. Apparently, that would now be required of him, but not immediately. He assured them he was a fair man and would treat everyone fairly and with respect no matter if he was a farmer, silversmith, blacksmith, or earl.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane lost count of the men who wanted him to consider their daughters, dowries, and wedding offers that would profit him much more than the gentle Mrs. Feld’s properties.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He wasn’t interested in any of them. He’d much rather be left alone to pursue Mrs. Feld at a leisurely pace and as he so desired. His uncles would have none of that. They would have rather he married her yesterday.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“As promised, Pat, I will look into everyone’s allowance and see what I can do to increase them all, but right now, there are other more important matters concerning the estates I must take care of.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I understand.” She held up a hand. “A consideration is all I ask,” she answered, seeming content that she’d received from him most of what she wanted.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They stopped in front of the two sets of double doors that had been swung wide to allow entrance into the ballroom. It had been a couple of years, or maybe more since Zane had attended such a grand affair of the Season given by the elite members of the ton. Young ladies who had come of age in the past year were officially available for all eligible men to consider for marriage. And, it was the beginning of the husband hunt for the young ladies as well. For Society, the entire Season was more about that intricate dance of manners and settlements than the thrill of romance.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had forgotten just how lavish the parties were. The Grand Hall was teeming with ladies dressed in colorful silk gowns, beautifully adorned with beads, bows, and lace. Their elaborate headpieces rivaled the latest fashions in Paris. Gentlemen wore their usual starched white shirts, neckcloths, waistcoats, and black evening coats with long tails.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The ballroom wasn’t without its share of glamor either. It was decorated to the hilt with vases and urns overflowing with colorful flowers. Lengths of shimmering silk streamed from the towering ceilings and cascading ribbons of satin fluttered around the fluted columns, chandeliers, and every gleaming sconce on the walls. Zane had never seen so many brightly burning candles. Servants roamed about holding trays filled with glasses of champagne for everyone to enjoy. On the far end of the ballroom, a well-tuned orchestra played one melodious score after another and would continue into the wee hours of the morning.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And the hell of it was that his family thought 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">he</i>
      lived a self-indulgent life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane quickly scanned the ballroom for Mrs. Feld but he didn’t see her among the gathering. His stomach tightened at the thought she might not be in attendance. The gossip about his wager was all over Town. Maybe she wasn’t as strong as he’d thought. He scanned the room again with more care the second time. A leap in his breath caught solid in his chest. His pulse ticked up at the sight of her silvery-blonde hair. Stifling feelings of wanting to rush over to her, he relaxed and he smiled. He didn’t know how badly he’d wanted to see her until he was afraid he wouldn’t. She was standing with another lady next to a line of chairs that had been set up along the side wall near the dance floor for the widows, wallflowers, and spinsters.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Time for the evening to begin.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Turning back to Patricia, he said, “I just heard the call for dancers to line up.” Taking hold of his sister’s hand, he placed it in the crook of his arm. “Do you think Cranston will mind if I have my first dance of the evening with you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not at all,” she said sweetly, seemingly surprised and delighted that he’d asked her. “He would love it and so would I. And don’t forget your cousin, Thelma is here tonight. Be sure to ask her for a dance, too. She came out last year but didn’t make a match, the poor dear. Perhaps you can help her find a suitable husband.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He cleared his throat. “I’ll be happy to dance with her, but I’ll leave the matchmaking to other members of the family.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nonsense. It’s your place to do it now. The family expects it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane grimaced. The list of all the family required of him grew longer each day.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">More than an hour later, Zane moved away from the crowd and leaned a shoulder against one of the columns in the ballroom. The only thing on his mind was having a dance with Mrs. Feld. As London’s newest peer, he hadn’t been idle since entering the ballroom. He’d indulged his Uncles Syl and Hector by dancing with two of the young ladies making their debuts and had conversations with half a dozen others. They were all beautiful, intelligent, and inviting in different ways, but none of them controlled his interest in the way he desired a chat and dance with Mrs. Feld. It was impossible to consider anyone but her. She was the one he’d been waiting for. Seemingly patient, but not really. He felt twisted in a knot that only she could untie. And he was ready for that release. He wanted to know if she’d found it in her heart to forgive him, if only a little, for placing the wager.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He might have been busy with others in the room as the evening progressed, but so was she. He hadn’t failed to notice where she was at all times. And who she was with. She’d glanced his way a few times, too. When two people were interested in each other there was no easy way to hide it. Though she continued to try.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her attire was modest compared to most of the ladies, but her elegance was unsurpassed. Her gown was such a deep shade of blue he’d first thought she wore black. When he detected the variance, he realized the subdued color enhanced the beauty of her hair and ivory complexion. There was a swath of cream-colored lace at the cuffs of her long sleeves but no garnish in her hair or hanging from her ears. A short, single strand of pearls adorned the neckline of her gown.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When she wasn’t talking to someone or dancing, as had happened three times since he’d been there, she seated herself alongside the wall with other ladies who watched the dancers and chatted happily among themselves. He kept thinking she didn’t belong there, among the women who, for whatever reason, had given up thought, hope, or desire of marrying.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was up to him to let her know her destiny wasn’t there. No time like the present to do it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He straightened and set off in her direction. As he drew closer, he felt as if every pair of eyes in the room were focused on him. It was as if they all had been waiting for him to seek her out so they could witness her response. It was his idea to go public with this pursuit. The chatter around him lowered as he passed. He didn’t mind. There was no reason for him to complain about the open display. It was of his own making.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane kept his gaze firmly on Mrs. Feld as he headed to the far wall where she was sitting. He didn’t allow anyone’s movements or talking distract him until he stood in front of her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When she looked up at him, his stomach tightened, and his senses stirred restlessly. Damnation, he had no doubts he’d made the right choice in choosing her. His gaze did a slow detailed sweep of her beautiful face before centering on her bright blue eyes. For a moment, he thought he saw surprise in their depths. Surely, she knew he would approach her before the evening was over.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He bowed. “Mrs. Feld. It’s good to see you again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She glanced about cautiously, rose, and curtsied. “My lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He reached for her gloved hand and the second his fingers closed around hers he felt a deep, rousing hunger shudder through him. He knew then she heated his blood like no other woman ever had. In the candlelight her eyes were captivating. He gave her the accepted, formal kiss on the back of her palm and then moved between her and the row of ladies behind her to give them a degree of privacy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Would you join me for this next dance?” he asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She inhaled deeply before saying, “And further more gossip about us? No, my lord, I believe you’ve done quite enough without any help from me, and I don’t think it would be in my best interest to accept.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her response wasn’t completely unexpected, so he took no offence. He relented with a smile. “All right. I suppose I deserved that rebuff after the wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, and much more. After what I’ve been through the past three days, were I capable of calling you out, I probably would have.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her saucy response made him chuckle softly. He gave her a nod of appreciation. “I believe you, and I’m a lucky man you can’t. You would be a formidable opponent. I have a feeling you’ll find a way of getting even with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve considered it and wish I could,” she said adamantly. “However, it’s your good fortune I wouldn’t dare stoop so low.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Though she was still angry with him, with just cause. Yet, even in her ire there was a softness and gentleness about her that drew him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m glad to see my ill-behavior hasn’t kept you from enjoying yourself this evening.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. It hasn’t,” she said and confidently lifted her chin. “You seem surprised that is the case.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m delighted. You’re a strong lady. I had no doubt you would carry on as normal.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Normal?” she asked with a breath of extreme exasperation. Her gaze focused tightly on his as she took a step toward him, seeming not to care that everyone was watching. “Really, my lord? You don’t know the half of it so don’t tell me you are delighted about anything concerning me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He noticed that her hands made fists at her sides. “That wasn’t my intention.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What was? You have completely disrupted my orderly life in the most tumultuous way possible. Because of you I’ve had a steady stream of ladies calling on me to make sure I haven’t taken to a sick bed over this wager you made. Some have sent baskets of flowers and others boxes of sweet confections to cheer me. I’ve received packages of handkerchiefs which I can only assume they felt I needed from all the crying I must be doing over your arrogant machinations. An anonymous person sent me an essay on Ophelia—of all things. Even the vicar paid me a visit to ask about my welfare. That you have the nerve to think I’m carrying on as normal is outrageous.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She was magnificent!</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her words and tone were heartfelt. He could almost taste her anger. By the time she’d finished a flush had heightened her face with indignation. It made her stunning. If they had been alone, he would have caught her up to his chest and kissed her, giving an outlet for all the passion pent up inside her. And there was plenty of it. But since they were far from alone, he offered the truth instead.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t stop to think of the many different ways this might affect your life.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Indeed!” She almost gasped after saying the word.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m sorry for that, but not for making the wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Disbelief danced in her bright eyes and made her all the more tempting. “I can’t believe you can say that so seriously. What kind of gentleman would do what you did?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A gentleman wouldn’t,” he answered with ease.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Exactly! Because of you, we’re the talk of Society. Everyone has been looking at us and whispering about us all night as they are doing right now. You are right. Manners and respect are taught, not born. You do need someone to teach you how to be a proper gentleman, but it won’t be me. Now, excuse me, my lord, but we are finished.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She turned away from him and sat back down in the row of ladies, all of whom were giving him the evil eye.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Tension flashed through him at her abrupt dismissal. His eyes narrowed, but then he looked at the beautiful curve of her lips set in a firm line, the satiny appearance of her skin and pillow soft swell of her breasts beneath her widow’s gown. Despite the prim exterior, he knew she was a deeply passionate woman and he wanted her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">No. He wouldn’t give up. Not for anything in the world. He hadn’t realized it until he saw her again, but she’d left him with a need that no other woman ever had.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She may not be aware of it, but she was a temptress, a curious mix of defiance and vulnerability. He understood that, accepted it, and could deal with it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">On the other hand, Zane had played enough cards to know there were times when you needed to cut your losses and save what you had for another game. Reluctantly, he would have to do that now—difficult as it was.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Feld was more than mildly upset with him about the wager and that made her as enticing as seeing a piece of spice cake on Christmas morning. Her vigor and fervor were seductive. He was going to relish every moment he spent with her. He wanted her to see him as the man she wanted to make her life complete.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As angry as she was with him, that wasn’t going to be easy to do.</p>
  </body>
</topic>