<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_8" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 6</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 6</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane had lost the first battle, but the night wasn’t over. He nodded once to Mrs. Feld, turned, and started walking away. The crowd that had somehow inched around them parted as he strode away. A few of them were close enough to have heard some of what she had to say. They could guess the rest.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That didn’t go well,” Uncle Hector said, coming up beside him almost immediately.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t need you walking with me, Uncle. I’m quite capable of handling the rejection of a lady refusing to dance with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, I know that. I only wanted to remind you I tried to tell you she wasn’t one you should try to court. There are more than a dozen ladies who would accept a proposal from you tonight. Best you put her and thoughts of winning your wager aside and get on to a young lady who’s looking for a husband. I have two more in mind.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It seems you don’t know me well, Uncle,” Zane offered, with no irritation at the man’s lack of misunderstanding that. Mrs. Feld was the one he wanted. “I always play to win and the game’s just started.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You are usually playing against a man,” Hector offered, struggling to keep up with Zane’s longer stride.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are you suggesting ladies don’t play fair, Uncle?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Certainly not. Though some do make that claim. I’m suggesting if it’s a widow you want to marry that you look more closely at Mrs. Pinewiffle. She’s not as lovely as Mrs. Feld, but she’s younger and I think she’ll be more accommodating to your marriage proposals. She appears healthy enough to give you as many sons as you want.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ll keep that suggestion in mind,” Zane said as Sylvester appeared at his other side.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If you were trying to keep the gossip going about you and Mrs. Feld, congratulations,” he said. “That was an excellent way to do it. Most of us couldn’t hear all of what was said, but we could see well enough to know she was giving you a dressing down you won’t soon forget.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And a fiery, delicious one it was, Zane thought and then chuckled. He didn’t want to forget it. He wanted to enjoy it. All it did was heat his blood more for her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Uncles,” Zane said as he stopped walking and looked at them. “You’re both acting as if this is the first time a lady has declined to dance with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It probably is,” Sylvester offered without a hint of a smile. “Perhaps if you sent her flowers instead of wagers she’d be more affable.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A server walked by and Zane stopped him. Grabbing two glasses of champagne for his uncles and then one for himself, he said, “No more lectures or suggestions. This is a ball. Let’s enjoy ourselves.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And Zane did. For at least another hour he danced, talked, and laughed among the other guests. As did Mrs. Feld. But he soon found himself drinking yet another glass of champagne and contemplating a second request for a dance with her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Lord Blacknight.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane didn’t recognize the voice, but he did the man when he turned to see the well-respected Earl of Lyonwood behind him. Lyon was the husband of one of Mrs. Feld’s best friends. Zane didn’t know the tall, broad-shouldered man standing beside Lyon, but it was a safe bet he was the husband of Mrs. Feld’s other good friend.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He didn’t think Mrs. Feld had said a word about him to the men standing before him. However, she’d probably talked to their wives at length after he’d seen them at her house a few days ago. And 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">they</i>
      had probably talked to 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">their</i>
      husbands. He appreciated the men’s show of force in approaching him and didn’t mind. As long as all they were doing was letting him know they were around just in case Mrs. Feld needed them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A breath of a smile lifted the corner of Zane’s mouth. They must have noticed him watching Mrs. Feld and assumed, rightly so, he was contemplating asking her to dance 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">one more time </i>
      before the evening ended.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Lord Lyonwood,” Zane said, dipping his chin in proper greeting. “It’s been a while since I’ve seen you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Welcome back to London even though the circumstances for your return weren’t what you would have wanted.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s true,” Zane said honestly, and looked at the man standing beside Lyon.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“May I present Mr. Garrett Stockton?” Lyon asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">May I present</i>was just a fraction of the manners and protocol of Society life Zane would prefer to ignore. He’d much rather have someone say the more informal 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">have you met </i>
      and not be so damned proper. But Lord Lyonwood had always known how to be a gentleman.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Though he’d never met the man, Zane had heard about Mr. Stockton and had a great deal of respect for the man who had been known as an adventurer. He’d shed the trappings of gentlemanly life for a time and traveled the seas to distant lands—much farther than Zane had ever traveled. From what he understood, the man had developed a formidable business in the shipping trade. Zane admired that kind of courage and free-thinking. He wouldn’t mind talking to him about his adventures over a glass of brandy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, Mr. Stockton,” Zane offered with a nod. “I don’t think our paths have ever crossed, but I’ve heard of you and the success of your company. I trust all is well.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve had good winds and fair seas as the old sea dogs like to say.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No doubt. I’ve never sailed the distances you have, Mr. Stockton, but I might want to do that one day. I’ve heard you’ve been to the Orient.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Singapore. It’s a long voyage and not for anyone who wasn’t sure he could spend a lot time on the close quarters of a ship.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Understood. I have no doubt it’s a fascinating country and worth the length of the journey for those who can endure it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ll be happy to talk more with you about it anytime, and it’s Garrett, if you would prefer.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded, appreciating Garrett’s friendly manner. The more protocols he could dispense with the better. Courtesy to your fellow man didn’t have to be as rigid as Society made it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you expect to be in London for all of the Season?” Lyon asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s my plan,” Zane answered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good. As you have probably heard, I have a card club that meets at my house once a week. We’re short a player this year. I wanted to invite you to join us if you have an interest.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane held his surprise in check. All esteemed gamesters and common gamblers alike had heard about Lord Lyonwood’s distinguished card club. Most of them would pay heavily for a chance to play with any of the members. Lyon’s father, the Marquis of Marksworth, was one of them and greatly respected not only in Society but all of London, too. Being invited to join the earl’s group would certainly make his uncles happy. They’d much rather see him playing cards in a home with titled gentlemen than the rowdy gaming hells near Bond Street. Zane was comfortable playing anywhere. So, hell yes, he welcomed this invitation. This news, and the fact he was pursuing Mrs. Feld, would go a long way in settling down the family a bit more.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We usually start at half past two on Thursdays,” Lyon continued calmly, showing no sign of being affronted when Zane didn’t immediately answer. “We keep it friendly but lively enough to enjoy the afternoon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve heard a few stories,” Zane answered, thinking Lyon had probably issued the invitation for the sole purpose of keeping an eye on him since he was pursuing Mrs. Feld. Zane was all right with that, too. He would have done the same if their roles were reversed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Lyon quirked his head and studied Zane. “So have I. Not all of them are true.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane smiled. “I didn’t think they were.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Can I count on you to join us?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I can manage that. Good of you to ask.” From the corner of his eye he saw Mrs. Feld walking toward the entrance. He didn’t know if she was leaving, but he didn’t want to take the chance. He had to talk to her again. “Gentlemen, if you’ll both excuse me. I was just about to ask someone to dance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His pursuit of the widow might have been started only to help settle his family’s jitters about the kind of earl he’d be. That changed fast after meeting with her earlier in the week. After that, there was real desire for her in his quest. He hadn’t expected to get so caught up with her, but she had filled his thoughts with an eager excitement he couldn’t remember ever feeling before. Obtaining the attention of a woman he was interested in had never been a problem. Mrs. Feld had already proven she would not dutifully fall in line as so many others had.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The ton loved drama and gossip more than anything, and Zane was about to give it to them in spades. He’d never been known for his self-restraint and there was no reason to curb what came naturally to him tonight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After having set his glass on a table, he caught up beside Mrs. Feld. She didn’t slow her step or look over at him but there was no doubt she stiffened when she realized he was walking with her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I just heard the call for a dance,” he said casually.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did you?” she said coolly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Would you join me for this one?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stopped and faced him. Her big, beautiful eyes narrowed, and a tiny wrinkle formed in her forehead. “I can’t believe you’re asking again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Obviously, time and the champagne he’d seen her sip hadn’t smoothed her ruffled feathers. He didn’t think she’d expected him to ask a second time either. Most men wouldn’t if turned down once in an evening, but that was another one of those accepted rules Zane had never followed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Everything about Mrs. Feld intrigued him. When he looked at her, there was an aura about her that had nothing to do with her beauty, sophistication, or her past experiences. But it was there, and it drew him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He remained relaxed as he took a slow, small step closer to her. “Did you really expect I wouldn’t?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. You should never ask a lady to dance twice in the same evening. Especially if she turns you down the first time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not like most men, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So I have found out. The hard way.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her a twitch of a smile, not minding that her temper hadn’t cooled. He was finding she stirred him like no other no matter her temperament. “Why would any man give-up trying to get something he wanted after only one attempt?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She seemed to ponder on that before saying, “I’m not saying in all things, but it’s the proper thing to do in this instance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She didn’t cower from his nearness but casually looked around the room, as if hoping no one was watching her converse with him. But of course, everyone had directed their attention to the two of them even if most pretended not to.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And because that is the way of it,” she continued. “You aren’t supposed to break the rules and certainly not in front of the most elite of Society. Probably most everyone in the ballroom is staring at us right now. I think that must be what you really wanted.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her a half smile. “Didn’t it cross your mind they were looking our way because you are beautiful?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” She blinked in horror for a second. Her cheeks flushed to a tempting shade of pink and her expression softened. “No, no, of course not. I would never think anything of the kind.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s true,” he said softly, letting his gaze sweep slowly down her face and back to her eyes. He knew he was vexing her, but he wasn’t trying to. Only stating the truth. “Everyone looks at you whether or not you are standing near the entrance with me or seated with the ladies. You’re beautiful, kind, and quite simply, Mrs. Feld, you fascinate them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Stop it,” she lowered her lashes for only a second and then looked around the room. “You don’t know what you’re talking about. I won’t hear any more of it. Every lady who is here tonight is beautiful.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I stand corrected. What I should have said is that you fascinate me. And you are the only lady in the room who does.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, you are an impossible man to talk to,” she said, looking back at him again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m determined.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She clasped her hands together in front of her. “Yes. I suppose you could call it that as well.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m still trying to settle in my mind that you aren’t the young maiden I thought you were that night in Paris, but a strong-minded capable lady who has created a good and noble life for herself and others.” He lowered his voice to a husky whisper, and said, “I want to dance with you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why are you being so insistent?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why are you refusing?” He kept his tone soft. “I’m not asking for your hand in marriage tonight, Mrs. Feld. Just for a dance. Everyone who is looking at us right now is thinking 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">‘will she say yes to him this time or turn him away again</i>
      ’?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Tell me, my lord, would you be happy and want to dance with me if I had done to you what you did to me?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Hell no.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I would be flattered if a lady wanted to no matter the reason.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, don’t try to sell that poppycock to me,” she said sternly, but quietly as one hand jerked to settle on her waist in frustration. “I don’t believe a word of it. Don’t pretend not to know every eligible lady in this room would marry you in a heartbeat. You are every lady’s dream. You are beyond handsome, a wild rake, and you are now an earl. What more could a lady want?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He kept his gaze tightly on hers and gave his head a light shake as he smiled. “You tell me. I’m only interested in you. All I’m asking for is a dance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If our situations were reversed and I had come back from Paris and pledged a wager I was going to marry you by the end of the Season how would you have handled it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He took in a long deep breath. “Carefully.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Which is exactly what I’m doing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her a twitch of a smile. “But I would have never refused a dance with you, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right,” she said, confidently as if she’d suddenly found courage she didn’t know she had. “One is about to start. We’ll have to hurry.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She marched off toward the dance floor. Zane stayed right beside her. They quickly positioned themselves in line with the others already in position for the cotillion. Ladies in a straight line facing their gentlemen partners. As the first chords were struck, they bowed to each other and the intricate dance began. It involved precise steps, perfectly timed moves, gentle touching their gloved hands and an occasional light gripping their fingers as she walked underneath his upheld arm.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane performed the intricate maneuvers with impeccable decorum considering he wanted to grasp her small waist, pull her close to his chest, pick her up and swing her around in his arms until they were both dizzy with delight. But that was for ladies in a bawdy house. Polite people didn’t dance that way.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He’d always enjoyed a waltz and a lively quadrille, but he’d never cared for the older, more formal dances of Society.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Until now.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As the dance progressed, he had to admit it was erotic in a way it had never been for him. There was a focused commitment and deliberation in each step that he’d never noticed. Her fluttering skirts brushed his legs seductively. The technique in how their hands touched ever so lightly, how she faced him so boldly before quickly turning away gave a feeling of intimacy with her. They moved in time with each other and with remarkable compatibility.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With Mrs. Feld the dance was a slow sensual repeating method of pursue, catch, and release. How had he never noticed that before?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Have you thought anymore about my proposal?” He asked as she passed under his arm for a slow twirl.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she answered. “I’ve been steaming about it since you were at my house.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That was the spirit that drew him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m glad to hear it,” he answered, their open palms touching lightly again. He was tempted to let his thumb brush against her wrist before they stepped back and bowed again but refrained. He didn’t want to send her rushing from the dance floor. He was absolutely mesmerized by her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They walked around in a tight circle and when they faced each other her eyes pierced him a determination he hadn’t seen from her before and suddenly, she said, “You have vexed me, my lord, to the point I think I 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">will</i>
      allow you to court me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A wave of anticipation swept through him like fire through dry brush. Zane nearly missed a step. Was she teasing him with her words as well as with the dance?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He remained silent and waited, sensing she would say more.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And I will do my best to make a proper gentleman out of you not only for your family but the benefit for all ladies who come in contact with you.” Her gaze stayed riveted on his as she passed in front of him. “And if I succeed, I will accept your proposal by midnight at the last ball of the Season.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Their palms met again as they stepped forward. The pressure from her touch was strong, sure. She was confident in what she was saying. His stomach tightened and his fingers closed over hers as she walked in a circle under his arm. The scent of wildflowers tempted his senses along with visions of kissing her lips, cheeks, and long slender neck.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Taking in a deep breath, he asked, “Am I to believe you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her fingers slipped out of his grip. They stepped away from each other and bowed before coming together again. “I don’t make promises I can’t keep, my lord. The question is, do you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With his gaze locked on hers he vowed, “I keep my word, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If that is true, I will marry you, but first, you must prove you’re capable of becoming a proper gentleman.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That should be easy enough,” he murmured as they walked in a tight circle. He’d been properly trained in how to be a gentleman.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Will it?” she asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That’s when Zane knew all wasn’t as it seemed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“During the remaining weeks of the Season you must give up wine, brandy, ale, and all spirits of any kind.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane gave a little snort as he clasped both her hands possessively and they twirled under each other’s arms. “Most gentlemen have a drink or two each day,” he said as her fingers slipped from his grasp again, but not before he let his thumb trace up and down her wrist a couple of times. “If you’d rather I not, I’ll give it up for you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Surely, he could manage not to take a drink for a few weeks. He’d never had a reason not to but was certain he could. Since that was all she was asking, it seemed a small price to pay for what he would get in the end.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You must also give up cards, dice, and all forms of gambling and wagering of any kind and for any reason.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s body stiffened. They continued to move through the painstaking steps of the complicated dance. Her courage was unbelievable. To even ask such a thing of an earl or any man was daring. Not only that—he’d just been invited to join the most sought-after card club in all of London. This demand wasn’t something he could take lightly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was finding out he couldn’t take her lightly either. The trouble was that he was falling for all of it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Again, Mrs. Feld,” he said from stiff lips, unable to suppress his disagreement in his tone. “Most gentlemen play cards whether or not they gamble. It’s a way of life that’s not usually questioned.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But you do both to excess,” she informed him, lifting her chin, making it clear she wouldn’t give an inch on this point. “The wager you placed at White’s is proof of that. But if you aren’t willing to try, I’ll withdraw my offer.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She was as cool as an early autumn morning. What she asked wouldn’t be easy. Everything about her was compelling. He considered once again what he would be giving up and what he would be getting in return.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right,” he finally said and could see from the tension around her eyes that she hadn’t expected him to agree to the second term of her agreement. Good. It was about time he got the upper hand in this matter, or at least caught up with her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You don’t think I can do it,” he offered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Maybe for a night but not until midnight of the last ball.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What a lovely spitfire she was turning out to be. He’d heard she was a nurturer. She enjoyed helping people. Taking care of them. Apparently, that didn’t include him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And there will be no swearing or cursing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” he snapped. “Blast it, Mrs. Feld,” he whispered, missing a step. The man next to him bumped his arm and gave him a foul look. Zane paid him no mind as his eyes were set only on his partner. “You go too far. Swearing is in a man’s nature and there’s no getting around it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her expression became more determined than ever and she leaned in toward him. “A well-educated gentleman such as yourself can find words to say other than swears, curses and cusses whether he’s with men, ladies, or horses.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Obviously, she could be fierce when she wanted to be. Zane bit back an oath and several vile bloody cuss words he wanted to say and simply ground out, “Fine. Consider it done. Are you finished now?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” she said as he lifted his arm for her to walk under.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What more could there be? I refuse to be in church every Sunday morning. I go on Christmas Day like most respectable people and that’s enough.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No women.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">No women?</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane felt a twitch between his shoulder blades that ran up the back of his neck and throbbed in his temples. His fingers tightened on hers again. Where did she get the nerve to demand such compliance from him? The truth was he hadn’t wanted to be with another woman since he’d seen her again, but he didn’t want her telling him he couldn’t be with someone if he wanted to.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She blinked rapidly and her shapely lips were set in a firm line. He was certain she’d said 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">no women</i>
      impulsively. It wasn’t something a genteel lady of the ton would say to a man. But he also knew now she had uttered it; she’d never take it back.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s going—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Feld froze and dropped her hands to her side and fixed her gaze on his. From the corner of his eye, Zane watched as the other dancers slowly realized what was going on and the line stopped in sequence. The music slowly died away and so did the chatter of the crowd.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Intensity radiated from her stance, her expression, and her countenance. She couldn’t have been more serious. And he knew why. She didn’t think he could do any of it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No women, no cards, no wagering, and no swearing,” she said unwaveringly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are you trying to make me a saint!” he said a little louder than he intended.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. Only a gentleman. But I will end proving you can’t change your rakish ways and furthermore, that you don’t want to.” She scoffed. “But if you can—” Suddenly her countenance changed. She relaxed her inflexible stance and smiled, confidently. “I’m yours.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The ballroom was as quiet as a sealed tomb. Realization of what was happening hit him. The kind, beautiful, and perfect widow he thought would make him respectable was really going to try to make him respectable.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He bent closer toward her ear and whispered so only she could hear, “I hope 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">no women</i>
      doesn’t include kissing. I have to kiss a lady’s hand, my sister, and cousins’ cheeks.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She held her ground unflinchingly as she seemed to consider what he said. “Understood,” she acknowledged in a tone as low as his. “Kissing accepted.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Over Mrs. Feld’s shoulder, Zane watched Lyon and Garrett push through the gathered crowd and move into his view. Their wives nudged their way beside them. They were taking a stand and making sure he knew in no uncertain terms they were there to protect her if she needed them. Movement on the other side of the room caught his eye. Patricia and his uncles stepped forward, too, and looked on with keen interest. But were they on his side or Mrs. Feld’s.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The gauntlet had been thrown down, but Zane wasn’t sure if he’d thrown it or Mrs. Feld had. One thing was sure, this cat-and-mouse game that only the two of them were playing had been witnessed by many.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">From the crowd, Zane heard whispers that did nothing to aid his thoughts on what just happened between the two of them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“He can’t do it,” </i>a man said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“No, he won’t accept her terms,” </i>someone else added.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“Can’t say as I blame him.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“What respectable gentleman would be willing to give up his ale and cards in the afternoons and his brandy in the evenings?”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“Or women?”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“He’d be a fool to try,” </i>a different man answered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“I’d say she got the best of him.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not yet, she hadn’t, Zane thought. His pursuit of Mrs. Feld has only just begun.</p>
  </body>
</topic>