<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_27" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 25</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 25</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina always felt better after visiting with the sisters at Pilwillow Crossings. She had deliberately stayed away from her house until darkness covered the sky. Not only did it nourish her spirit to be at the abbey but today it kept her from having to talk with Adeline and Julia. They meant well but she wasn’t up to bearing their concern for her. She hadn’t actually told them how deeply she felt for Zane, but she was sure they knew. Probably from the first time they saw her with him they knew she felt differently about him than any other man. She’d never hidden that from them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Having been too numb to sleep for very long, she’d sent them both a note early in the morning saying she’d be out all day and would see them at the ball. She wanted no one going with her, acting as a companion and certainly not as the dedicated friends they were. Part of her healing would be handling this on her. She couldn’t let losing Zane affect her the way losing Stewart had. From that her recovery had been long. Now she was older and wiser but she knew she would miss Zane all the days of her life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A tired laugh passed her throat as she walked up to her front door. It appeared Zane had changed her more than she had changed him. Imagine her—a widow showing up at a ball without a companion. It simply wasn’t done but she would. If the old guard of Society were so inclined, they could shun her. Right now, she’d welcome it. She was feeling very much alone anyway.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wouldn’t be spending the rest of her life any different than she’d expected for the past five years. She had always said she’d never marry again and believed it—until Zane had her dreaming of happily-ever-afters. For a few days he had given her hope she could enjoy the incomparable feeling of true love.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Oh, why had she fallen in love with London’s most notorious rake?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What hurt the worst was that he never truly loved her. Why else would he have gone to the club and spent the night gambling and—and? Her thoughts paused. He’d said there were no women.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She swallowed hard. Even now she wanted to believe that was true.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But again, it didn’t change the outcome. Any or all, it was the one sure way he wouldn’t have to marry her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Staying at the abbey also kept her from the possibility of seeing Zane should he even want to see her and try once again to explain his unforgivable actions last night.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After they made love, she had lay bare her deepest soul to him, telling him things she’d never told anyone. How could he have been so callous with her love?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina opened the door and started taking off her gloves.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Is that you, Mrs. Feld?” Mrs. Lawton called from above the stairs.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she answered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Lord Blacknight has called on you three times today and waited more than an hour each time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you for letting me know, Mrs. Lawton,” she answered, untying her bonnet.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You best hurry on up. You’re already late getting ready for the ball.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina placed her bonnet, gloves and reticule on the side table. There, lined in a neat row were three notes. Her name written in the bold lettering of a man. She started to swipe them all off the table and fling them as far as she could. How dare he start trying to follow accepted rules now!</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She turned away and headed up the stairs. After all the times he came over without asking, how dare he leave her notes today. She walked into her room and gasped. Hanging on her wardrobe was the gorgeous bright pink gown that had been hanging in the shop window near the abbey.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It arrived this afternoon,” Mrs. Lawton said with a beaming smile. “I figured you wanted to wear it tonight, so I pressed it for you and laid out your stockings, shoes and jewelry for you to choose from.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina’s heartache over the earl had been so great, she’d forgotten she’d gone to the shop yesterday and had been fitted for the gown.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">To wear tonight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When she thought she’d be accepting Zane’s proposal.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not an apology.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Anger jumped on her so fast she was suddenly reeling. She couldn’t believe she was such an idiot. To want Zane to see her in that color again. No! No! She was a widow and would remain a widow, wearing dark, drab widows’ weeds.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Why would she want to ever wear that dress? She didn’t even want to go to the ball. An apology from Lord Blacknight meant nothing to her. His word meant nothing to her or anyone else. She’d hung so much hope on him. On that gown. Now she hated it. She never wanted to see the color pink again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina ripped the dress off the wardrobe, wadded and squeezed it into a tight ball. She rushed over to the window and with amazing strength threw it open and hurled the gown out.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mrs. Feld, what are you doing!” Mrs. Lawton exclaimed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">In the bright moonlight Brina watched as the wind caught under the thin gossamer fabric and lifted it higher for a moment before slowly allowing the gown to flutter down and fall in a heap on top of the purple rhododerdron bush. She stared down at discarded silk and should have felt better.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But she didn’t.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s apology wouldn’t make her feel better, either. He wouldn’t mean it anyway. If 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">he</i>
      even showed up publicly to give it. Fine. She didn’t want it. It no longer mattered. All she felt was loss.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Another terrible, terrible loss.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mrs. Feld?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina heard the housekeeper’s worried voice behind her. She straightened from the window and faced Mrs. Lawton, doing her best to act as if the woman hadn’t witnessed her display of anger.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Should I mix you a tonic of brandy and honey.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.” She softly closed the widow. “But I think I will have a brandy. I didn’t sleep well last night and I’m told it will help settle the nerves.” She turned and saw her bed where Mrs. Lawton had laid out her shoes, stockings and lace-trimmed stays. “I’ve decided I’m not going to the ball tonight. You can put away my jewelry and other things and lay out my robe. I’ll be back up shortly.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She walked downstairs and was headed down the corridor for the drawing room to pour a nip of brandy when she heard a light tap on the front door. Her heart felt as if it jumped to her throat as her first thought was Zane. Her first thought was always Zane. But then the sound came again and she realized it sounded like Harper’s knock. She started to call up to Mrs. Lawton to answer the door but stopped. Even if it was the earl, she couldn’t be afraid to face him. What was done, was done.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Cautiously opening the door, she saw it was Harper and fell into his arms. She was so happy it wasn’t Zane. If it had been him, she might have wanted to listen to his excuses, to hear an apology.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina, dearest,” he said, holding her tight. “I’m all right. Everything is fine now. Don’t be upset.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m just glad it’s you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Who else would it be? Everyone else is at the ball. Where you should be dancing and enjoying yourself.” He held her for a moment longer and then set her away from him. “Why aren’t you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She breathed in heavily and suddenly noticed his face. His lip was swollen and there was a cut above his eye.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not going—but, Harper, by the heavens! What happened to you? Who did this? Don’t tell me you fell as Robert did. I won’t believe you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, no. I didn’t want you to see me like this. I didn’t think you would be here. I only came to return this.” He reached into his coat pocket and pulled out a note and one of her mother’s fine porcelain figurines and placed them on the side table by her bonnet.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What had happened at her parents’ house came back to Brina, and she said, “I don’t understand. What were you doing with it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I stole it from their house. That’s why I was there the afternoon you saw me. I was going to sell it to help pay on my debts to Mr. Remick.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She gasped. “Gambling debts?” She knew Zane’s cousin had been a bad influence on Harper. This was proof.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“In the end, I didn’t have the nerve to sell it. At first, I thought to just slip back into their house and replace it but Lord Blacknight told us last night that when you’ve done something wrong you should make it right.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She tensed even more. “You saw the earl last night?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not at first.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did he do this to your face?” She could hardly breathe. “He will hear from me about this.” She started toward the door. “Tonight!”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What? Brina, wait. What are you thinking? He didn’t do this. As heaven is my witness, Blacknight saved us last night. I’ll always be grateful to him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina blinked. Her mind seemed to be going faster than her ears could hear. “Us? You and Robert? Saved you from what? It looks to me as if he’s taught the two of you how to be brawling gamesters just like he is.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.” Harper’s eyes narrowed in disbelief and he shook his head. “Didn’t the earl tell you what happened? He was in such a hurry to get back to you. I’ve never seen a man so on edge about the time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt as if her body were going limp as Harper’s words were sinking in. “No, and I don’t want to hear anything he has to say. He’s not a gentleman. He’s not a man of his word and I hope I never see him again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You really don’t know what he did, do you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know he gambled.” Thinking about that renewed her strength. “That’s enough.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But you need to know why he played cards.” He took both her hands in his. “You’ll listen to me about this,” he said firmly, making sure her gaze stayed on his. “Robert and I were duped into a high stakes games with Mr. Remick and when we couldn’t pay them, he forcibly took us to a crimping house. He wouldn’t accept money from the earl because Remick considers himself a master of cards. He insisted Lord Blacknight had to play him one game at a time to win our freedom. If he hadn’t done it, Robert and I would be on a ship heading to Singapore right now as payment for our debt.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Singapore!”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. We were crimped. It’s what Mr. Remick does. With his skill, Lord Blacknight played in front of everyone at the gaming house and finally won enough games to save us from months or years at sea.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina couldn’t think straight. The only thing she could manage was to shake her head and hug Harper again. “I’m so glad he saved you from that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I can’t stay any longer. Lord Blacknight thought it would be best if I stayed out of London for a while. He hired a coach to take me to Northcumberland. It’s waiting for me. He’s sending Robert away, too. I didn’t ask where. We’re both happy to still be in England not to have been sold to a boarding master.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane played to save Harper and Robert.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t be upset with the earl for gambling. He was so furious he railed at us because he had to break his promise to you. It really bothered him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He saved you?” she whispered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper nodded again. “I hope one day he’ll forgive me and that you will, too. And I hope you’ll forgive him for breaking his promise to you. He’s in love with you. That was clear to me and Robert. So, it’s our fault he—</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Excuse me, Harper. I must hurry.” She turned and started rushing up the stairs. “Mrs. Lawton,” she called. “I’ve changed my mind. Heat your iron. But first, run outside and get the pink gown off the rhododerdron.”</p>
  </body>
</topic>