<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_19" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 17</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 17</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Passion was a peculiar thing Brina decided, placing a large basket on the dining room table. She was certain she’d had as much of it for her husband as she now had for the earl. The problem was, she didn’t remember it. The past couple of nights she’d lain awake in her bed trying to recall the memories of Stewart’s touch.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She’d failed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Once they were so vivid. Now, she couldn’t bring them to mind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Perhaps it wasn’t so odd she couldn’t summon them to comfort her anymore. It was so long ago. At one time, recollections of her husband had overwhelmed her to the point she thought she’d never recover from the loss. The sad truth that she hated to admit even to herself was that feelings and memories of Stewart had started to fade before Zane came into her life and disrupted it with his wager, his kisses, and his very presence.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Now it was Blacknight who took up too much space in her thoughts. If she wasn’t thinking about him, she would see, hear, or touch something that would bring him to mind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Especially when she was alone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She hardly had room for other and more important things to ponder such as getting on with the preparations to give the girls painting lessons. The spring weather had been lovely, and it would be helpful to the girls in their sewing classes if they knew how to sketch a dress and then paint it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yet, time after time, she put those thoughts aside because she greatly enjoyed thinking about Zane and remembering his touch and kisses. How divinely delicious it was to feel wanted again. For some reason, she’d always thought it would be a betrayal to Stewart to have wanton desires for another man, but now that she actually had those feelings for Zane, she didn’t feel disloyal to Stewart’s memory at all.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She only felt hard, fast, flowing 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">passion</i>
      .</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And that was troublesome. She hadn’t expected to be so enamored of him. He was supposed to be a rake. Why hadn’t she heard that he was drinking and gambling—or at the very least, swearing? That is what she needed the earl to do. Not give her kisses that made her feel as if she were melting into a pool of sensuous fantasy. Not proving he could change. That he could be a gentleman refuse her invitation for more than kisses thrice.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Thrice!</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She had no doubt he wanted her. The evidence had been clear, strong, and tempting. She desperately wanted him—to be with him, but she hadn’t changed her mind about marriage. It was too hard. Too heartbreaking and she’d never live through that again for any man.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A knock on the front door made Brina jump. Her first thought was that it was Zane. Anticipation gripped her. And that aggravated her. Why did he have to be the first person to come to mind?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It could be anyone,” she whispered, and shook her head at how easily she could get caught up into thinking about the unforgettable earl.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Maybe Adeline had walked over with her rambunctious little boy. Chatwyn loved to throw the ball to her while she and Adeline chatted. Perhaps Julia had stopped by for a visit or maybe even Mr. Inwood had sent more flowers. The young bachelor had already sent two baskets. All of them pink. He was handsome, nice and gentlemanly. A note asking if he might call on her always accompanied the bouquets. Brina had absolutely no desire to have him court her. She had all she could handle wrapped up in a man named Blacknight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Heaven help her! The only time he should cross her mind was when she was envisioning him going to his club and drowning himself in brandy and gambling. That was the only thing that was going to save her from a marriage she didn’t won’t.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And so far, he hadn’t cooperated.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m only home for Adeline or Julia,” Brina called to Mrs. Lawton as she passed the dining room doorway heading to the front of the house.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I understand, Mrs. Feld,” the housekeeper assured her without breaking her stride.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Determined to rid herself of purely selfish thoughts, Brina pulled a large, round tin out of her basket and placed it on the table. Next, she grabbed the stack of thin cotton fabric she had cut into small squares, and then the lengths of string she’d carefully measured and snipped yesterday afternoon. She lined them up perfectly on the table in the order she’d use them. This system made her project go quickly and easily.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After opening the tin, she shook most of the contents into the bowl and placed a teaspoon in the middle of it. That’s when she heard a man’s voice. A familiar voice. The earl’s voice.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Anticipation filled her again. Followed by more annoyance with herself. It would be so much easier if she felt nothing but mere curiosity when he came to her door. Why did he refuse the usual manner of sending a note asking to call on her at an appointed time? Why did she even want to see him? He’d been nothing but trouble since the first time she met him. She would have saved herself a lot of distress if she’d just left him tied to the chair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Lawton quietly appeared. “I know you didn’t want to be disturbed, Mrs. Feld, but it’s Lord Blacknight. He says he’s hoping you’ll make an exception and see him. He has something important he needs to discuss with you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Important?” That got her interest. “Yes, thank you, Mrs. Lawton. Ask him to join me in here.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Any resolve she’d had not to be affected by him melted away the moment he appeared in the doorway of the dining room. Her heart and chest felt as if it expanded. His tall lean body looked exceptionally powerful. The color and texture of his thick black hair and the way he combed it away from his face gave him a strong, fierce appearance that drew her. Now, she knew she would never grow tired of looking at him or being moved by the sight of him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His dark blue eyes brushed softly over her face. She didn’t know how, but she felt his deep desire for her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good afternoon, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Trying to tamp down all she was feeling and her simple delight at seeing him, she said, “My lord, don’t you think it would have been nice to let me know you wanted to come over this afternoon?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I thought you liked surprises.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His innocent comment made her smile. “Perhaps, but I’m not certain I always appreciate surprises from you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You seemed to enjoy it when I brought horses for you to ride. The fast curricle.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. I suppose I enjoyed both those things, but then there was the matter of the wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He winced and stepped farther into the dining room. “Not my finest hour.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, but we won’t dwell on that. Mrs. Lawton said you had something important to discuss with me. Naturally that made me curious.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m glad. I wanted to know if you’ve seen or heard from Harper in the past couple of days?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, I saw him day before yesterday. He came over and had tea with me. We had a lovely visit both times except for—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He walked toward her slowly, determined until he stood just inches away. “For what?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He was very concerned about the curricle ride with you—as most everyone seems to be.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s features relaxed and he smiled and nodded. “I received my share of lectures about how irresponsible I was to be so uncontrolled when you were in my care.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina huffed and folded her arms across her chest. “I really can’t fathom the stir it has caused. I thought Harper might really be on the verge of calling you out for endangering my life.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Maybe he should have. I’ve heard several comments maligning my lack of restraint.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nonsense. Your handling of the horses saved us from crashing more than once.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He smiled and accepted her praise without comment.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I had to tell him I’m the one who encouraged you because I didn’t like being spied upon. The way everyone is acting, you’d think I was the first lady to ride in a carriage that was speeding along that fast.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He lifted one dark brow. “Maybe you were. We were almost flying.” His voice lowered to almost a whisper as he continued, “More than that, I think everyone sees you as an angel, and I am the devil who is corrupting you and leading you astray.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina tensed and turned away from him. She didn’t like that characterization used for her. If people only knew what she’d done, they’d never call her that again. She wasn’t an angel. Far from it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked over to the table. Realizing she hadn’t replaced the lid on the tin, she asked, “What was the particular reason you wanted to see me about Harper?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He followed her over to the table and leaned a hip against it. “I wondered if he might have mentioned Robert during your visits with him. Uncle Hector said he hasn’t been home in a couple of days, which is unusual, so he’s worrying.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Robert have a place of his own?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. I know he and Harper have been out together and I was hoping he might have mentioned Robert was staying with him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I suppose he could be, though it would be unlikely he’d stay with him for long. I’ve not actually been there, but my father has said that Harper’s room is quite small. If you’re concerned, I could send a note and ask him to come see me about this.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl shook his head. “I’d rather you didn’t. Young men don’t usually want their fathers or uncles asking questions. Robert’s impulsive. He could be staying at someone’s house for a card party or other things.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s quite possible. Harper mentioned he’d recently gotten more involved in playing cards and he hoped to be invited to join a card club soon. He was quite excited about it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane straightened. “Did he happen to give the name of the person who invited him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not that I recall.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Can you think of anything else?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Harper has been acting a little strange lately,” Brina offered, but didn’t want to say too much. She couldn’t come out and accuse Zane’s cousin of influencing Harper with his gambling. Not at this point anyway. Though there might come a time she’d have to say something. “It wouldn’t have been proper for me to quiz him about it. Men enjoy their gaming.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As we’ve mention, Lyon has a private card club.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But very exclusive, Brina.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She returned the tin to the table after securing the lid. “All men think their clubs are exclusive, do they not? Where or who Harper plays cards with is not any of my business. For now. Perhaps Robert’s shouldn’t be any of yours or his father’s.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I only want to satisfy Uncle Hector that all is well with his son. Apparently, if there is a problem that arises within my family, I am the one who is duty bound to promptly take care of it. Besides, asking you about Robert gave me the opportunity to come see you.” He gave her a twitch of a smile. “Robert wasn’t my only reason for coming over. I wanted to see you. I enjoy being with you, looking at you, and desiring you as intensely as I am right now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina’s heart started beating faster. Glancing down at her dress, there was nothing suggestive about the loose-fitting pale brown gown she wore but his words made her feel as if she were clothed in a luxurious silk gown.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I—I don’t know what to say to that. It’s not the kind of thing a gentleman should say to a lady. Thank you doesn’t seem appropriate for such a comment.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You don’t have to say anything.” He gave her an endearing smile. “I just wanted you to know—in case you had any doubts. Let’s go riding. I brought the horses.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That would be delightful. She’d love to do it again. It was a beautiful afternoon. She glanced at the table and then down at her feet. The toes of her black satin slippers peeked from beneath the hem of her skirt. She didn’t even have her riding boots. Much as she would like to ride again, she simply wasn’t prepared. Why couldn’t he give her proper notice?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She sighed. “No. I can’t possibly go this afternoon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You need to ride again so you won’t forget how.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t forget in five years.” Brina gave a soft chuckle. “I’m not likely to forget now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Let’s make sure you don’t. We’ll be followed again, but I’m getting used to the men who watch me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s such a beastly thing for them to do. I don’t know how you put up with it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shrugged in a nonchalant manner gave her a bit of a grin. “I am putting up with a lot of things right now, Brina. Compared to some of those things, these men don’t bother me at all. I wave or tip my hat so they know I see them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She knew he was talking about the things she had forced him to give up. But he was kind enough not to spell that out and she was grateful for that. There were still times she couldn’t believe she’d issued all those demands. Or that, so far, he’d followed them all.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, I can’t ride today. I must finish getting these ready for Pilwillow Crossings. I need to take them to the sisters. It has to be tomorrow because Julia has already asked to go with me. I really can’t change the day.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He glanced at her odd collection of items on the table. “What is it you’re making?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Little bags of comfort,” she said softly. “I add a spoon of tea leaves to the center of the little squares and then tie up the ends with a string. These small sizes make enough for one cup of tea.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He studied on that for a moment before looking at her with a puzzled expression, and asked, “Wouldn’t it be far less trouble if you just gave them the entire tin?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You think it’s for the sisters to drink?” She laughed. “No. These are for the sisters to hand out to people who aren’t fortunate to have tea or even food every day. For some it will be the only tea they get. Three mornings a week the sisters make soup and bread to give to the needy. They also provide poultices to those who may have an injury. I asked if I could help by making these little bags of tea to hand to everyone who comes. Most of the people who come have few comforts in life. At times, something as simple as a warm cup of tea can make one feel better no matter the circumstances.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He reached out and briefly caressed her cheek with his fingertips. His touch was warm and soothing. “They probably enjoy the tea as much as the soup.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know about that,” she said honestly. “It’s certainly not as nourishing. Yesterday, I rolled bandages for the sisters to give to those in need.” She looked down to the other end of the table at a large basket brimming with white rolls of cloth.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You did all that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She nodded. “It’s such an easy thing to do but means so much. Some have injuries that get very little care and most have nothing to cover the wounds to keep them clean. I take all I’ve made to the sisters once or twice a week.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m understanding more now why my uncles kept telling me you were too good for me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She turned away from his touch. “Please don’t say things like that. It upsets me to hear it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His expression quizzed her. “Why? It’s true.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She remained silent. She couldn’t explain and didn’t want to. Feeling a pang of sadness, she offered, “As you know, our Society frowns upon a lady doing anything that might be considered work, but I’m not bothered by that. It feels good to be needed, to help others have a better life. I wanted to help the sisters pass out the food to the ones who come for help. Unfortunately, Sister Francine wouldn’t even consider it, but not because I was from Society.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What then?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I wa’st capable.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He looked at her as if she might have lost her mind. “No. I don’t believe that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s ture. She was right to refuse my offer. I would be giving extra handfuls to the people with children and then others would be left without anything to take with them. The sisters do it as equitable as possible. They have learned how to be compassionate while being dispassionate. Very difficult to do. They are good at being kind and just to everyone who comes for help.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What you’re doing is kind, too.” His eyes softened. “Why does it trouble you so to be thought of that way?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Because she knew how truly awful she’d been.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane touched her cheek again, this time letting his fingers trail over her jaw, down her neck and arm where he caught her hand in his. Squeezing her fingers, he brought her hand up to his lips and kissed the back of her palm. His touch was warm. The small gesture comforted her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How did you get started doing this?” he asked as he continued his hold on her hand placed on his chest over his heart. “Did the sisters ask for your help?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">How much did she want to tell him?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Understanding filled his eyes and expression. Brina was drawn even more to him. Beneath her hand, his chest was warm, solid.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He lightly squeezed her palm again. “Tell me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“By chance I was riding by the abbey and saw a long line of poorly clothed men, women, and children. They passed by a table where a sister dipped into a large pot and filled their cups and bowls with soup. Another sister would hand them a piece of bread. Not far away, another table was set up where sisters handed out bandages and little bags, something like the ones I’m making. Later, I found out they were filled with herbs that had healing qualities. I went back several times before I had the nerve to go inside and actually talk to one of the sisters.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes turned curious. “Surely they were happy to have caught your interest.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">All the inadequacies she felt after that first visit came crashing down on her. “Not exactly. You don’t want to know about any of this,” she said dismissively, and she didn’t want to tell him. It was another part of her past she kept hidden. She pulled her hand away from Zane’s grasp, and walked to the window and looked over the small garden.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He followed and touched her shoulder affectionately. “Of course, I do. I want to know everything about you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Keeping her gaze set on the view from the windowpane she whispered, “It’s not easy to talk about one’s shortcomings.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you have any?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His tone seemed so sincere, not sarcastic and without really knowing why, she turned to him and said, “I told Sister Francine I wanted to leave my place in Society and join the abbey to help them take care of unfortunate people.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He blinked and his brows rose.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You look as shocked as Julia did the day I told her I wanted to join the abbey.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am,” he admitted honestly. “Making it possible for unfortunate people to have a cup of tea is a long way from taking a vow.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know.” She offered a bit of a sad smile. “The sisters do so much selfless work for others. They are good-hearted women and I have such admiration for them and all they do. I wanted to be a part of that. I felt if I could just be good enough, just help them, and help enough people I could redeem—” she stopped and swallowed hard.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gently took hold of her shoulders and squeezed just enough to let her know what she was saying was important to him. “Redeem what?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She appreciated the shimmering light of concern that shone in his eyes and earnest, honest appeal to have her tell him more, but she couldn’t. She didn’t want him or anyone to know all her past. As it was, she’d already said too much.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Too many things,” she finally said. “The sisters rise in the mornings thinking, 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">how many suffering people can I help today</i>
      . I rise and say, 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">what will I play on the pianoforte this morning. What dress will I wear to the park this afternoon or to dinner party this evening?</i>
      My life was so empty, and helping people who truly need it was the only way I could think to help myself.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A sad laugh escaped past her lips and she shook her head. She needed to be a better person, to do more for people but didn’t know if she could ever make up for her past. “Sister Francine took one look at me and knew I couldn’t handle what would have been required of me physically or mentally. In my desperation at the time I didn’t believe her, but she was so right.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have my own reasons for being glad she recognized you shouldn’t join the abbey.” He pulled her close and wrapped his arms around her as he reached down and kissed her forehead, letting his lips trickle down to just below her eyes before whispering, “But I refuse to believe you wouldn’t have been strong enough to handle it. You certainly seem to know how to handle me and I know that is no easy task.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina found herself amused by his last comment and snuggled in deeper into his comforting embrace, laying her check against his warm chest. “I don’t know how to handle you at all. You frustrate me at almost every turn. And I found I’m not suited for a complete life of servitude no matter my protests to the opposite at the time. Unfortunately, it took me a while to realize that while my intentions were quite admirable, they were not practical for me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What happened to make you aware of it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Actually, Julia helped me realize my inadequacies by proving to me that I didn’t know how to care for myself so I certainly couldn’t take care of anyone else. I didn’t realize how sheltered my life had been and how incapable I was until I tried to do something for myself. After a disastrous afternoon in a kitchen trying to cook a meal, I concluded it would be best to aid the sisters in other ways. As I do now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina raised her head and looked over at the tea, cloth and string, before looking back to Zane.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know why I’m telling you all this,” she said, looking back into his eyes. “I’ve never told anyone I was thinking of joining the abbey. Adeline and Julia know, of course, and the sisters. But no one else. I’ve never wanted others to know I failed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Failed?” He grimaced. “What rubbish.” His arms tighten around her and he kissed the top of her forehead again. “You didn’t fail. You learned a lesson. An important lesson. Different people are suited for different lives.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I do believe that now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You know, I feel the same way you felt. I’m not suited for the life of an earl. I would rather have the carefree life of a gamester than be deciding which of my family needs more allowance, which tenant needs the fees lowered, which party I’ll support in Parliament. I don’t want to the responsibility for any of those things and many others. The only difference is that you had a choice. I don’t. You chose wisely and so must I. I am the earl whether or not I’m suited so I must learn to be the best I can be. That’s why I need you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His words lifted her heart and she swallowed down the feeling of inadequacy that often rose inside her. “I suppose you do understand. Your problem is that you don’t like following accepted rules.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Rules are enjoyable only if you are breaking them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina heard laughter in his voice. It rumbled in his chest. She closed her eyes and enjoyed the sound before turning her face up to look at him again. “Now you have me curious. What rules have you been breaking since I last saw you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“None of yours, of course.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The mischievous light that touched his eyes made her realize how much she enjoyed his sense of humor. “Are you sure? Not even a nip of brandy before you go to bed to settle your nerves.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” he asked, with a guileless smile. “You doubt me?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Spoken like a true rake.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He brushed his hand along the side of her hair. “Not everyone can be as angelic as you, Brina.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She stiffened at his words and pushed out of his arms. She was no angel. If he knew the truth, he’d never say that again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He tried to pull her into his arms again, but she resisted. “What kind of angel neglects the needs of others to go for a ride in the park.” She looked back toward her supplies lined so neatly on the table. “I must get back to my work.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right,” he said and walked over to the table and picked up a piece of the cloth. “Let me see if I can figure this out. You hold it like this.” He laid the white square in the palm of his hand and added a spoonful of the tea leaves to the center. After bringing all the ends together, he picked up a string and tied it in a bow. Holding it up to her, he smiled. “There. With me helping it will take half the time to finish this, and we’ll still have enough daylight for a short ride through the park.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane knew how to touch her heart to make her feel wonderful. He was an earl! It was almost unbelievable that he wanted to help her do something so menial, but she saw in his eyes he was sincere.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That looks good,” she praised him before adding in a light-hearted tone, “but you don’t have it quite right.” Taking the little sack from him, she untied the bow. “You must give the fabric a twist like this and then make a very tight reef knot.” She quickly retied it and gave it to him to inspect. “That will secure it so it won’t accidently come untied and the tea be lost to the wind before the person gets home.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Understood,” he said, and pulled out the chair in front of the items and sat down. He grabbed another square to make it as she had shown. “I’ll keep doing this while you change into proper riding clothes. If I haven’t filled all of them by the time you return, we will before we go riding.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” She eyed him with teasing annoyance. “You think you might complete these before I can change and return? There are one hundred squares here.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Ninety-seven.” He started on another one. “We’ll see. I’m working and you are still standing there. I bet you I’ll have more than half of them finished before you are down and ready to go.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina started for the stairs but stopped short of leaving the room and turned back to the earl. A breathy 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">oh</i>
      passed her lips as she gave him a knowing smile. She walked closer to him. “Did you just offer me a bet, my lord?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His hands stilled on the string. His eyes narrowed just enough to let her know that he knew immediately what she was referring to.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he offered casually, and finished tying the knot.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You did,” she insisted with mock seriousness, inching even closer to him. “You are caught. You said 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">I bet</i>
      you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane smiled up at her, and placed the bag on the table with the others. He rose from the chair, slid his hands around her waist, and pulled her close. His gaze locked solidly onto hers. “No,” he insisted with an earnest expression. “It was just a turn of phrase, figure of speech, a slip of the tongue habit. Not a legitimate call for a bet.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His hold on her was friendly. She could have easily slipped out of his embrace, but she didn’t want to. They were alone in her dining room and suddenly she wanted more from him. She wanted his heart-thudding kisses again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not so sure about that, my lord,” she answered in a light-hearted tone. Her shoulders swayed lightly from side to side, her hips rocking against the firm hold of his hands. “Perhaps you should try to convince me what you claim is true.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His arms tightened on her and his face moved closer to hers. “I do believe you are tempting me to behave badly, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She nodded her confession and asked, “What are you going to do about it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For a long moment he stared at her, taking stock of her teasing attitude to assess whether she was serious.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I may have to kiss you,” he said in a voice that was soft and enticingly husky.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes, that’s exactly what she wanted. Their last time together was seared into her memory and she ached to be that close, that intimate with him again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He waited for a response from her. She remained silent but her eyes moved hungrily over his face. It was impossible to deny the yearning he had caused inside her. She reached up and let her fingers slowly drift down his cheek and across his closed lips, marking their shape with her fingertips. After she lowered her hand, he took the initiative, bowed his head and tenderly kissed her briefly on the lips.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Is that what you had in mind?” he whispered huskily.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” she answered on a gusty breath. “This is what I had in mind.” Her arms slid underneath his coat and circled his slim waist. She lifted her lips to his and pressed ardently to show him how she wanted to be kissed with passion. Her mouth clung to his in an eagerness she didn’t know she possessed as her hands slid up his wide, strong back.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane answered her kisses and this time held nothing back. His lips moved commandingly over hers, his tongue probing and searching her mouth.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she whispered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">This is what she’d wanted. To be held tightly, kissed thoroughly again and again. Her head fell back, and his lips moved over her jawline, down her neck and back to her lips. His hands caressed all around her shoulders, past her nape to where his fingers slid into the back of her hair. He held her head steady as he deepened the kiss again and again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Flames of passion flared between. His mouth sought hers over and over again with ever increasing pressure and pleasure. His hands molded over the contours of her back, her waist, and around to gently, but firmly caress her breasts.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina shivered slightly and murmured another soft, “Yes.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She clung to him as if some unknown force were trying to rip him away from her arms. This was the kind of devouring passion she wanted from him and she gloried in the way it made her heart thunder in her chest even as her head became dizzy. She took in the tension and urgency in his embrace and welcomed it, returned it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Always, when she was in his arms, she came alive. Yet, all too soon his hands stilled, his kisses turned to short, parting pecks.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He lifted his head and looked at her with moisture from his lips on hers, passion from her caresses still blazing in his eyes. “You have a decision to make,” he whispered on a deep, aching gasp.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her breaths were labored and as short as his. An ache filled her chest and squeezed her abdomen.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do we continue this upstairs or go for a ride?” she managed to ask past a thick throat.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Inhaling deeply, he shook his head. “Whether you will release me from the promise of no women.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">No women?</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina stiffened. She wasn’t sure she believed what she heard him say. “You mean you are still going to hold me to that knowing we both want to be together right now in the privacy of my home?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He bent his head again and placed his cool lips to the base of her throat and trailed soft, moist kisses all the way up to her lips where he gave her a few more sweet kisses before looking into her eyes and whispering, “You’re the one I want. I’m trying to win your hand in marriage, Brina. Not just the afternoon in your bed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was no reason for it to, but his bluntness stung. She fought back a stab of his rejection. She had invited him upstairs and he was declining. Pushing out of his arms she stepped away and huffed a breath of exasperation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That is a terrible thing to say to me,” she said, tugging on the waistband of her dress.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It was respectful and true,” he argued with no anger in his expression.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How dare you make no distinction between a paid woman—a mistress, and a lady.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He leaned in close to her. His gaze felt like a brush of velvet across her cheek. It was tantalizing. “I know the difference, Brina. You know that, too. It is you who must make the distinction. I will abide by your answer.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her chest heaved. Drat the man. He was right. She hadn’t made anything clear when she said 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">no women</i>
      . At the time, she didn’t even know she was going to say it, much less try to qualify it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No bets are off between us, my lord,” she issued firmly. “Our bargain stands as is. You best get busy if you are going to have more than half of those finished by the time I am ready to ride.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina turned and headed for the stairs. She didn’t mind the soft rumble of a masculine chuckle that drifted from behind her. The more she was around the earl, the more she liked him—no, no. It was more than mere like she felt for the earl. She liked several men, including Mr. Inwood.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wanted Lord Blacknight in the most primal way.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She never expected that to happen.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It made her vulnerable. It had made deeper feelings for him to grow and fill her with longing. She’d known she would have to endure his courtship when she made her bargain with him. What she hadn’t expected was that she would find herself looking forward to it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Why had she ever agreed to his terms?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And why hadn’t the rake taken a drink or picked up a deck? His willpower was far exceeding her expectations. She never expected him to last this long.</p>
  </body>
</topic>