<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_18" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 16</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 16</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A light mist of rain dusted the top of Zane’s hat and crest of his shoulders as he walked down the street toward The Brass Bull Gaming House in the early evening hour. Foot traffic was sparse because of the turn in the weather but a steady stream of carriages rolled past him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane chose to walk to his meeting with Harry. It gave him more time to think about Brina. It wasn’t just having her in his arms, at her own volition that had caused him to suffer unfulfilled passion that was still with him days later. It was that she’d wanted him just as strongly and urgently as he had wanted her. She had been so tantalizing he had to satisfy her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But then he also had to deny her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He sensed the passion simmering beneath the prim exterior of her widow’s clothing long before she had initiated the kiss in the carriage, but he hadn’t expected her to act on it—being a proper lady. They were both hungry to fulfill their frantic need for each other and would have if she hadn’t put those bloody damned and hellish restrictions on him. He shook his head in frustration as dampness sprinkled his neck.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina had been right. Inappropriate, vile curse words had become a habit for him—even in his thoughts.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded to a gentleman he passed and then hunkered deeper into his cloak to keep the wet chill off the back of his collar. Whether or not he made the right decision to call a halt to what was about to happen between them in the carriage that afternoon still troubled him. His body would argue that he hadn’t, but his mind disagreed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sometimes.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And sometimes he sensed that his heart was weighing in on the matter, too. Which was troubling. Those thoughts he tried to stay away from. It was one thing to want her only for himself. As his bride and countess. Loving her, possibly being in love with her was an entirely different matter and one he shied away from considering. A feeling such as love wasn’t for gamblers like him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina could never imagine the amount of willpower it had taken for him to set aside his desire for her. Every ounce he’d had, and then some.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The truth of it was that she’d left him no choice but to say no to what they both wanted. He didn’t know if he could trust her not to use his being with a woman, even if it was her, against him at the last ball of the Season when he proposed to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her vow to remain a widow was clear. He couldn’t take her vow to herself lightly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her premise from the beginning was that she expected him to fail. And he’d come close a few days ago—which was why he was mostly staying away from her unless it was at a party—with other people watching them. That way, he was less likely to succumb to her desire to be with him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane now knew, more than the day he’d made the wager for her hand, that he wanted her. All he had to do was stay firm on those promises and she would be his. He’d made it over two weeks and could make it the rest of the time. His worry was, could he change 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">her</i>
      mind before he made it to the last ball of the Season?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was still so much to know about her. Why had she been dressed in the pink satin gown in Paris? Did she harbor deep lasting feelings for her husband as people claimed or was she, knowingly or not, using the perception as a protective guard against giving her heart to anyone? He wanted to know what had made her decide she never wanted to marry again. He needed to know more about her past to find answers.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Going without a glass of fine wine or a lively card game, difficult as it was, had been easy compared to staying away from her. He had relived the sensations of his lips against hers, the fulness of her soft breast beneath his hand, and her sweet, whispered feminine sounds of pleasure for endless hours. At times, he thought he might storm over to her house and insist she remove her demands from him so he could make her his.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But, after a fierce battle with himself he’d come to his senses, pushed the treasured memories aside, and continued his studies to learn about the vast properties that were now under his command.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He also hoped the gossip about them would settle down now that he hadn’t been seen with her for a couple of days. News traveled amazingly fast in the elite ton. By the time he’d made it to Middlecastle’s house for dinner after their adventurous carriage ride, it was obvious everyone there had already heard he was seen driving the curricle recklessly through the city’s streets with Brina onboard. A hush had fallen over the drawing room when he entered, and everyone looked at him as if he’d suddenly grown two sharp thorny horns.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Some of the ladies quickly turned their heads away in protest that he had the gall to attend a dignified event after such ill-bred, dangerous and careless behavior. Others gave him sly smiles of approval. Some merely looked surprised. None more so than his hostess, the Duchess of Middlecastle. It was only much later in the evening he discovered why Her Grace had gone running from the room at the sight of him. It had nothing to do with the race to dodge the spy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina had been adequately protected all evening by her friends, Lady Lyonwood and Mrs. Stockton, and so it seemed the duke and duchess as well. They had been cordial when they spoke to each other but there was no opportunity to have a conversation about the event and the gossip surrounding it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When l dinner was served and they went into dining room, he’d been seated on the opposite side from Brina and so far down the long, dimly lit table he hadn’t been able to get more than a glimpse of her for over three hours.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As he’d expected the chairs were small, the seating tight, and the china, crystal, and silver abundant. So was the wine but he didn’t have a sip. Not one to grouse about anything for too long, Zane found a way to enjoy the evening by engaging in a lengthy conversation about Paris with the young widow, Mrs. Pinewiffle, who was seated on his left, and a chatty young lady making her debut into Society to his right. After only two glasses of wine she was spilling the reason why the duchess seemed so unhappy with him. Zane had failed to respond to her invitation that he would be attending. His lack of manners had caused her to delay dinner while the servants rushed to set a place for him at the table.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The fact that Brina was already planning such a long evening for him to host was still an idea he was having to get used to. He’d much rather sit around a card table. Gentlemen were always given plenty of room when gaming. No elbows or knees ever touched. You never had to wonder which glass was yours. However, if a long sit-down dinner would make her happy, he’d endure it. But she would damn well be sitting next to him and not at the other end of the table.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The mist had turned to a drizzle, Zane noticed as he tipped his hat to a couple scurrying along as he passed them. He pulled his cloak tighter about his neck and kept walking. So did the man who’d been following him. When Zane decided to walk, he expected the man in the cabriolet to simply follow at a safe distance, but he’d jumped out of the carriage and was following Zane on foot.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane wanted to court Brina the usual way a gentleman would pursue a widow. Candlelit dinners in her home. A friendly game of cards, or chess. Smiles over a glass of wine, gentle touching of hands, and delicate kisses to start a night that would end in searing passion in her bedchamber.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Thoughts of that possibility kept him warm until he opened the door to The Brass Bull Gaming House and strode inside. The smell of liquor was strong. His stomach clinched. He had missed having a drink in the evenings. It was harder than he thought it would be not to pour himself a splash of brandy by habit when he was alone. By the third night without a drink, he’d considered having Fulton take every drop of claret and brandy out of the house so he wouldn’t accidently have a drink before he remembered e promising Brina he would stay away from it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Until she was his, and he would.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Even if it killed him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina Feld was a wicked woman to have trapped him into such a pact. But she was wonderfully wicked. Beautiful and enticing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The hell of it was that he missed late-night and all night card games, too, but was getting used to going to bed earlier, waking earlier and going for a ride in the park while the day was still quiet, and before Uncle Syl and Uncle Hector arrived for their daily hovering sessions with his solicitor.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After the brisk walk in the cool rain, he would have liked to settle around a table by the fire with a glass of claret or a sip of brandy to warm him before enjoying a game or two of cards. But he would do neither this night. He pushed the thoughts from his mind and hung his cloak on one of the pegs near the door.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Huffing a rueful breath, he popped his hat on top of his cloak. According to his uncles, none of the scandal sheets had been kind the past couple of days. Being called the Hellion Earl didn’t matter to him but it had Hector in an uproar and Sylvester desperate to calm his brother. Zane was close to telling his uncles he’d learned all he could about the earldom from them. It was time for them to get back to whatever normal lives they had before they decided to make themselves a daily fixture at his house.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">What bothered Zane most was that one of the gossip sheets had slighted Brina by suggesting she’d been a willing participant in their wild ride. Which she was. An encourager, in fact, but he hadn’t liked what was written about her in the column—
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Mrs. Feld appeared to be enjoying the ride and draped herself over the earl’s shoulders as the carriage sped wildly down the road.</i>
      Zane was fair game. Maligning her wasn’t. It was no surprise at all that not one of the scandal sheets mentioned he and Brina were being chased by someone driving just as fast.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The taproom was dim and noisy with chatter as he scanned it. Laughter and the solid clunk of tankards hitting wooden tables echoed around the room, but Zane heard a man from a nearby table whisper, “Can I buy you a drink, my lord?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“In two weeks, three days, and seventeen hours,” he quipped and kept on walking as the person chuckled. He didn’t mind the remark or laughter that followed as he threaded his way around the tables. He had no idea how many weeks, days or hours until the bargain with Brina was at an end, but it couldn’t come soon enough. Until then, only one thing mattered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That she not win.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Very ungentlemanly of him, but necessary.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I heard that was a mighty fine race you had a couple of days ago,” a young bearded man said in a normal tone as Zane passed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave the man a nod.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Another stranger from behind him called out, “Did you win the wager when you won the race?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No bet,” he answered with good humor. “No race. Just an enjoyable afternoon ride.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry waved to him from a far corner table. Zane headed that way. He’d been enough of a scoundrel in his days not to let the ones in the taproom, nor the one who had followed him to the club to bother him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was close to ten years now that Harry Robins and Zane had been friends, having met at a gaming hell shortly after they were both old enough to enter. Their skills, looks, age, natures, and even allowances were equal but not their social status. Zane’s father was a gentleman. Harry’s, a wealthy tradesman.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Ordinarily, the two lifestyles would never meet and surely not mix, but it hadn’t kept them from becoming friends and often gaming partners—until an unfortunate event abruptly ended Harry’s card playing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">While walking home late one night, Harry had come upon a man being robbed by thugs. Good fellow that he was, Harry stopped to help. One of the robbers had a long sharp blade and almost sliced Harry’s palm in two. A surgeon stitched him up and saved the hand, but it was of little use to him. He couldn’t shuffle a deck, make a fist or even hold one card. He had his hand but no movement or feelings in his thumb and fingers.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry hadn’t let that stop his gaming. He just no longer played the game himself. He still haunted the gaming hells and found ways to wager with dice and other men’s high stakes games. It was a common pastime for some.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How are you, my lord?” he said, rising and offering a bow.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded. “Managing.” He pulled out a chair and sat down. “How about you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Managing quite well,” Harry said, with a congenial smirk, before adding, “I was sorry about what happened to your family.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you. Most everyone’s recovered from the shock.” A server walked over, and Zane pointed to his friend’s glass of red wine. “Want another?” he asked his friend. Harry shook his head, so Zane motioned the man away.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was winning his battle over his desire to have a drink and play cards in the evenings and he would win the battle for Brina’s hand. It seemed as if everything in his life was changing. He knew it would be a struggle to adjust to being earl of the estate and head of his family. All he had to do was win one battle at a time.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was glad to hear you’d come by to see me. I had good intentions of getting in touch earlier.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry shrugged. “I knew you would eventually. You’ve had quite a lot to happen recently—wagers and titles. Tell me, how does it feel being an earl?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Different, and the same. I still put on my clothing the same way every morning but learning to accept people I’ve known all my life or for years, like you, bowing and calling me my lord.” He shook his head. “That, I’m still adjusting to.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry snorted a good-natured laugh. “I bet that has caused you some consternation. I’m surprised you still want to be seen with me. It was quite clear your uncles didn’t want me hanging around when I went to your house.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My uncles mean well—but live by old rules and traditions they aren’t likely to give up.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I would assume they didn’t appreciate your terrorizing the Town with your out-of-control curricle a couple of days ago.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Out of control? You bloody—” Zane caught himself and smiled. “Englishman.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry chuckled. “That’s the nicest name you’ve ever called me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I promise not to make a habit of it. And you know, I am always in control of the horses. My uncles didn’t mind the speeding carriage so much. They were livid I had Mrs. Feld with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His friend chuckled again, clearly enjoying the fact he had riled Zane. “Was she frightened?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not at all.” Thoughts of Brina always distracted him. He took a moment to remember the exhilaration in her eyes and eagerness in her kiss. No matter what he was doing or who he was talking to, he always felt as if she was with him. “She loved every minute of it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His friend eyed him skeptically. “That’s surprising considering—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry stopped midsentence but Zane knew what he was going to say. Her enjoying the fast ride was surprising because of Brina’s reputation as the perfect widowed lady, the example every lady who had lost her husband should follow. He didn’t mind people thinking of her that way. He had, too. Now, he knew there was another side to her as well.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Deciding to ignore what he considered Harry’s comment was going to be, he said, “I wanted to meet with you tonight because I need your help.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry leaned forward, and in a low voice asked, “Does it have anything to do with the man who walked in shortly after you did and hasn’t taken his eyes off your back since you sat down?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.” Zane felt a twist between his shoulder blades and his gut tightened. He looked around the room. “Every time I leave the house someone follows me. I assume hoping to catch me take a drink, gamble, or visit a mistress. I’m sure they are thugs being paid by whomever has wagered the most money. If I stopped one spy, another would simply appear in his place, so I don’t bother to confront them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“There are probably many men following you and watching the clubs. Every pair of eyes in here lit up when you entered the room. The amounts being entered in books all over Town is astounding everyone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Blast it—I never dreamed one little wager would turn into such madness.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Maybe because it wasn’t little.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Seemed so at the time,” he mumbled. “I only wanted to get 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">her</i>
      attention. Not notice from every gamester in England.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But that has happened now. You are being watched. What do you need me to do?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was hoping you’d ask. I may have mentioned my cousin, Robert to you before.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry shook his head and leaned further back into his chair as he moved his wine glass closer. “You have too many cousins for me to remember the names of any of them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was true so Zane nodded. “He’s a young man thinking he wants to be a skilled gamester, but, he’s still a greenhorn, impulsive, and easily led. Apparently now, all the affections he used to have for women has turned to cards.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry shrugged amiably and took a drink from his glass before saying, “He’ll come back around to where he realized he can handle both.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane blew out a derisive laugh. “The problem is he doesn’t want to take the time, as you and I did at his age, to study, learn and get good at the games.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Young men today have no patience or discipline for the finer details of card playing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Right,” Zane agreed. “I have reason to suspect he may be getting into debt with someone or a card club. Maybe more than one.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You think it’s possible that some of the men are duping him and using him to plump their pockets?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Precisely,” Zane said, and looked around the room again. “He’s a good fellow but maybe with more swagger than he can back up. As you well know, there are a few men who like to make their living off a younger man’s pockets. Until he learns to control his gaming limits. He’s come to me twice for money since he’s been home. That causes me worry.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Is he giving you any details?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No and I try to be careful. I appreciate a young man needing his privacy. He wouldn’t like it if he knew I was checking on him. I hope you can make some discreet inquiries for me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“An easy enough request. Do you have names?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not that I can confirm. Only suspicions right now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Your instincts are always good.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane hoped they didn’t fail him this time. “Robert’s spending a lot of time with a man his age who seems to have enough money to stay in the games, Harper Tabor. I haven’t been around him often. He seems innocent enough, but I feel something isn’t right. He doesn’t have the attitude or style of an accomplished gamester.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You think he might be a decoy to lure Robert into debt?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For Brina’s sake he hoped that wasn’t the case, but to Harry, he said, “Very possible.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve not heard Tabor’s name mentioned in any of the clubs, nor a word about your cousin.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Tabor could be one of the greenhorns being duped himself. He’s young, too. I don’t want Robert getting in deeper than he should. I need to know if he’s borrowing money to gamble from anyone else and who he might owe.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The amount can’t be huge. You know word like that gets around fast.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s why I’m asking now. If there are debts I want to settle them before they get out of hand.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you have any other details?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Robert mentioned a man named Remick who was having a series of games and he didn’t have the blunt to get in.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry shook his head. “Never heard his name, but games and clubs come and go so frequently.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded. “I could be wrong and both Tabor and Remick are square with Robert and they are all having friendly games every evening to improve his skills. I want to make sure before I leave him to stand on his own.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ll ask around and be in touch when there’s something to report.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The favor will be returned whenever you ask.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry straightened in his chair and picked up his glass of red wine and sipped. “You can grant me that favor right now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Tell me what you want.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I want to hear about the widow who convinced you to give up wine, cards, and women.”</p>
  </body>
</topic>