<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_22" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 20</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 20</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sitting in the back of a well-polished landau on plush comfortable seats with the top down and being driven by a liveried driver was the proper way for a gentleman to take a lady on an afternoon ride through the park, Brina thought.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It would also be quite boring if not for the fact the dashing Earl of Blacknight was seated beside her. He made all the difference in how she felt.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The reason most everyone in the ton remained in their best clothing and took to the parks on a sunny Sunday afternoon during the Season was so they could see and be seen by others. The weather hadn’t disappointed Londoners today. The sun was midway down the western sky with only a stray trace of white clouds breaking across the moderate shade of blue. Warm air didn’t have a hint of breeze to stir it around making the day pleasant. Cloaks, capes, and coats had come off in favor of lightweight clothing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina held a pale gray parasol edged with a darker shade of braided ribbon to match her dress and pelisse. Zane wore a black hat and dark brown coat and trousers. The buttons on his dark-red quilted waistcoat were covered in the same fabric. Well-matched horses and expensive wheels allowed the carriage to move along the road at a smooth and gentle pace.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">If not for Zane, Brina would have much rather be back at her house rolling bandages for the sisters which was her usual Sunday afternoon project. However, she had agreed to such outings as this was part of her bargain with the earl to show his family he had settled down, graciously accepted his place in Society and was ready to be a respectable member of the ton.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Much to her surprise and dismay, he was doing a splendid job. An even greater surprise was that she looked forward to it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It also vexed her that time was passing quickly and she hadn’t heard one hint of gossip that Zane might have broken any part of their bargain. No one had come forward to say he’d uttered so much as a swear—let alone an obscene one. He’d come close with her. But not close enough for him to surrender and agree she’d won. Some oft used words of exclamation just couldn’t be considered obscene. Too many people said them or variations of them. She often said merciful heavens or drat which a few people would say are variations of hellfire and damnation. Both words were in the Bible for goodness sake! How could she insist they were obscene?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His strength troubled her, impressed her and drew her. Drew her with such fearless abandonment it would be so easy to give in to it and not even struggle. His sense of character was stronger than she’d suspected, than she was led to believe by all the gossips who said he cared nothing for his family or the responsibility of earl that had fallen to him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And she couldn’t forget Paris.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She truly never thought he’d last one night without a pair of aces in his hands, let alone over three or four weeks. What was she to do? Go back on her word and not marry him? That seemed almost as dreadful as marrying him. There was the comment he said the other day in her house. 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">I bet you. </i>
      Though she was in a mind to let it slide at the time, she hadn’t forgotten it. Slip of the tongue, well-used turn of phrase, or whatever he chose to call it, he couldn’t deny he said those three little words and offered her a wager. An arrow in her quiver if he didn’t start drinking or gambling soon.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not only did she have to consider all that, she also had to reflect on the fact she enjoyed being with him. He made her laugh but he’d never laughed at her. He desired her but hadn’t taken advantage of her advances. How could she not appreciate a man who surprised her with a horse to ride? All these things had somehow helped her come to care for him. How deeply she didn’t know yet. Hadn’t wanted to know. Which, of course left her emotions in turmoil.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">So, what would she do if he somehow managed to refrain from all the gentleman’s vices she’d asked of him, and really expected her to marry him?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You seem deep in thought, Mrs. Feld,” the earl said as they crossed the busy street and headed onto the path that would put them in St. James Park.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do I?” she asked, grateful he couldn’t read her mind and hoping her cheeks weren’t coloring as she answered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded. “You seem troubled. Are you not enjoying our proper afternoon ride?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked over at him and smiled. “Very much.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Really?” He gave her a half grin and moved more into the corner of the landau and turned his body so he could face her directly, without having to continue turning his head. “Are you not missing the horses, yet?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, and I’m upset you know that I am,” she teased. While the thought of a neighborhood and park she’s seen a thousand times might be boring, the man she was with was not. She missed sitting atop a horse and guiding the animal where she wanted it to go. It made her feel more a part of her surroundings and not just someone who was looking at them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Tell me,” she said, “are we being followed by anyone today?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m followed every time I leave my house. I have adapted much in the same way I am getting used to having a butler, a solicitor, and my uncles arriving every day to go over yet more documents, account books, contracts, and requests for my help.” A chuckle reverberated softly in his throat. “Don’t ask our driver to lose the cabriolet shadowing us today. He’s not capable and neither are the mares.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She gave Zane a confident smile. “I wouldn’t. I trust no one but you to handle a team of horses so expertly.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m waiting for the day you will trust me with other, more important matters.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His gaze swept over her face making her feel she could believe him even though she didn’t know specifically what he was referring to. It still made her want to believe him. He was winning her over with his unpredictable, mostly slight ungentlemanly behavior at times. He’d never been crass or rude to her or anyone else when he was with her. Well, perhaps he was rude when he hadn’t responded to the duchess’ dinner to let the lady know he would be attending. Now he was reluctantly, but graciously making amends for that with a party of his own.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I do wish I could do something a little scandalous today,” he said. “Everyone we’re passing seems stiff and in need of a reason to relax and enjoy the afternoon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina laughed, too. There was something enchanting about him saying that. But everything about him seemed to be enticing her. She tried to ignore the feeling by saying, “You have done enough for a lifetime.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shook his head and his brow creased. “I was just thinking how I’d like to reach over and kiss you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her breaths became rapid at the thought, but it would be madness. So instead of encouraging him, which she would have liked to do, she asked, “Is your book of poetry in your pocket? Reading it should curb your restless state.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He patted down the front of his coat and then looked around his booted feet. “How did I get away without it? It’s been my constant companion since you gave it to me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina laughed. “I don’t believe you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes twinkled with mischief. “Nor should you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You probably don’t even know where it is?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He leaned toward her once again, giving her a gentle smile. “Not true, I would never misplace something you gave me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The way he looked at her meant he knew exactly where the book was and that made her want to kiss him even more. But not now. Later. When they were alone. She would.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They fell silent as the driver maneuvered the horses and carriage to fall in line behind a queue of conveyances waiting to enter the congested traffic already in the park. While they waited Brina listened to chatter from people in nearby carriages, the jingle and rattle of harnesses, and snorts from the horses as they hustled by pulling their load. Recent rains had turned buds into leaves on the trees and shrubs. Flowers had been planted at the entrance and many of the blooms had opened. Scattered patches of green grass flowed into brown patches of ground still dormant from the winter and made a patch work of the area.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Which reminds me,” she said, changing the subject before either one of them acted on what they were both feeling. “Do you have any questions about your upcoming dinner?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“None. I’ll find a way to get through it. Patricia and my uncles are excited. They think your idea for me to host the evening was superb. They keep asking Fulton questions and he continues to assure them his staff knows how to do it all from the previous earl and everything is in order and under control. It should be a perfect dinner party for us.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Us?” she questioned. “Why do you say that? I sent over the menu, guest list and seating arrangements for Fulton but the evening is for you alone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he said huskily, reaching over to let his hand rub down her arm. “It’s for us. For our future. Together.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Thoughts of the future made her heart race again. As a lover, yes. Yes, she’d be willing to find a way to make that happened. She looked away from him, and on a grassy area not far away she saw people standing and waving. “Isn’t that your Uncle Hector and his wife waving to you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, and Uncle Syl with them.” Zane paid them no mind. “It seems I can’t go anywhere without seeing them these days.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She turned back to him and smiled. “We should go over and speak to them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he said unequivocally.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His short answer and clipped tone irritated her. “It’s the polite thing to do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s torture. I spent part of the morning with them. That was more than enough for today.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You can’t just ignore them,” she insisted. “They are motioning for us to drive over and say hello. Look, they have refreshments and will probably ask us to join them for a while. This is something you need to do. Something you wanted to do. Learn how to make your family feel you care about them and that what is important to them is important to you. Furthermore, I can’t help you be polite and proper if you don’t allow me to help you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane rose up in the seat, looked their way and gave them a long, hearty wave. He then turned back to Brina, smiled engagingly, settled back into the cushion in a much too casual manner for being in public, and said, “After our ride through the park,” Zane offered as they started up a small rise, “I told the driver to take us down to the abbey. We’ll stop there and take a stroll to look at the buildings you wanted to see in that area. “I’ve wanted to do it before now, but decided I’d rather take a closer look at the area with you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh,” she said, touched by his words. Just when he was ignoring his family and she was thinking him irredeemable, he surprised her with his kindness. “You remembered I wanted to do that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes swept over her face. He leaned in toward her again. “I recall everything about you, Brina. I remember how you taste, how you feel in my arms. At night in my dreams I hear your sighs. When I wake your scent surrounds me like a garden of sweet-smelling flowers. I am never without thoughts of you and that makes you always with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His voice was husky and persuasive and delighted every one of her senses. His gaze was so penetrating it was as if Brina was living every word he said. She remembered all those things about him, too. As surely as he was sitting beside her, he wanted to kiss her right now.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It didn’t matter there were other people walking near their carriage, riding on horseback, and wagons and carts passing by, moving along in front, or trailing behind them. That very real, stimulating attraction was always between them. She moved to reach over and slip her hand into his, press her lips on his, but thankfully the carriage wheel hit a bump in the ground and they were jostled. The moment to touch and kiss was lost.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You are being bad, my lord,” she said in a voice that was only half teasing. Sometimes he made her feel so good she wondered if she might wake up to find him a dream.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If you only knew how desperately I wanted to take you in my arms right now, you would know that I am actually being very good.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She believed him and that was why she changed the subject to one that she’d been debating even mentioning to him today. “Have you seen Robert or had word from him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No one has seen him,” Zane responded. “Uncle Hector had a terse note saying he was with a friend and there was no need to worry about him. He’d return in a few days.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Hmm,” she said, thoughtfully. It was good to know that Harper had kept his word about having Robert alert his family. Surely that was good and should ease some of her suspicions all was not as Harper had told it. But it didn’t.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane looked at her as if he were giving himself time to digest her words. “Why did you say that?” he asked. “And do that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do what?” she asked in all seriousness.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Frown.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t?” she rebutted.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His bright, delicious blue eyes locked on hers. “You know you did and what does hmm mean?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Meeting his unwavering stare, she quirked her head a little and asked, “What does it mean when you say it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That I’m unsure of the meaning of what the person has either asked me or answered me. And 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">that</i>
      usually concerns me, Brina. So what do you know about Robert that I don’t know?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well, of course I have no idea. Why don’t you tell me what you know.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He smiled and as if without thinking reached over and ran his gloved hand down her cheek before drawing it away. “Gentlemen allow ladies to go first.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She watched him as closely as he watched her. Their cat-and-mouse game had returned. “I defer to you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right. Because of Robert’s recent unusual behavior I’ve asked a friend to see if he has gambling debts.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The anxiety she’d had about Harper returned full force. “That sounds like a good idea.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m also checking on the man named Remick. Robert and Harper have mentioned him. He may be hustling our cousins to join a club so he can get them into debt with him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina hoped that wasn’t true. Harper had a generous allowance but it wasn’t bottomless.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why would he want them in a club if they were indebted to him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So they will eventually harass their families for more money.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s an absolutely wretched thing for a man to do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But it happens more often than you would think. Now, what do you know?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Unsure of how much to say for fear of betraying Harper, she offered, “I saw Harper two or three days ago and asked about Robert.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina, I need to know everything he said?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She stared at him a long time. Zane was being so honest with her she supposed she needed to tell him what she knew even though it would mean betraying Harper and ruining her relationship with him should he ever find out. It wasn’t an easy decision to make. But if Zane could help Harper how could she stay silent?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Robert is staying with him right now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her a disbelieving look. “You knew this days ago and you are just now seeing fit to tell me?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Harper said he would see to it Robert let his family know he was fine now and with a friend and obviously he did.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait,” Zane kept his tone soft, but leaned in close to her. “What did you mean by he is fine 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">now</i>
      ?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She swallowed hard and remained silent. She didn’t want to jeopardize her relationship with Harper or Zane over this. She lifted her shoulders a little while staring into the distance, listening to the sounds of the carriage and the horses clopping along. She had to weigh betraying Harper against possibly helping him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You are giving me cause to worry, Brina. I suddenly have the feeling you are not telling me truth.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am,” she said, taking umbrage at his words.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Then perhaps it’s just you aren’t telling me all of it. Why is it so hard for you to you trust me?” he asked, sharply.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Even if I don’t tell you everything I know, it doesn’t make what I do say less true.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He avert his gaze and muttered something so low she couldn’t hear it but was certain it was an obscene curse word.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When he looked back at her, anger shone in his eyes. “I need to know everything. I’m trying to help my cousin.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And I am trying to help mine,” she said just as hotly, folding her hands tightly across her chest. “And the truth is, my lord, I don’t think Robert is a very good influence on Harper. He had no problems until he started gaming with Robert, and I wish they weren’t friends.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Is that so?” He gave a short derisive laugh and looked directly at her again. “It just so happens I have been thinking the exact thing about Harper. That he is the one leading Robert astray.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” She exclaimed more loudly than she should and leaned in close to him. They stared at each other, equal in passion about their cousins. “I have you know that Harper is a gentleman and has never done anything wrong in his life. He’s only recently started gambling, sir—since spending all his time with Robert who was obviously taught everything he knows by you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His grimace hardened as he moved his face closer to hers. “If you know what kind of trouble my cousin is in, tell me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His anger proved an equal amount in her so she remained silent. Fuming.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Fine,” he retorted and leaned back in the seat with bounce. “I’ll talk to Harper?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Heavens, no!” She reached over and placed her hand on his upper arm as if to keep him from immediately leaving the carriage. “You mustn’t do that. Ever. Harper would never trust me with anything again. Promise me you won’t mention this to Harper or Robert and I’ll tell you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His expression softened. “All right, but tell me everything you know.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane listened attentively as Brina relayed her last conversation with Harper to him. “So it seemed suspicious a young man would fall and injury himself so badly—but it could be true. Except a few weeks Harper had showed signs of bruising. I’m worried he is gaming at a hall where ruffians play.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s what I’m thinking.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina closed her eyes for a moment and shook her head. That is not what she wanted to hear him say. “What can we do about it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shook his head decisively. “There is no we in this, Brina. I am already looking into a man named Remick and what Robert’s indebtedness might be to him or others.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Zane, you must promise me you won’t go to Harper’s to talk to Robert?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her a conciliatory smile. “I might get angry with you from time to time but I won’t go back on my word to you. You should know that by now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes, to her determent, she was learning just how seriously he took giving his word.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Besides, if Robert is he’s staying out of sight while his bruises heal, for now he’s safe. That gives me time to find out what’s going on.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If Harper is any trouble, will you tell me?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes swept down her face and lingered on her lips. “Of course, I will.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you. I’d want to—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My lord, Mrs. Feld, how are you on this lovely afternoon?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina looked over to the carriage that had driven up beside them to see Zane’s uncle, Mr. Sylvester Browning and his brother and his wife.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She heard Zane mutter another oath.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After a lengthy ride through the park with more than a few nods, waves, and calls of greeting to people they knew, the earl’s carriage rolled to a stop in front of the abbey. The large stone building, with its plain wooden door stood out like a stalwart beacon among all the smaller buildings surrounding it. There was nothing notable about it other than its size. A small sign out front read The Sisters of Pilwillow Crossings. The good work that went on inside for the poor made it a formidable and a majestic place to Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane hopped out and reached to help her down onto the pavement. “This isn’t a part of London I’m familiar with,” he offered as he looked around the street.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I wonder why? No gaming hells nearby?” she offered with a smile, knowing it wasn’t a busy section of London for shoppers or other many businesses.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If you keep teasing me in such an attractive manner, Brina I’m going to have to go against my better judgment, that of my uncles, and the entirety of my family and the ton and kiss you right here on the street.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You wouldn’t.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He took a step forward and reached for her. She whirled away and laughed. “You must behave, my lord or you’ll have it where neither of us are welcomed in Society again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His gaze swept seductively up and down her face. “There will be no promises about that from me on this afternoon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Deciding it was best to leave that subject alone, Brina cleared her throat, pointed, and said, “The sisters set up tables and give out the food there in front of the main entrance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The building is bigger than I thought it was. How many women live there?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know for sure. I never asked. Probably thirty.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are all of them nuns?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. Maybe half. In this abbey, you don’t have to take the vows of the church and join the order to unite with them. Everyone is to follow all their rules. Remaining chaste, participating in prayers, and performing whatever duties you’re assigned without grumblings or rancor. Otherwise, they would be dismissed from sisterhood.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Sounds reasonable,” he commented.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When she showed Zane where the tea and bandages she’d prepared were handed out, Brina noticed the now familiar cabriolet had stopped in front of a building not far behind them. The driver looked the same; standard black top hat and hunkered down in a black cloak. Though he’d never been close enough she could see his face. It angered her the man continued to follow Zane. He had no right to watch the earl’s every move. She supposed it was a testament to his willpower that he hadn’t flattened the man.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For a few moments she thought about grabbing Zane’s hand and racing down the street, ducking between buildings with him much in the way she had imagined racing through underground tunnels when they were in the chateau in Paris. But she then remembered how upset everyone was about the curricle ride and she pushed the exciting thought of escaping with the earl aside.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There were only a few other people on the street so Brina started walking and Zane fell in beside her. Three men walked ahead of them and a couple strolled leisurely on the opposite side of the street. The road was free of traffic, except when the cabriolet rolled slowly behind them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“This building behind the abbey that we’re going to look at, have you checked to see if it was for sale?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she said confidently as they continued to walk. “It’s not currently available.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Perhaps I could put in a good word—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, thank you, my lord,” she said looking over at him pointedly. “This is my project for the sisters, and I will handle it myself in due time. I’m in no hurry. Besides, Sister Francine 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">is</i>
      the type of person who will need to be gently coaxed into seeing that the sisters could make use of a separate chapel for the abbey. Their wants and needs are few and simple, but their service and hearts are pure. I only want to—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">From the corner of her eye, a splash of color caught Brina’s attention. She glanced at the window she was passing. There, displayed in the seamstress shop, was a gown almost the exact shade of the pink costume she wore to the masquerade ball.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her heart skipped a beat.</p>
  </body>
</topic>