<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_16" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 14</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 14</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The force of her weight knocked Zane back into the corner of the carriage, lifting his feet off the floorboard, though he seemed not to notice. In one swift motion, his legs spread and he caught her between his thighs with a primitive groan. He accepted her hard, eager, and commanding kiss. With ease, his hands slid under her cape, circled her back, and pulled her close, pressing her breasts against the firmness of his powerful chest as if he were trying to bind her to him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They clung together; his lips as hungry as hers. Neither able to get enough. His tongue probed deeply into her mouth over and over again. Their breaths came in ragged little gasps of infinite pleasure.-</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mmm,” he whispered against her lips. “I needed to touch and kiss you like this.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Heart-throbbing impatience filled her with an eagerness she couldn’t ever remember feeling before.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why did you make me wait so long?” she asked between deep searching kisses.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The rumble of his chuckle thrilled her. “I was only waiting for you to let me know you were ready.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina leaned her weight onto him when he ran his hands down the sides of her body. Cupping her hips, he shifted his body to fit her softness against his hardness. Her womanhood clinched deliciously. Immense pleasure filled her, and she had no desire to stop what was happening between them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wanted to enjoy every moment of it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her fingers curled into the fabric of his waistcoat before relaxing and brazenly skimming down the front of his trousers. A breathy satisfying moan left his throat. Knowing her provocative caresses caused his body to tighten and tremble with need, she touched him again and again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Their intense, ravenous kisses didn’t slow. Neither did their searching caresses. Brina wasn’t sure she understood the explosion spirals of sensation shooting through her at alarming speed. These were new to her but wondrous. She couldn’t deny herself the exquisite vibrations that had taken control of her senses, her body, and her mind. The ecstasy of what she knew was about to happen between them was shaking her to the core.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It couldn’t come fast enough.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s lips left hers and he kissed over her jaw and down the length of her neck. Carefully he gently pulled on the neckline of her dress and it easily fell off on her shoulder. Her head fell back, and he kissed the small rise of her breast while his hand caressed and fondled it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They shared every gasp, every moan, and every breath that passed from their lips as they kissed long, deep, and savoring. It pleased her to feel him tremble beneath her searching hands. His arms tightened around her possessively as they teased, tasted and enjoyed this time of being alone with each other.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The thrills that swept through her were shattering all remembered thoughts of how kisses and caresses in the past had made her feel. Surely if she’d ever experienced this kind of earthly, raw, and heated desire she would have remembered it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The pressure of their kisses and touches became harder, deeper, and longer. She pressed her lower body against his, wanting more of him. Zane answered by reaching down and gathering her skirts, pulling them up to her thigh. Her knee came up, knocking her bonnet and his gloves off the seat. With natural ease, his hand slid beneath the soft cotton of her underclothes and his palm outlined the shape of her hips, buttocks and thighs as they kissed and kissed and kissed again. When his hand moved over to her most womanly part, shivers and sensations of exquisite pleasure soared through her as his light touch pleased her swiftly all the way to a climax.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A whispered moan, a breathy “Yes,” escaped past her lips as her body fell weak and satisfied against his. She buried her face into his hot, pulsating neck, unable to move.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane let go of her dress and caught the back of her head in his hand. His breaths came deep and hard as hers though she knew he had not finished what they had started, even though she had. She looked down into his eyes, her heartbeat still beating franticly as she stared at him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Breathless. Stunned. And more than a little confused that he had not carried through. Her whole being cried out for him to make their union complete.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t ever think I don’t want you,” he whispered huskily, and then winced as he shifted his weight beneath her, proving his words to be true.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Raising her head, Brina swallowed hard. She’d wanted him, too. Completely. Not just this brief act of consolation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What happened?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes focused intimately on hers. “I intend to make you mine, but the first time I make love to you it won’t be in a carriage behind a tree.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wanted him. Didn’t he realize how distinct it made him? She hadn’t even looked at a man with desire in over five years. He was the first she’d ever considered for a lover. Her skin tingled and she shivered slightly. All of a sudden he was the one being sensible and she the reckless one.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">she stared down into each of his dark, fathomless blue eyes. Neither blinked, nor retreated from the issue between them. “There won’t be many times we can be totally alone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I want you too much to do this now,” he said earnestly, gripping her shoulders tightly to hold her against him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her heart continued to pound in her ears. Her pulse continued to beat in her chest. It wasn’t an ideal situation. A carriage, but they could manage.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why?” she asked from a thick throat.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He reached up and brushed kisses across her bare shoulder, up her neck to her lips for a deeper, longer kiss. Ripples of pleasure danced inside her and fed the hunger that hadn’t been satisfied. She hadn’t had enough of him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He pulled back from her but kept his gaze on her face. “If I am to make you mine for all time, I must not make you mine today. We have a bargain. Tempting though it is right now, I’m not going to break our pact.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina suddenly realized what he was saying.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">No women.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But that didn’t mean her. Did it? No, not her!</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She struggled with what was between them as she continued to seek clarification from him. She supposed it did mean her. He was taking her at her word.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Why do you all of a sudden have scruples?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His brow and around his eyes wrinkled with concern. “I’m fighting for you,” he answered earnestly. “I told you I always play to win.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But she didn’t want him to win. Yes, she wanted him for a lover. But as a husband? Her heart started beating faster again. No, no. She couldn’t go down that road again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve never been so thoroughly seduced by anyone as I have by you,” he whispered. “You are an inviting mix of a proper, innocent lady and a sinfully tantalizing woman.” He gave her a faint smile. “And I want both. I was unbelievably tempted to disregard my promise to you. I was only one more kiss away from giving in to your desire for more and my yearning to make you mine. You must believe that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes, she did. She didn’t like it, and it shocked her. She averted her eyes and pushed at his chest. His hands tightened on her arms as if he didn’t intend to let her escape his hold. He looked as if he started to say more but fell silent. Softening his grip, he slowly let go.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Pulling at her dress and cape, she straightened in the seat and moved away from him. She shouldn’t be upset with him, but she was. It didn’t matter that he was only following 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">her</i>
      dictates. Rules she never expected him to take to heart and actually follow. Demands she never expected to haunt her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yet, she had no one to blame but herself. Now she had to be levelheaded and get over it. He wanted marriage. She only wanted him for a time.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They were in each other’s lives for the duration of the Season. For now, she had to leave it at that and hope he hurried to the nearest gaming house to have a drink and a game of cards. She certainly wasn’t going to marry him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She couldn’t marry anyone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Ever.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know what happened to me,” she said straightening her clothing. “I’ve never been so free before I—I guess it was the thrill of the ride that caused me to lose myself to the point I lost all rational thought.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It was your desire for me that had you mindless of all else,” he said with a teasing grin as he picked up her bonnet from where it had fallen and handed it to her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What? No, no,” she argued, half irritated and half amused by his assertion as he laid her gloves in her lap. “You’re a horrible person to insinuate that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m truthful. I fully admit you have seduced me like no other woman, but you won’t admit I make you feel the same way.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was right. It was hard enough admitting it to herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She placed the bonnet on her head and stuffed strands of hair underneath it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are you upset with me?” he asked, tightening his collar and neckcloth.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course I am,” she said in a light-hearted tone. She was pleased to that he had—well, what he had done for her. “You ruined a perfectly good ending to an exceptional ride.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He chuckled, pulled the brake handle and gave the horses a gentle nudge to start moving. The harness rattled once more, and the curricle lurched as they moved out from under the tree’s branches.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What party are you attending tonight?” he asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The Duke of Middlecastle’s dinner,” she answered, tying the ribbons of her hat under her chin. “He and Lyon are good friends. The duke is always at Lyon’s card club—anyway, I know him fairly well and I’m going with Adeline and Lyon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You know Lyon invited me to join his club,” he said offhandedly, keeping his eyes straight ahead.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. I shouldn’t have, but I jumped to conclusions and accused Adeline of asking him to do it so he could keep an eye on you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane whipped his head around to look at her. “Did she?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Brina answered. “She assured me it was issued because of your reputation as a card player in London. I believe her and she forgave me. Apparently, many gentlemen are clamoring to play with you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Seeming satisfied with her answer, he gave his attention back to the horses. “I told Lyon if he has an opening after the Season, I’d be happy to join.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am not opposed to you joining right now,” she said with a hint of delivery in her tone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane chuckled. “Your wishes will not persuade me to go back on my word to you. I wasn’t going to attend Middlecastle’s dinner, but if you’re going, I will. Seated in a very small, uncomfortable chair, squeezed elbow-to-elbow at a table for a dinner that can last three hours is a form of torture.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I just had an idea,” Brina said, before the plan had developed fully in her mind. “I think you should give a sit-down dinner party.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No.” He shook his head. “At my uncles’ insistence, I had one for my family shortly after I returned. I want it to be a long time before I have another.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Family dinners are easy.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So my uncles said, but there is nothing easy about my family and the things they want. More allowance, trips to America, land. Their requests seem endless.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You must decide about those things, but you say you want me to help you do things that are proper. A dinner party where you invite people such as the Duke of Middlecastle, the Earl of Lyonwood and other peers who are in Town would be good for you. It will have to be toward the end of the Season as most evening dates are already filled for everyone, but I think we can fit one into everyone’s schedules. I don’t know why I didn’t think of it before. It will please your family for you to have a grand dinner for such important guests and prove to other members of the peerage that you are serious about your place in Society. Mainly that you want to get to know them and are willing to work with them should they need you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He grimaced. “They should know that anyway.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Some people need to be told.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He flashed her a grin. “You sound as if you’re getting excited about this idea of a dinner party.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Somewhat, I am. It would be enjoyable to plan a party. I haven’t had reason to in a very long time. Living with my parents in their home gave me very little to do. My mother is talented, efficient and neither needs or wants help. Besides, I promised to facilitate your transition into the world of London Society, the peerage and help ease your family’s concerns. I’ll start planning it for you. With your permission, of course. Perhaps your sister will agree to act as your hostess.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’d rather you do it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She frowned.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, wait,” he quickly said. “Don’t say anything. I already know. It wouldn’t be the proper thing to do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They laughed as he guided the horses back onto the trail that led to the main road.</p>
  </body>
</topic>