<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_24" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 22</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 22</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane shut the ledger and pushed back his chair. “I think that settles it, Uncles.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Settles what?” Hector asked from his seat across the massive oak desk.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Your tutelage. I have now been through every account book, looked over every contract, and been briefed on every tenant. I know where every piece of property is located, the size of it and approximate value, and the type of land it is; grazing, waste, fertile or inhabited. I will continue to seek your guidance in the future when needed but for now, I see no reason for you two to make daily visits.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Uncle Syl shifted in his chair and sniffed. Uncle Hector tapped his cane once on the floor as they looked at each other for a considerable amount of time. Surely they had known this time was coming, but clearly not that it would be today.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Finally, Hector’s chin bobbed. “What about the family?” he asked. “Many requests have been made of you that you haven’t addressed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s true. I have delayed that until my review of everything was finished.” There were so many different family members asking for favors of different magnitudes he didn’t remember them all. “I admit this is a way the two of you can continue to help me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hector glanced over at Sylvester and they both smiled, thinking that would continue their routine of counsel to him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Put together a list for me of all the people and requests that have been made so far. In fact, make me a list of all my relatives and what relation they are to me. Are they second or third cousin—niece, aunt, or you know what I mean? All of them. My mother’s family as well. I’ll set aside a time to meet with you and go over everyone’s requests.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That wasn’t what they wanted to hear.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Hector’s brows grew closer together by the second. “I’m not sure I know the names of all of them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Neither do I,” Uncle Syl said, looking puzzled by the thought of what Zane suggested. “You know how it is. Cousins, nieces and nephews get married and have children which makes you have more cousins, nieces and nephews. How far down the family tree do you want us to go?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“As far as you like. I’ll leave that decision to the two of you. I would also like a recommendation from you as to the merits of their requests.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Sylvester was the first to give in. He bowed from his lower back toward Zane. “We’ll get it done. Your great Aunt Imogene will probably know everyone in the family.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. Leave it to us.” Hector moved his cane around and placed it between his knees, resting both his palms on the handle and leaned forward. “But we were hoping we might continue in our assistance of you until after you are wed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane tensed. “I appreciate that you want to but for the reasons I indicated, it seems unnecessary. Besides, I don’t know when I will wed.” Or if he would wed. He still wasn’t certain he could trust Brina to fulfill her part of their bargain even though he’d followed to the letter the rules she laid down—well, except for a swear or two. And then there was that troubling mistake he’d made in her dining room when he’d mentioned making a bet with her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But you have Mrs. Feld’s assurance she will wed you after the last ball,” Uncle Syl said. “Have you done something to keep her from accepting your proposal? Something we don’t know about?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he said firmly. And he didn’t intend to. “I’ll propose to her per our agreement. That is all I have to say about it. You have taught me well. It’s time I take over on my own going forward.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane saw Fulton step into the doorway. “Yes, Fulton.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mr. Robbins is here to see you, my lord. He says it’s about your previous discussion with him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Show him to the drawing room and tell him I’ll be right there.” Zane rose. “Uncles, I have more things to take care of. I’ll see you back here tomorrow 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">night</i>
      for dinner.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Hector said, relying on his cane to help him rise. “And with parliament ending its session a week early, the last ball of the Season was moved up to the night after.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What? I have it on my schedule as still almost a week away.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It was until late yesterday. The ball committee moved it up. You know how it is, once Parliament ends its session everyone is ready to escape Town and head to their summer homes and begin their house parties.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That didn’t give him much time. He needed the extra days to win her love.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Love?</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That was such a big little word!</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But yes, he not only wanted to win her hand, he wanted her love. She was loyal and tender-hearted. There was no doubt she loved her family, her friends, the sisters and the girls at the school. He’d wanted her to love him, too. He didn’t want her holding back any part of herself from him. She was attracted to him. She enjoyed the way he made her feel. What he didn’t know was why she still continued to proclaim she wanted to be a widow.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That remained a mystery. If she had loved her husband so much that she’d pined after him for years why wouldn’t she want to find that kind of love and happiness again?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He looked at his uncles. “I’ll make sure it’s on my calendar. I don’t intend to miss. I’ll let Fulton get your coats and see you out.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane strode into the drawing room and joined Harry, who stood near the far wall looking up at a large tapestry depicting a battle scene. “Good of you to come, Harry.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry turned to look at Zane, a quizzical expression narrowed his eyes and pursed his lips. “So, when you became the earl, this house and everything in it became yours? Is that right?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Nodding, Zane stopped beside him. “It all becomes part of the entailed property of whoever is the earl. It can’t be sold. It can only be passed down to the next man to inherit the title.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry chuckled. “That’s a good way to keep it all in the family. Just declare it can’t be sold.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane smiled, too. “I hope you finally have some news.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Some,” he said. “Not as much as I’d like. I don’t know if it will help you very much.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Anything is more than I know.” Zane heard his uncles coming down the corridor. He pointed to chairs by the far window. “Let’s sit over there. Can I get you something to drink? A port or brandy?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he said, settling himself into one of the wide-striped blue and beige covered chairs. “I’ve asked around on Remick. He’s from America and he’s been in London about three months. He purports to have various business ventures there—but no one seems to know exactly what the businesses are. But, he always has plenty of money to play so no one really cares.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Understandable. As long as he pays as he plays.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The odd thing about what I’ve heard is that he does most of his playing at the smaller gambling houses—Hillspot, York and Petly’s, Buck and Doe’s. Places like that. His bets are in line with most everyone’s there and he seldom loses. He goes to gaming houses such as The Brass Bull and when he’s there, his bets are large, and he usually wins.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Cheating?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not that anyone has ever accused him,” Harry said. “Just damn good like you are. But it’s like he’s two different men. One night he’s at The Brass Bull betting hundreds of pounds and the next he’s at the Hillspot where bets are limited to five pounds. The same places your cousin and Mr. Harper Tabor are playing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So, he makes money off the small bets where players aren’t as good and then plays with the skilled players?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s what I’m thinking. And the rumor is he’s starting his own club to teach younger players how to become skilled.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And they have to pay in order to get in these clubs?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry nodded. “There’s one other interesting bit of information you might find useful. I heard Mr. Remick asked if he might be a guest at Lord Lyonwood’s card club and he was refused. Now that you are an earl, too you might want to ask Lord Lyonwood what he knows about the man.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, I believe I will ask Lyon.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harry shook his head. “Imagine an American wanting a seat at the earl’s table?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded as he looked over at the clock. It was almost five. Rather late in the afternoon to call on someone. Brina wouldn’t approve, but he didn’t want to wait until tomorrow to talk to Lyon. Besides, Lyon lived right beside Brina. Why pass up an opportunity to see her?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">By the time Zane saw Harry out and had his landau brought around half an hour had passed. His carriage stopped in front of Lyon’s house alongside four other carriages, including the Duke of Middleton’s and the Duke of Marksworth, Lyon’s father. That’s when Zane remembered it was Lyon’s card club day. He wasn’t one to interrupt a man’s game. He didn’t know how long they played but he’d wait.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With Brina.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He stepped out onto the pavement and sent his driver away, not knowing how long he might have to wait. As he started toward Brina’s house, he heard talking coming from the back of her house. After he passed the tall hedge that separated her house from Lyon’s, he saw the top of Brina’s head. He walked about halfway down the side of her house and looked over the garden wall. She wasn’t alone. There looked to be a dozen girls with her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane huffed a silent laugh at them. They wore what looked to be men’s long-sleeved shirts over the top of their dresses. Easels were in front of them, paint brushes were in their hands. Brina stood in front of them talking. He moved in closer so he could hear.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A good painting of a flower begins with a well-drawn flower. You will see, I’ve already drawn the flower for you to make your first lesson easy. We are going to start with the stem. I want all of you to dip your paint brush into the green paint. Don’t look at your partner or her work. You are only interested in your drawing. Pretend you have the entire easel to yourself and not just half of it. What the other girls are doing or how they are doing it should not affect what you do. After you have paint on your brush make slow easy strokes like this.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane continued to watch her. The way her hands moved and her shoulders rolled as she colored in the stem of her flower. Her voice remained calm as she continued to instruct. She would make a few strokes and turn back to her students and explain something else before placing her brush on the canvas again. The girls were quiet and attentive as they watched her and made the same strokes.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After her stem was finished, Brina put her brush down and walked over and looked at their paintings. The girls asked questions and she answered, seeming to make suggestions. He was mesmerized watching how unruffled she was with them and how much they seemed to enjoy her, sometimes all of them talking at the same time and vying for her attention by gathering around her. She would quiet them and sent them back to their easels.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane relaxed and folded his arms across comfortably over his chest. He could watch her all day. She was a good and patient teacher. She would be a good and patient mother. To his children. Their children. He didn’t just want to marry her, he didn’t want to live without her. He loved everything about her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And it was a damn good feeling.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He didn’t know how long he watched her, but he finally heard talking from Lyon’s house and the sound of carriages leaving. He would have to see her after his visit with Lyon.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After the last carriage rolled away, Zane knocked on the door.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Lord Blacknight to see Lord Lyonwood if he’s available,”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait here, my lord,” the butler said, and moments later Lyon came walking down the corridor and motioned for Zane to come.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Blacknight,” Lyon called. “Come join us. Garrett’s with me. We’re having a drink.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane’s stomach twisted and one of his hands made a tight fist of frustration. He would love a drink right now. “Nothing for me,” he mumbled to himself and headed toward Lyon. The men shook hands and once inside the book room Zane greeted Garrett as well.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Sit down,” Lyon offered pointing to a chair.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you. I won’t stay that long. I know it’s after hours. I wanted to ask you about a man named Remick. I heard he wanted to play with your club and was wondering if you could tell me anything about the man.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Lyon scoffed. “The American? No, I can’t tell you much about him. He</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">asked to see me, so out of courtesy, I met with him. Apparently, he’s a skilled player and wanted an opportunity to play with my group.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But you didn’t agree.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course not. It’s not that men like him aren’t good. They usually are a good challenge. But if I allowed one man to play with us it would get around and others would want to test our skills, too. Best not to start. I’m sure you know that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane nodded. He’d met every kind of card player there was.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s the same with race horses,” Garrett offered. “Men take them from town to town wanting to test their horse against yours.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He had nothing to lose by asking,” Zane said, picking up the conversation again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t mind him asking once, but I didn’t like it when he waited for me outside White’s and asked the second time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That didn’t set well with you. Did you find out anything about him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. Does he want to play you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane smiled. “I think everyone in London knows I’m not playing right now. I’m asking about him because of my cousin. Remick appears to have started a private club. I have reason to believe my cousin might be involved with him or his club, and I just want to make sure the man plays fair and not out to line his pockets with a young man’s wealthy family.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I had no reason to ask about him any questions. I wasn’t interested. If I’d known I would have been happy to.” He looked at Garrett. “You’ve met him, Garrett. What do you think of him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I agree with all you said. He’s obviously good and knows it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane looked Garrett directly in his eyes and asked, “You’ve gambled all over the world. Do you think he’s a master gamester and out to get a young and impulsive young man’s blunt?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Garrett weighed his words before saying. “Something about him doesn’t add up. Most skilled players are trustworthy. They probably wouldn’t stay alive very long if they weren’t. Usually the most important thing for them is the bragging rights. Money is secondary and only to feed their habit. However, I wouldn’t trust an American who’s come to London to set up a card club.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nor do I,” Zane said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After a few more minutes of discussing Remick, Zane left Lyonwood’s house. Dusk had settled. Lights were showing in houses up and down the street. It was early evening. A highly inappropriate time to pay call on a lady. Proper gentlemen would wait until tomorrow, send over a note and wait for a reply.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane has always known the rules for a gentleman.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But he had always preferred just being a man.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He rapped the doorknocker once and took off his hat while he waited. When the housekeeper opened the door, he said, “Good evening, Mrs. Lawton.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My lord,” she said with a proper greeting.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If Mrs. Feld is home, I’d like to see her. I have some important news for her.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The housekeeper looked behind him as if to make sure no one else was with him before saying, “She’s just finished her evening meal. I’ll have to ask her. Come inside to wait while I ask.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane walked in behind the woman and place his hat on the side table. When she turned and started down the corridor, so did he.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Quietly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">As he neared the double doors leading into the dining room, he saw Brina pushed back from the table. In one hand, she held a glass of red wine and in the other a book. She was so beautiful a longing quiver started in his loins. She’d been reading while having her dinner. A silver branch with five lit candles flickered near the book. Her lush blonde hair fell long and enticingly around her shoulders.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She had no idea how lovely she was sitting there or what it did to him to look at her so beautiful and serene. His breaths quickened and he swallowed slowly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mrs. Feld, the—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Earl is here,” he said, stepping from behind the housekeeper.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Startled, Brina looked up. “My lord, what are you doing here at this hour?” She placed the book and glass on the table.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Obviously the wrong thing. Arriving early in the evening, interrupting your dinner. Behaving badly as usual.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” she answered, almost whispering as she rose from her chair. “It’s all right. I’m finished.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I wanted to see you.” No, it was more than that. He wanted to hold her in his arms for as long as he wanted. He wanted to kiss her until he was breathless. Until she was sighing with pleasure.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We’ll go into the drawing room so Mrs. Lawton can finish in here.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Please bring your wine with you.” He gave her a wiry smile. “Just because I can’t drink doesn’t mean you can’t.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina gave him a lopsided grin. “I’m finished with that, too.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He walked beside her down the dimly-lit corridor all the while thinking what he wanted to do was take her in his arms, shove her against the wall and well . . . That’s not the reason he came over. He had every intention of telling her what he’d discovered about Remick and what he thought Robert and Harper had gotten themselves involved in. Right now, he had no desire to visit that subject right now. Their cousins’ problems were fading from his mind. He wanted only to think about Brina. What he felt when he looked at her. How he felt when he touched her. Tonight he wanted her to know just how much he wanted her and he wasn’t going to give a damn about anything else.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane knew how dangerous it was to bet everything he had on one game. He would caution anyone about being so foolish. You always left something to play again. But tonight, he wasn’t going to. He was going to bet it all.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They walked into the drawing room. The draperies were still open and the still room was shadowed in early evening twilight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ll light the lamps,” she said. “Sometimes, I go straight upstairs after dinner and never come into—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait,” he said, taking hold of her hand when she reached to turn up the wick. In the darkness she turned toward him and stepped into his arms.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Their lips met softly, brushing lightly back and forth in delicate, feathery, motions that were meant to stir and entice. The kisses stayed that way until Brina’s arms wound around his neck and she pressed her lower body against his.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane was lost to the hunger he had for her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His kisses turned fervent and deep. With eager hands he felt the shape of her slender, womanly body. He tasted the warmth of her mouth, teasing her with his tongue. Her lips were sweet with wine. His hands pressed firmly into her buttocks to hold her tighter against him. She gasped and he groaned as they both fed on the desire that swept through them like fire through dry grass.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina matched his yearning. Her fingers dug into the fabric of his coat. His lips left hers and he kissed his way down her neck and quickly back up to her lips again as her hands moved down his back to cup his bottom and press him closer.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He lifted his head. The only light came from the corridor but Zane saw was as crazy passionate for him as he was for her. He’d seen and felt her love for him as she held the kitten. He’d knew he loved her. Now he wanted to show her. With the last ball moved up, he had run out of time.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was dangerous. She could use this night against him but he had faith it was time for him to 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">trust</i>
      her with his love, time to 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">trust</i>
      himself and put all his cards on the table.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I love you, Brina. I don’t want any wagers or bargains between us. Just me and you. Let’s go to your room,” he whispered huskily.</p>
  </body>
</topic>