<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_25" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 23</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 23</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina didn’t know how they got up to her room. Did they walk? Run? Did he carry her? It didn’t matter. It was bathed in moonlight and they were completely alone for the first time.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She had been attracted to Zane and wanted him to make love to her almost since he’d come to London but he had rightly denied her. Now was the right time. All through their brief courtship he’d surprised her, teased her and made her laugh. He knew how to listen to her innermost feelings without passing judgement and she had slowly fallen in love with him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Once they were locked inside her room it seemed their lips never parted. At times their kisses were short and fierce and sometimes they were long and passionate. Still, at other times his lips caressed their way over her cheek, down her chin, and along the column of her neck, causing shivers of delight to cover her before searing her lips with his once more.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They tumbled onto the bed, giving no care for their clothing, shoes, the bedcovers, or the pillows. Those things were easily disposed of as they kissed and touched and explored each other’s body. It was frantic but loving. He covered one nipple with his mouth and the other breast with his hand as she opened herself to him and he took her for his own. She held his head to her breasts and moaned with sweet, satisfying pleasure.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt his love for her and she gave her love to him. Wave after wave of intense pleasure crashed through her as his mouth left her breast and he kissed her chest, the hollow of her throat, and the crook of her neck. Her hands gloried in the feel of his warm flesh beneath her hands.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He whispered her name over and over again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She felt and accepted the pent-up desire he had for her and gave it back to him with full measure. At times, their passion was fierce, driving, and desperate, but always loving. His hands tangled in her hair and her hands raked over his shoulders, back and down his slim hips as their bodies joined in a fierce coming together that left her with an earth-shattering explosion of sensation and his body shuddering.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They were breathless, happy, and sated.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Even though Brina already had some knowledge of loving from her brief marriage, she’d never felt the all-consuming sensual world Zane had introduced her to. Every kiss, every touch, every breath he drew showed her he wanted her. No one else. And that made her love him all the more.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Moments later Zane lifted his weight from her and rolled over. When he pulled her into the circle of his arms Brina suddenly felt like crying. Their coming together had been so passionate, so complete that she knew the depth of her love for Stewart had been only a young girl’s flight of fancy with her first beau.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Tears suddenly flooded her eyes. Stewart had loved her but never with such fierce passion, never making her feel as if she was the only woman he had ever wanted. As if she was the only one who could make him feel complete.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Memories tore through her mind, tears flooded her eyes, aching flooded her heart. And now, after all these years, she’d given up her undying love for Stewart and replaced it with unyielding, undying love for Zane.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And it hurt so bad.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Guilt crushed down on her and she rose up in the bed and whispered, “I hated him. I hated—” Her voice broke on a sob before she managed to say, “Stewart.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane rose up beside her, placing his arm lightly around her shoulder. “What? Brina, no. You couldn’t have hated him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s true,” she whispered as tears fell from her eyes.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her an incredulous stare. “You loved him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, I loved him, but I hated him for saving all those people.” She clutched at the sheet covering her chest over her heart as a rush of intense shame filled her. “I hated him for that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He tried to pull her close to him but she brushed him away his arm, revulsion for having to admit that tearing at her soul. “I’ve told you I’m not good. I’m not a good person, an angel. I hated my husband for putting all those people above me and saving them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t say that,” Zane whispered softly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s true and you might as well know it.” Another sob fell past her lips. “Why didn’t he save himself and come home to me? Yes, I hated everyone on them for taking him away from me. They were all alive and going on with their lives and my husband was dead. I was so selfish. I hated him when Stewart was anything but selfish. That makes me a horrible person.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She choked back a sob but the next one she couldn’t hold inside. Nor the next. Suddenly she was wrapped in Zane’s strong arms, her face pressed into his naked chest and she was crying her heart out.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He held her close, rubbed her back, kissed the top of her head and all she could do was cry.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When her tears and sniffling subsided, Zane took hold of her shoulders and forced her to face him. “You’re not a bad person for feeling that way. I’d bloody well be furious, too.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You would?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Anyone would be. There’s no greater sorrow than the bone-shuddering loss of a loved one. All your feelings are understandable.” He reached and pulled the sheet around her shoulders. “You’re not selfish, Brina. At nineteen your soul had been shattered. You were sad and hurting.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But I hated him for a time. I hated all of them and I have such scorching regret I ever thought such things as wishing they’d never been saved.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know,” he whispered softly, drying her face with his hand. “You were human. That’s all.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve tried so hard every day to make up for those terrible feelings. I want to help everyone, hoping I can in some way make atonement for all those revolting things I thought for a time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“First,” he said and lifted her chin with his fingertips. He gave her a smile. “You don’t have to work off feelings you had while mourning. No one expects that of anyone. But even if you did, believe me with all that you have done for the sisters, the girls, and everyone else in Town—you have more than made up for any bad feelings you had. Brina, you shouldn’t carry guilt for emotions that are natural, and even expected when a loved one dies.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mine were excessively so. I know that. I felt so much anguish I thought I might be losing my mind. My parents were worried and wouldn’t allow me to be alone.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He kissed her forehead softly. “But you didn’t.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She shook her head and swallowed hard.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What happened to help you get over the hurt?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Meeting Julia and Adeline and their idea for the school to help girls whose family members died with ours. Suddenly there was someone who needed something from me as Stewart had helped those who needed him. Stewart was gone but I was alive and could continue his example by helping others. The school gave me the opportunity to not think about myself or my loss, but to think about what I could do for others.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane reached over and tenderly kissed her forehead. “You are a person who feels emotions deeply. That’s why you were so deeply wounded. It takes time for wounds like that to heal.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s why I never want to marry again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, Brina,” he whispered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I never want the possibility of feeling that intense anger at someone I love. I never want to bear the guilt again for hating someone I never met. Loving is too hard and brings out the worst in me. I don’t want to ever be that way again. That’s why I didn’t want to love you. And that’s why I can’t marry you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait,” he brushed her hair again and softly kissed her lips. “You don’t want to love me, but you do?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. I do love you, but I don’t want to marry you because I don’t want to lose you. I know I couldn’t bear it again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane smiled and kissed her softly on the lips. He then held her close and breathed in long and deep. “Let’s start with you loving me as I love you. Just love me, Brina. That’s all I’m asking for. We’ll get to marriage tomorrow or the next day, or next month. All I want to hear you say right now is that you love me. All the rest will come later.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I do love you, and—” he placed his fingerstips over her lips.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. Don’t say anymore. Not tonight. Let’s have this time together with just the two of us. Loving each other. No past for either of us. No guilt, no bargains. Not even tomorrow. Just us tonight.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And just us,” she whispered as her lips claimed his.</p>
  </body>
</topic>