<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_14" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 12</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 12</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina decided to forgo bonnet and cape since the school was only a short distance away. The midday sun was shining down and that, along with her simple long-sleeved, dark-gray dress, warmed her aplenty for no longer than she planned to be out of the house.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She walked out the back door, down the steps and into the small portion of garden that separated her house from a three-story building that used to be a servants’ quarters. There was no intricate lattice work or fancy outside moldings on it. Only a plain sign over the door that read The Seafarer’s School for Girls. A few paces later, she came to the tall yew hedge that served as a boundary on both sides of the house. In the middle of the shrubbery was a vine-covered trellis that had been built so the servants could easily come and go from the main house. The archway now served as entrance to grounds of the school.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Finding such a perfect property had been a dream come true for Brina, Adeline, and Julia four years ago. Situated in the middle of a privately secluded cul-de-sac near the business district of St. James made it valuable. After hearing what they wanted to do, the owner had made it affordable. Now that Brina lived on the grounds, she was convinced they couldn’t have found a better place in all of London.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The school started with nine girls. All from families that had lost either a father or brother who worked on the 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Salty Dove</i>
      . It had taken time for their solicitor to track down eligible girls and explain what the widows wanted to do for them. Persuading their relatives to allow them to come live at a boarding school and be taught to read and write as well as the seamstress trade hadn’t been as easy as Brina thought it would be. Boarding schools for girls were rare. Free ones almost nonexistent.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Another child had been added the first year. Little Nora. At only five, she was younger than the other children. Brina, Adeline, and Julia knew they had no choice but to take her into the school. Her mother abandoned her there shortly after the school opened.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Nora was the illegitimate child of Adeline’s first husband. There had been several attempts to find the girl’s mother but no leads to her whereabouts had been discovered. Their hope was that one day the mother’s circumstances would change and she would come back for her child. In the meantime, her daughter was being well-cared for, educated, and would one day be earning her own way in life as a skilled seamstress.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina knocked on the door of the school and opened it, calling, “Hello,” as she entered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The ten girls immediately pushed back their chairs from the long rectangular table and rose. So did Mrs. Tallon and her two helpers.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good afternoon,” Brina said, walking into the large, square room with enough windows to let in plenty of light. “I hope I’m not interrupting anything too important.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not at all, Mrs. Feld,” the head mistress said with her usual pinched expression. “Your presence is never a disturbance for us. We welcome you anytime. Say hello, girls.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good afternoon, Mrs. Feld. How are you today?” they asked, all speaking in perfect time together.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina beamed as the chorus of greetings echoed from around the room. Fanny, one of the oldest students was always easy to spot with her long, vibrant red hair. Recently, she’d learned how to somewhat tame her unruly curly locks by pulling half of them up and away from her face, tying them at the back of her head with a ribbon. Fanny wasn’t tall, but she made up for height in her personality. Unlike the other girls, she was never shy around Brina, always lifting her hand and waving as she said hello. Brina acknowledged her with a slight nod.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m good,” she answered the girls. “Thank you for asking. I don’t know if you’ve been outside today, but the sun has chased away the cold wind and the weather has warmed considerably again.” They looked at Brina but said nothing, so she added, “I enjoyed hearing you sing this morning. Your voices were pure and enchanting. Angelic. I thought I was listening to a choir in a cathedral.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Ahhs and gasps of surprise sounded around the room. The girls looked at each other and smiled. Brina was glad her compliment pleased them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We’ve continued to work on the flowers you brought us, Mrs. Feld,” Fanny said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s wonderful to hear,” Brina said, moving a little closer to the table. “I’ll send over some more. One can never have too many flowers to study.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I drew a beautiful snowdrop yesterday,” the tall and thin Mathilda said in an eager voice.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did you? How lovely.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I drew one, too,” one of the other students chimed in cheerfully. “Mine was bigger.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But it wasn’t as pretty as mine,” another girl said.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, it was,” Fanny remarked tartly, taking up for her taller, crest-fallen friend. “Yours didn’t have any leaves on the stem.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We were told to draw a flower, not leaves,” she remarked right back to Fanny, jerking her hands to her waist and sticking out her tongue when she finished.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I drew a garden of flowers this morning and everyone said mine was the best,” Mathilda injected excitedly, seeming not to want to be outdone by any of the other students.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s because no one else drew flowers,” one girl added with a high-pitched giggle at the end of her sentence.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Suddenly, in the space of a few seconds, all the girls were talking at once and Brina couldn’t hear one over the other. She hadn’t realized how competitive they were.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Girls,” Mrs. Tallon called above their loud, excited chatter. “You can all sit back down now and go back to your work.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Quietness quickly settled over the room, except for the sounds of chair legs scraping across the wooden floor.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The head mistress walked over to Brina. The skin around her eyes and forehead had tightened though her lips formed a smile. “Was there something in particular I could help you with today, Mrs. Feld?” She spoke in a hushed tone. “If so, perhaps we can discuss it outside so as not to hinder the students any longer.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Tallon was never disrespectful but Brina felt as if she was never happy for her to come over to visit her or the girls. She had once suggested it might be better if she sent a note over and ask Mrs. Tallon to visit her. Brina didn’t want to do that. She enjoyed seeing the girls, looking at their happy faces and hearing their voices.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She supposed she could understand why Mrs. Tallon thought she was interrupting their studies, but Brina didn’t want to stop no matter if Mrs. Tallon wished otherwise. Besides, children needed a break from their studies once in a while. And everyone loved unexpected surprises if they were good ones.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Brina answered in the same soft tones. “I wanted you to know that with Lady Lyonwood and Mrs. Stockton’s approval, I will soon be giving the girls painting lessons. Probably on Sunday afternoons. I’m not sure of all the details yet.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Tallon’s smile faded rather quickly. “Painting?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina remained undaunted. “Yes. My plan is to stop reading to them as I realize many are now reading quite well on their own. So, I won’t be disrupting them any more than usual or taking any more time from their studies and sewing preparations. The painting will be in place of the reading.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, of course, Mrs. Feld. I do thank you for that consideration. As I stated when I came to work at the school, I believe in discipline, decisiveness and dedication to the art of sewing. If you feel the art of painting will help them achieve my objectives to make them valuable to the community one day, I will yield the time to you for painting lessons.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank you.” Brina felt that went easier than she expected until she realized the head mistress wasn’t finished.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Tallon’s lips widened but there was no pleasure in her smile. “However, I do feel if we find that some of the girls are not inclined to do well with a paintbrush, as many don’t, we allow them to do something else. Just as we’ve discovered some are better with cutting the fabric and others with the needle, and still others with tying ribbon into a bow and making a shapely rosette.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I understand, Mrs. Tallon and think that is a reasonable request. I’ll be happy to do that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mrs. Tallon’s eyes slowly returned to normal and her expression softened a smidgen.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thank, you,” Brina said, knowing she should let Mrs. Tallon make decisions like that. She was the head mistress. “I’ll be in touch. Don’t hesitate to let me know if you need anything.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After saying good-bye to everyone Brina stepped outside, closed the door and leaned against it, wondering if it was natural to want to help the girls have a more fulfilled life. Was it natural for her to want them to need her for something? Plenty of other ladies in Society successfully lived as widows and seemed perfectly happy without needing the satisfaction she received from being with and helping the girls and the sisters.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina took in a deep breath. She didn’t know what she would do if she couldn’t help the girls in some way. Perhaps she would go visit the sisters at Pilwillow Crossings and take the bandages she rolled last night. It always seemed to cheer her to talk with them. Surely they couldn’t get too many to give out to the unfortunate who depended on the abbey’s help.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Feeling unsettled by the prospects of not being actually needed by anyone, she lifted the hem of her skirt and started down the three steps. As she made it to the bottom, she heard a squeak of metal and looked over at her side gate. An sudden rush of expectancy tightened in her chest.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Blacknight was entering her back garden. But just as quickly, she wondered why. He should be going to her front door if he wanted to see her. Did he think he could break every rule of Society?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes, he did.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For today, she didn’t mind. Just seeing him lifted her spirits and made her forget she was feeling unwanted by anyone. She welcomed this unexpected 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">good</i>
      surprise.</p>
  </body>
</topic>