<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_29" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Epilogue</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Epilogue</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The September sky was bluer than Brina could ever remember seeing it. A faint hint of autumn stirred in the late afternoon air as she and Zane rode their horses. The grass, leaves on the trees, bushes and undergrowth were just beginning to show signs of cooler days ahead.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For Brina everything looked brighter, fresher, and newer since she and Zane had married. After their nuptials they’d made the long trek up to Northcumberland to visit with her parents. They couldn’t have been happier that she’d married an earl, though she knew it would take her mother a bit of time to get used the fact the earl was the once notorious black sheep of the Blacknight family. Her mother would adjust.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Harper was doing well and Zane suggested he not be in any hurry to return to London. Surprisingly Harper agreed. After a visit there, they had journeyed down to Dorset to see Robert. He was doing well, too and had changed his affections once again to a lady, having decided they were safer than cards.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Both young men had sworn off gambling. Whether or not it would be forever only time would tell. They seemed to have put their scare with the crimp behind them and neither were in a hurry to return to their previous life.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After their wedding journey, Zane had joined Lyon’s card club and seemed perfectly happy playing only once a week, except for a friendly game at the occasional summer garden party Londoners enjoyed. Brina had assured him she wouldn’t mind if he wanted to go to White’s for a game or two during the week. He insisted he’d much rather have his brandy sitting with her in front of the fire in the evenings than furthering skills he no longer needed to use.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His life was full with her, his duties as the earl, and his family. His uncles continued to offer their help and Zane was always kind when he declined. Brina continued her work for the sisters and the girl’s school. The painting lessons weren’t going as smoothly as she’d hoped, but she was determined not to give up. If just one girl showed a natural talent for the art, it would be worth the trouble.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What are you thinking about?” Zane asked as he halted his horse and folded his hand over the pummel.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina reined in her mount, too and looked at Zane with all the love she was feeling. She thought about asking him to remove his hat. She loved to see his windblown hair and the sun’s rays shining on it. But, of course, it was proper he keep his hat on until they were seated to have their refreshments. She was so blessed to have him love her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was thinking about you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He chuckled. “Good. I was thinking about you, too.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Were you?” she asked teasingly. “Thinking about me doing what?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Racing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She quirked her head and narrowed her eyes. She liked that idea. “If you wanted to race the curricle’s again why are we on horseback?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shook his head. “Not curricles this time. Horses. You are seasoned now. Your horse against mine.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She rather liked that idea. “Do you mean it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course. You are doing so well, I was thinking it’s time we had a short race. Longer when you are more comfortable. But for today if I win—I get to take you to bed as soon as we get home.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her breaths increased at the thought he was suggesting. The racing and the prize. “And what do I get if I win?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You get to take me to bed as soon as we get home.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She gave him a completely unserious frown. “You are impossible, Zane Browning.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He laughed, but said, “I’m serious. You’ve been riding again for several months now. I think you can handle yourself.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Hmm,” she said, really liking his idea. “A lady and a gentleman are not supposed to race horses in the park.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He grinned affectionately. “I know, but are you game?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Ha!” she said in good humor. “I think I can handle myself, the horse, and you, my lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Prove it. To the tree?” He pointed. “I’ll let you have a generous—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina didn’t wait to hear the rest of his sentence. She’d already snapped her heels against the horse’s flank and the mare took off faster than she’d expected. It took her a moment to settle into the saddle at the faster pace but she felt safe, comfortable. Wind quickly brushed her cheeks, swept her lightly tied bonnet to the back of her shoulders, and grabbed at strands of her hair. She laughed, so pleased with herself that she had gotten a head start until she heard Zane’s horse coming up fast behind her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She saw the head of his horse edging up beside her. She urged her mount to go faster. Zane actually wanted to win. She was so close to the tree. So close, but no, he passed by her the length of his horse’s nose.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No fair,” she complained in jest as they stopped the horses under the tree. “You are a beast.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I told you. I always win.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You are no gentleman, Zane Browning and you never will be.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane jumped down and rushed over to help her dismount. “I love it when you use my name.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I shouldn’t you know.” She put her hands on his shoulders as his hands circled her waist and lifted her to the ground. “I called you by your first name in front of your sister once.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He looked into her eyes. “It doesn’t bother her. She forgets and calls me Zane sometimes, too. And I forget where we are sometimes and do this.” He bent his head and kissed her lips softly, wonderfully.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She stepped away. “And I never mind when you do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina reached back and grabbed the blanket roll from her horse while Zane untied the basket from the saddle horse. After they’d settled themselves, she started to open the hamper but Zane put his hand over hers, squeezed it lightly, and said, “I have something I want to share with you before we have refreshment.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He looked serious. Too serious. “All right. I like surprises. That is as long as they are good ones.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You will have to decide that but I thought it was something you needed to know.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She pulled her hand out from under his. “Now you are making me quite uncomfortable. I do hope you don’t have bad news.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He pulled a sheet of foolscap from the pocket inside his coat and unfolded it. “I hope you don’t feel that way by the time I finish. I think I have good news. May I read it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her heart was pounding. “Yes, of course.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mrs. Caroline Hawkins had her second child last week. Mother and child are doing fine.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina didn’t know that name and had no idea why he was reading it to her but she remained quiet and let him continue.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Mr. Arnold Pendergrass just entered his first year at Oxford. Mr. and Mrs. Richard Graves celebrated twenty years marriage this month.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What are you doing?” she asked. “I don’t understand. You have my interest. I’m quite happy to hear about these people, but I’m also quite befuddled. Why are you telling things me these things about people I don’t know.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Because I thought you needed to know their names and stories. The first person I mentioned was Miss Caroline Smithers when Stewart saved her. She’s now married with two children.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Tears came so quickly to Brina’s eyes so quickly, so fully she didn’t have time to stop them from overflowing or blink them away. She quickly wiped her cheeks.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Arnold was only eleven when he was saved,” Zane continued in somber tone, after glancing at her. “Mrs. Graves was pregnant when Stewart helped her onto a piece of wreckage. She lost the child she was carrying but because of your husband, she’s alive and taking care of her other three children. There’s more but you can read them when we get home. I see this has upset you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes.” Brina choked down a sob and wiped more tears from her cheeks. “Of course it has. You know how I once felt. You know how awful I once was. How do you know all this? Why are you doing this?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I thought it was important for you to know. After we made love the first time, you shared your feelings about Stewart with me. I could see that you were still sad and I just kept thinking you should be happy. Look what your husband did so unselfishly so others might live. Just as you do good things for the sisters at Pilwillow Crossings. You are happy when you roll bandages and make tea for them to hand out. Look you, Adeline and Julia—you’ve saved nine girls by starting that school. All these are reasons to be happy that Stewart lived so he could do these good deeds. Not sad. And Stewart should be remembered in your heart as he is in their hearts with happiness. You said Stewart had saved five people but it really was more than that because of how life goes on and touches others.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina sniffed again and looked into the eyes of the husband she loved so dearly. “Thank you for doing this for me. I should have looked into finding them myself.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shook his head. “I wanted to do it for you. I want to make you happy about your past, your present, and your future with me. You are my life.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I am the happiest person in the world because of you,” she whispered. “I love you, Zane. I’m so glad I found you in that room in Paris.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane grinned. “You are never going to let me forget that are you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She laughed and reached over and hugged him tightly. “Never in a million years.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His strong arms circled her waist and he kissed the top of her head.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina thrilled to her husband’s touch.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The End</p>
  </body>
</topic>