<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_9" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 7</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 7</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The only sound Brina heard was her own breathing.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina knew there had been times in life when things got out of hand, but those times usually happened to Julia. Her friend was noted for unintentional mishaps and was more adept at handling unexpected surprises of her own making. But really, Brina must put the blame for this catastrophe exactly where it rightly belonged. On the Earl Blacknight’s more than ample shoulders.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was almost as if he’d goaded her into making demands by accepting the first one. Why had he done that?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wouldn’t have said a word to him if he hadn’t asked her for a dance the 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">second</i>
      time. Something no proper gentleman would have ever done. And despite her resolve to ignore him, he’d seemingly so innocently pulled her into a discussion she didn’t want to have, making it easy for her to trade words with him. Most disturbing of all was how their exchange made her feel invigorating—alive. Their entire conversation had been astounding. They were quibbling over the possibility of marriage. A subject that should always be handled delicately and in private.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They had the entire ballroom looking on and trying to listen.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Obviously, nothing was sacred to Blacknight. He 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">did </i>
      need someone to teach him proper conduct. Suddenly, there was something immensely thrilling about being the one who was going to do that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was a powerfully built man. Handsome. Tempting. She wasn’t immune to his physical presence. Much as she’d like to. It was the intensity with which she felt the attraction that unsettled her. Sensations too rapturous to think about stirred within her when she looked at him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Seconds ticked by as they stood silently in front of each other as if they were daring the other to be the next to speak. The crowd remained quiet, too, and continued to watch them. She had no idea how much of their conversation some had heard.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But enough.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Where had she gotten the nerve, the fortitude to be so bold to an earl who was known for his gambling, drinking and carousing with women? And in front of so many people? She wasn’t the kind of person to need attention or affirmation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">If she’d ever wanted to back down from anything in her life it was now. But, of course, she couldn’t. She’d gone too far. Somehow the earl had drawn her into bargaining with him for something she didn’t want.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Marriage.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was insane.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But it was done. And the black-hearted rake that he was, he’d agreed to all her demands.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">In truth, there was no one to blame or thank but herself for the position she was in.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With her wits finally returning, there was no time to ponder further the ins and outs of the ways this man aroused her. She needed to bring this spectacle in front of everyone to a close. Filled with resolve, she leaned in toward him and said, “We have one more thing to discuss before this is settled.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He followed her lead and inclined closer to her, too. “You drive a hard bargain, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">With her courage returned, she replied, “You are asking me to give up my freedom. If there is even the slightest possibility that you might win, I want to make sure you’re going to be worth it. Walk with me. I need a glass of champagne.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I need one, too,” he muttered under his breath.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina cut her eyes around to his as her brows rose, and she set her lips in a firm line.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But I won’t be having one,” he added under his breath. “I’ll be happy to get a glass for you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They started walking away from the dance floor and toward a refreshment table that had been set up on the far side of the ballroom.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There were more whispers and murmurings from the crowd. Brina tried not to pay attention but it was difficult not to hear some of them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“What are they going to do now?”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“I think she handled him quite well.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“It’s about time someone did. His family never could.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“A lovely lady like her shouldn’t have to put up with such a scoundrel.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“I’ll be at White’s first thing in the morning, and I’m putting my money on Mrs. Feld.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">“I believe I will, too.”</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Tension and frustration shook through her, but she kept walking.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You were quite spectacular just now, Mrs. Feld,” he said with guarded praise.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes. She was, but she’d be the talk of the gossip sheets tomorrow. More ladies would flood her with flowers, sweets, and kind words next week, but this man was making her feel like smiling with his high praise. Her impossible demands had been a shock to him. They were to her. There was no way he could adhere to one of them, let alone all of them. It was startling to think she had the courage to tell him 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">no women</i>
      .</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Where had that idea even come from?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was perturbed by it, but so far, obviously not deterred.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What else do we need to settle?” Blacknight grumbled, as they moved farther away from the thick of the crowd. “I think I’ve already agreed to give up every sin known to man.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You have some nerve being peeved with me,” she countered. “After your actions.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If I’m remembering correctly, Mrs. Feld, you were the one who did most of the talking just now. All I wanted was a dance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was referring to you involving me in your scandalous wager in the first place. Not the conditions I attached to it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of which you said you had another. I can hardly wait to hear what the next one is.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina glanced over at him. She had really gotten to him with her unpresented requirements. That pleased her. Much as she would like to deny it, he was immensely compelling when upset with her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The one I haven’t stated is the most important.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Maybe to you,” he mumbled and picked up a filled glass from a server who passed by.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The orchestra returned playing and the crowd started talking as they dispersed. She had no doubt who they continued to whisper about. But she couldn’t worry about that right now. She had to finish what she’d started.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They stopped in a corner and he handed her the champagne. “I don’t know what else you could want from me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Humility would be nice,” she answered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That might prove as difficult as giving up an afternoon game of cards is going to be.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Which is why I’m certain in the end, I will win this wager. However, let’s look at the facts. If you should somehow miraculously win, you would get me and money from the gentlemen’s wagers at White’s. I’ve been told it’s considerable.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded confidently. “After tonight, it could quite possibly reach to the stars.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have the conditions set forth for you, but we need to talk about one last point. What I get if you lose.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“An earl for a husband,” he answered quickly and without an ounce of boasting.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She scoffed. “What possible value could there be for me in something I don’t want.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His head tilted in question for a moment before a flicker of admiration sparked in his expression. “I agree. You should be entitled to something if you win. What do you want from me?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nothing,” she whispered, knowing it to be true.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyebrows quirked upward as he considered her question. “No. It’s only fair you receive something I can give you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When he said that, she remembered the kiss he’d given her as a thank you. Her heartbeat quickened. He’d held her so tightly she felt treasured, kissed so briefly but so thoroughly, she couldn’t erase it from her memory.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Heat flushed her cheeks.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">To cover the sudden, unbidden sensations, she quickly said, “Since from the beginning you made this wager a public one, we will end it the same way. I want everyone to hear your apology when you lose.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What else?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina blinked. “Nothing else.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You have almost half a dozen conditions for me to follow in the next four weeks. Surely you want more than an 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">I’m sorry</i>
      if you win. Money? Jewels? Land? There must be something.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. No, I don’t,” she said earnestly. “Money or land? What kind of person do you think I am?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He leaned back to study her. His expression turned gentle, almost comforting and he slowly nodded. “A good one. I know you wouldn’t ask anything for yourself, but I thought you might ask something for your school or the sisters.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She appreciated he realized he’d misjudged her motives and had no trouble admitting it. The boarding school was well-funded. She could have asked him for money to aid the sisters’ work at Pilwillow Crossings. They could always use more donations. But being benevolent to a charitable organization would be too easy for him. It would require nothing of him but giving money.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He needed to do something that would be difficult for him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Only one thing would do.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I want nothing from you other than a public apology for getting me mixed up in this terrible scheme of yours and upsetting my life without any care for what it would do to me or how it would make me feel to be a part of your questionable behavior.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It might seem unimportant or perhaps even unnecessary to him or others, but it was important to her. Instead of the peaceful life of serving others she’d expected to live when she returned from France, she now had to train a man on proper behavior befitting an earl and head of his family. And learning how to say 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">I was wrong </i>
      and
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">I’m sorry</i>
      were two of the first things he needed to learn.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Besides, she had a feeling that to this gambling man, losing a wager—to a lady, and then having to apologize wouldn’t come easy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">No matter that right now he thought it would.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You have my word,” he said with an unusual tenderness.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His expression was gentle and his words were heartfelt and nourishing after the battle they’d just had. One that she felt she had won—at least for now.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If that’s all you want, I’ll do the grandest of apologies,” he added. “Instead of the banns to announce our forthcoming marriage, I’ll take out an ad in 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">The Times</i>
      and all the newsprints proclaiming the errors of my ways and your victory. Would that make you happy, Mrs. Feld?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She drew in a heavy breath. “I don’t need anything so ostentatious. At midnight, the last ball of the Season, a simple apology will do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If I fail and you win, I will comply.” He folded his arms across his chest. “If I refrain from all you have dictated, at midnight, the last ball of the Season, you will agree to accept my proposal of marriage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina swallowed hard. Suddenly she didn’t want to agree. Fear he might somehow win pounded in her chest. It had been easy when they were dancing and their hands touching to play tit-for-tat with their words. But now, this was serious.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Could she go back on her word?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do we have a bargain, Mrs. Feld?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She willed herself to be calm once again and remember she had proof of his rogue ways and had to believe with all confidence he could not change them for her. “Yes.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He answered with a nod. “I assume you know the stipulations you’ve placed on this bargain of ours means we’ll be spending a lot of time together.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt a twinge of unease. “Even though, I’m committed to try, I’m not sure how much time I can devote to helping you in your endeavor to change your ways.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s not only that. You’ll want to be with me as much as possible to make sure I don’t swear, take a drink, or—.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She suddenly cleared her throat and he paused.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Commit any other offence that would keep me from upholding my end of the bargain and winning your hand.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A humorous light shone in his eyes and despite her best effort she warmed to it. It should infuriate her, but now that their connection was set, she found his easy-going manner a bit charming and tempting her to go along. This entire affair should have her feeling wretched. She didn’t want a man in her life. In any capacity.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have other commitments, my lord. People who depend on me for certain things. I cannot not be constantly watching to make sure your behavior is acceptable, and don’t believe I need to. I think different people heard portions of our exchange tonight,” she answered. “By tomorrow everyone will put together the bits and pieces they heard and the terms of our agreement.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She stopped and drew in a deep breath, wondering if she could handle the scandal of it. “Anyway,” she added, “You will have a thousand eyes watching you. If you step out of line just once, someone will see or hear, and I have no doubt they will let me know if you stray.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have no doubt of that either, but just in case, I’ll be over tomorrow afternoon and we’ll ride in the park.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Tomorrow?</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We certainly don’t have to start this charade that soon. No reason to hurry with anything.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He stepped closer to her once again and lowered his voice, “You have much to teach me, Mrs. Feld and I am eager to learn.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His closeness always filled her with a shiver of desire and that made Brina wonder if it would really be the other way around. She had unwittingly given Lord Blacknight a reason and a way to pursue her in front of everyone. And he had just started.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A faint gleam of humor shone in his eyes. “No time to waste. If I’m going to have to live without a game of cards, no drinking, and other things of a nature too primal for a gentleman to mention in your presence, you will have to live with seeing me. Often.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, you are a beast,” she exclaimed in a frustrated tone. “Because you will be suffering, you want me to as well.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her such a charming grin her displeasure over the entire affair almost faded away. Brina had a feeling she had no idea exactly what she’d gotten herself into. Much to her chagrin, apprehension and anticipation twisted together inside her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right,” she agreed. “If you insist, half past two for a ride in the park will be fine.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“There’s one thing I should remind you of before we seal this,” he said. “I always play to win.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And you should know I’ve never put a wager on anything in my life—I wouldn’t be doing it now if I had any concern about losing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded. “I will take no mercy on you just because you are a lady.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I would be affronted if you tried.” She took a sip of champagne, looked at him and smiled. “Oh, my, this tastes so wonderful. Cooling after such heated talk.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her a twisted grin. “You are a delight when you’re being wicked, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What I can’t believe is that I’m going to be spending time with you when I could be doing something to help someone in true need. I have important things to do during the day. Taking jolly rides around the parks with you wasn’t in my schedule.” She stopped. Her gaze bored into his. “Why did you get me mixed up in this? I was just beginning to get my life—” she bit off the words and ended with an exasperated sigh.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His expression softened, and he leaned toward her in a concerned way. “You were beginning to do what?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Warmed by his sincere tone, her earlier confidence evaporated in an instant and in its place was the crushing need to be held against his strong chest and comforted. Blacknight was offering her the opportunity to share her heartache with him. And strange as it was, for a moment she wanted nothing more than to do just that.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But no. She couldn’t. Ever.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She wasn’t going to pour out her heart to him about how she’d struggled since her husband died. First with the denial, then shock and later the overwhelming anger that nearly destroyed her. Oh, the anger had been so difficult to deal with. She hadn’t even shared her deepest feelings with Julia and Adeline. It was too horrible for anyone to know.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina took a step back from him. “Nothing,” she said cautiously, displeased she’d allowed some of her inner struggles to show to the earl. Those she shared with no one. Not even her best friends. “Nothing at all. Why are you looking at me so intensely?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was just making sure you are all right and—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And what?” she insisted, keeping her gaze directly on his.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Thinking I might need a list of words that you believe are swears, curses and cusses. You know, just so I’m safe.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, that.” She relaxed and smiled. “I suppose I did get a little carried away with that one. I meant only the—.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His brow rose. He wasn’t going to let this pass. “I’m listening.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I only meant the really coarse ones.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Good. That, I’m certain I can manage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Can you?” She sighed and shook her head. “I’ve never been one to wish ill-fortune on anyone, my lord, but just so we’re clear, you 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">can’t </i>
      be safe.” Her words were calmly spoken. “I’m not happy about this bargain we have struck, my lord. But know this, I don’t believe you can change, and I am committed to remaining a widow. In a way it seems unfair to you to go through with this.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His determined expression slowly relaxed and his lips formed a half smile. “Maybe I forgot to tell you, I always win.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl caressed her face with his gaze so intently it was as if he were caressing her skin with his fingers. The air around them seemed to crackle with words that weren’t being said and feelings that weren’t being expressed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not this time,” she asserted, handed him her glass and walked away.</p>
  </body>
</topic>