<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_6" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 4</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 4</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Oh, he is an infuriating person!” Brina exclaimed as she shut the door and spun toward her friends. “He was the first time I met him, and still is. It would serve him right if I called his bluff and—” Brina caught herself and stopped mid-sentence.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She didn’t miss the 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">look</i>
      that passed between Adeline and Julia, so she quickly fell silent.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What bluff would that be?” Adeline asked, regarding her with more than casual interest while untying her bonnet and lifting if off her golden-brown hair. “And why specifically is Lord Blacknight infuriating?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” Julia agreed, removing her gloves, but not taking her gaze off Brina’s either. “As one of your dearest friends, there’s much I’d like to know right now. Starting with when did you meet him the first time? Why was he here just now?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve heard about Zane Browning’s exploits—I mean the earl’s,” Adeline corrected herself. “Most of them from family members grumbling about something he has or hasn’t done to upset them all. And, it’s odd, but I don’t remember ever meeting him. Since he acted as if we had met, I went along.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I do recall being introduced to him some time ago,” Julia offered. “He’s such a dashing scoundrel and so aloof concerning the ton and everyone else from what I’ve heard. Who could forget him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Who indeed, Brina thought!</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline unfastened her cape. “You need to toss all your flowers onto the table and let us know exactly what’s going on between you two.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">While they were talking, Brina’s gaze kept sweeping from one friend to the other. She needed to buy herself some time to digest her discussion with Blacknight before she tried to explain it to anyone, including herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait,” Brina said. “First things first. Where are your sons? You know I want you to always bring Chatwyn and Paston with you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Sorry, I couldn’t bring Chatwyn with me to Adeline’s today,” Julia said, brushing a strand of her chestnut-colored hair behind her ear. “It’s Lyon’s card club day and Garrett was coming over to play with them. A five year-old wouldn’t mix well with men intent on their pastime. I promise to bring him next time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">It was always a disappointment not to see their boys, but Brina only said, “All right. Next time. I asked you over to discuss something I want to do for the girls. Come into the drawing room. Mrs. Lawton will bring in tea.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We can resolve this issue quickly,” Julia said. “Whatever you want to do for the girls, we’re fine with it. So, that’s settled. We’re not going anywhere until we know what’s going on with you and the most talked about man in London right now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I really don’t want to talk about Lord Blacknight. He doesn’t deserve a moment of our time. We have more important things to discuss.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Brina, there is nothing more important than the black sheep of the Blacknight family being at your house with his nose not much more than an inch from yours.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Right,” Adeline added firmly. “Tell us now.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He wasn’t that close.” Was he? Brina let out a deep breath of resignation, and as calmly as possible considering her emotional state, she said, “He wants me to marry him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia went still.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline gasped.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Their wide, non-blinking eyes and parted lips told Brina that perhaps she should have broken the news a little more gently. They were her dearest friends after all. Their friendships had developed when they were widows struggling to make new lives for themselves. The three of them had been through much together. Society had made them acquaintances. Tragedy made them widows. Friendship made them strong. Even though Adeline and Julia now had adoring husbands, and sons, the three had remained as close as sisters.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina supposed she needed to be the one to tell them what Lord Blacknight had done, though it still hardly seemed real. They would hear about the wager from their husbands soon enough anyway, and probably everyone else in Town. Even now the news could be spreading through Lyon’s card club at Adeline’s house next door.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know. You can’t believe it either, can you?” Brina offered what she hoped to be a quick little laugh to make light of her announcement, but it was more an exasperated sigh.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“When did he ask you?” Adeline questioned in disbelief. “Just now?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. Naturally, being the rake that he is, he couldn’t just ask for my hand in the proper way a gentleman would. He had to do it in the most incorrigible way possible.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What do you mean?” Julia asked, still looking aghast.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He placed a wager in the betting book at White’s that I would agree to marry him by the last ball of the Season.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That scoundrel!” Adeline whispered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia gave her a surprised grin. “My heavens! What a stupendous way to get your attention.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It was. But, of course, I won’t marry him,” Brina reassured them, feeling as confident as she sounded.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I should hope not,” Adeline agreed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What has been going on between you two that we don’t know about?” Julia asked, cutting her eyes around to Adeline as if soliciting her help to get to the bottom of this.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Nothing,” Brina insisted honestly. “I hardly know him. We’d only met once before. I didn’t know who he was at the time, and he didn’t know me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia pursed her lips before saying, “Yet, he came over today and asked you to marry him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. After all his wayward years, and because the title fell to him, he’s looking for a sense of respectability. He thinks I can help him and that courting and marrying me will help settle his family’s misgivings about him and the kind of earl he will be.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Wait, wait,” Julia said, holding up both her hands. “I think it’s time we go into the drawing room. I’d like to hear the beginning of this story.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina had been caught and supposed there was now nothing to do but tell them everything. And really, she wanted to. Earl Blacknight wasn’t like any man she’d ever met. She’d been with him twice now and he didn’t do anything the gentlemanly way. He’d made it clear he was going to pursue her. She needed a plan, and all the guidance her friends could give her if she was going to handle this rake.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After they were all comfortably seated with Julia and Adeline on one settee and Brina the other, she realized her heart was still racing from Blacknight’s visit. Just thinking about all the earl had said, how he’d looked at her with such intensity had her quaking inside with trepidation and of all things, anticipation at the thought of seeing him again. And that enveloped her with delicious shivers of desire.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well?” Julia stated, her dark blue-violet gaze holding fast on Brina’s.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina shook of the unexpected feelings about Blacknight, and said, “It all started in Paris.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Paris!” Adeline exclaimed. “You’ve known him that long?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And you never breathed a word to either of us about seeing him there when your returned.” Julia admonished.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I couldn’t,” Brina persisted. “I didn’t know who he was until today. He was wearing a mask.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline and Julia gave each other that 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">look</i>
      again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A mask?” Julia said succinctly. “You definitely need to start at the beginning.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And don’t leave out one tiny thing,” Adeline ordered. “We need to know it all.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Shortly after arriving in Paris, I confessed to Aunt Josette I had considered joining The Sisters of Pilwillow Crossings and the reasons I eventually decided against it. She was very understanding and glad I chose to get away from London for a while. A week or so later, she suggested since I had considered a life of servitude and found it wasn’t for me, it would be good to shed my widows’ clothing and go out for an evening of light-hearted, free-living entertainment. She said the best way to decide what kind of life I truly wanted was to experience them all. You know Aunt Josette has always been quite liberated in her thinking and actions. And I’d—well you know what I’d been through.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline’s golden-brown eyes widened again and her brow rose high. “What did you do?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia moved to the edge of the settee and leaned forward.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina continued. “After much thought, I agreed to join Aunt Josette at a private masquerade ball. It seemed the perfect foil for me because no one would see all my face. I admit, regretfully so now, that I lulled myself into believing there might be some restorative value in participating at least once in the vastly different lifestyle of Paris’ Society so I dressed in the most glorious shade of pink I’ve ever seen. I’d never worn anything like that gown. It was gathered tight at the waist. The skirt was full and billowing so beautifully. It stood out to here.” She held her arms out to show how wide the skirt was. “I wore a crown of painted leaves. And—”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina hesitated. What she was admitting had to be a shock to Adeline and Julia. To anyone who believed she’d never shed dark clothing since her husband’s death.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And what?” Adeline asked breathlessly, motioning with her hands for Brina to hurry along.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“She spent the night in the earl’s arms!” Julia whispered.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Brina answered earnestly. “I didn’t. I swear, I didn’t. He’s a rake of the highest order. How can you think that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But you wanted to,” Julia offered, encouraging her to answer truthfully.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Had she?</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. No. That never entered my mind.” Not that night anyway. The truth was that it might have crossed her mind a time or two since then. Well, maybe more than a time or two, but she’d stopped those thoughts as quickly as possible. Sometimes. But she didn’t need to tell her friends every little detail of what happened and how she felt about it then and since.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She needed to keep a few secrets to herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After a few more moments of hesitancy, she continued, “There wasn’t time to think about anything like that. When I came upon him in the room, I thought he was a thief. He was only half-dressed and tied to a chair with a lady’s silk scarf.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia and Adeline rose to their feet and stared down at Brina. Neither of them uttered a word. She’d silenced them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Sit back down,” Brina said, trying to will away her frustration about the chaos the earl had brought into her life. “I’ll tell you everything that happened.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And in a rush of excited words she did.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Almost everything.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She started her tale when she entered the chateau and was almost immediately accosted by a drunken man. During her story, she was interrupted numerous times with ohs and ahs and with questions and comments from both along the way. Mrs. Lawton brought in tea and piping hot apricot tarts. She admitted to the unexpected shock of the brief kiss—but didn’t tell them about the lingering, disturbing and wonderous feelings that still plagued her. No need for that. She finished her story at the point where Julia and Adeline had appeared in her doorway.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Now I know why he’s called the scoundrel of the ton!” Adeline exclaimed. “It’s beyond the pale for him to think you’d marry a man with his reputation. And what arrogance. It’s astounding. To think you’d do it just to help him seem more respectable so he can find favor with his family now that he’s the earl.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know. He must do something more than marry me to convince them he’s changed. It would serve him right if I came up with a wager of my own,” Brina grumbled. “How do you think he would like it if I asked all the ladies I know to place a bet that I won’t agree to marry him by the last ball of the Season. I wonder if he’d react favorably to that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He wouldn’t like it at all,” Adeline agreed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia placed her teacup onto the small table that stood between the two settees, leaned back and smiled. “I think you might be on to something, Brina.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina was a little concerned by Julia’s confident smile. “What do you mean?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Maybe you 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">should</i>
      consider his proposal.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Absolutely not!” Adeline injected.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Let me explain,” Julia argued. “There seemed to be something between the two of you when you looked at each other.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Adeline whipped her gaze back to Brina. “Was there?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Well—” Brina hedged.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He’s the devil of depravity and debauchery which is why he’s spent so much time in Paris. That you found him tied to a chair—and by a woman, no less, shows he is living up to everything we’ve heard about him. He cares for no one but himself, stays separated from his family for most of the year, and when he is in Town he never visits to even ask about their welfare. I don’t know what Julia is thinking but you can’t possibly consider this travesty he’s put upon you for one second.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina knew all of what Adeline said wasn’t true even though it was accepted as fact. He obviously cared for some of his family. He’d saved his cousin from a marriage that would have probably been an unfortunate one. For both, considering how quickly the young man went on to find another woman’s affections.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But . . .</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course, I can’t and won’t consider such an idea,” Brina stated again. “He’s a scoundrel for doing this. You both know that.” She turned to Julia and saw that her friend wasn’t convinced. “All right, there was, or perhaps I should say there is a spark of something when I look at him. It’s true. I might avoid telling you all the truth, but I won’t lie to you about anything. I suppose my feelings have something to do with the fact he seems so dangerous to me, and yet so safe at the same time. I can’t explain it. It’s just there, but I certainly don’t intend to act upon it. As his reputation bears out, he seems to have skipped all civility in something as sacred as marriage and placed a wager on it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I understand all you say and agree,” Julia replied calmly. “Both of you indulge me and let me finish what I was going to say. Before you went to France, Brina, I remember asking you why you thought you would be happy joining The Sisters of Pilwillow Crossings and you said, ‘because I’m not happy where I am.’ Tell me, are you happy where you are now?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She’d lived the past five years thinking she’d never be happy again because of Stewart’s death and the subsequent things that came close to driving her to madness. Now, living in the house in front of the girls’ school and helping the sisters at Pilwillow Crossings, she’d found a certain amount of contentment.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Until today. Now she felt an anxious excitement coiling inside her. As if that passageway to adventure the earl talked about was before her and all she had to do was step into it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, I was until Blacknight showed up and announced his preposterous wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Blacknight obviously didn’t want you to agree to marry him today.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Didn’t he?” Brina asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He wouldn’t have made the wager if he had. He would have simply come over and asked for your hand like any gentleman would have. He’s a different kind of man. Strong, self-confident men want to pursue the lady they are after. What would be the enjoyment for either of you if he asked you to marry him and you said yes or no immediately? There wouldn’t be any value in that for either of you. Saying no gave him exactly what he wants. A reason to pursue you and a reason for you to run.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You may be right,” Brina said, thinking back on the earl’s shenanigans in a whole new light. “He said something similar.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia pursed her lips in thought again. “Your first inclination was the right one, Brina. You should find a way to turn the tables on him and agree to marry him but with conditions he can’t possibly accept.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What?” Adeline exclaimed.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” Brina persisted. “I don’t want to marry him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know. I’m not suggesting that. Only that you get even. He’s made a very public wager involving you, but you have no say in it. Only the men at White’s can put up a bet. You should stand up to him and make your own wager.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I can’t believe it, but think I’m agreeing to this, too,” Adeline added, placing her cup on the tray beside Julia’s. “He needs to be taught a lesson he won’t soon forget.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The idea of doing something to upset the earl’s life as he had upended hers was intriguing. It would serve him right if she could get the upper hand in the situation he’s created and beat him at his own game by forcing him to accept a wager from her he couldn’t possibly win.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know,” Brina answered, shaking her head. “The possibility sounds good but I’m not sure I can do it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Sure you can,” Julia encouraged. “As an example, everyone has heard Blacknight’s instincts are superb when it comes to gambling and he’s certainly fought more than one duel over a card game. I’ve heard few can match his gaming skills. Maybe you could say if he can manage to not gamble during the rest of the Season you will marry him. Of course, he can’t quit. Men seek him out to play against him. He’s a master at it. So, he will lose the bet and your hand in marriage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So—what would you win if he lost?” Adeline asked. “A bet has to work both ways. He loses you but what do you win?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I don’t know,” Brina said. “What?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Julia shook her head. “That is up to you. What do you want, Brina? What is something the earl could give that would make you happy if he lost? Only you can decide what that is.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina studied on Julia’s words. Didn’t she have what she wanted? A home of her own and a life that was filled with people who needed her to help them. A way to atone for what she’d done. What she didn’t need was a man.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If you are going to consider what Julia is suggesting,” Adeline said. “One thing you must remember is this is a very serious matter the earl has brought to your door. If you offer him a wager, and he accepts, you have to ponder the consequences of what will happen if you lose.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Marriage.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That possibility was too hurtful to even think about. Brina threw her napkin on top of the tea tray, rattling the empty cups. She rose and walked over to the window and looked out at the spring day. It had been a perfect until the earl had arrived at her door. She had come through the dark times in her life and had definite plans. Now she was not only unsettled, she was angry with Blacknight for inserting himself into her life, making her think about the possibility of doing something to get even with him, and worse making her feel the wonderful, sensuous sensation of desire once again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Love and marriage were two things she never wanted in her life again under any circumstances.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She didn’t want to ever have the possibility of going through the kind of heart-breaking loss, hot, bitter anger, and soul-destroying despair that had crippled her for years. The only thing she really wanted was something the earl couldn’t give her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Redemption for what she’d done had to come from someone much higher up than the Earl of Blacknight.</p>
  </body>
</topic>