<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_15" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 13</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 13</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Trying to tamp down the excitement filling her, Brina took off at a brisk pace and met up with the earl near the trellis. “My lord,” she said, hoping she was breathless from her haste and not from the mere fact he’d come to see her. “I’m surprised to see you today and here in my garden.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Your housekeeper told me you were at the school,” he said, taking off his hat and running his hand through his shiny dark hair. “I decided to wait for you. Outside this time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked at him, still amazed by how handsome he was, amazed how her heart beat faster every time she was near him, and amazed by how easily he evaded acceptable rules and manners.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A gentleman doesn’t wait for a lady to return,” she answered, hoping she sounded at least a little annoyed when, really, she wasn’t feeling irritation at all. But she should. “He leaves his card or a note as to when he might call again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Seeming nonplussed by her explanation, he shrugged and gave her a touch of a smile. “That’s the proper way, is it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, and you must know it,” she said with no scolding in her tone. “He doesn’t wait because it might not be a convenient time for the lady to see him. It could turn into an awkward situation when she returns.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl kept his gaze on her and a smile curving his lips. “Do you feel awkward being with me right now?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” she answered honestly. Seeing him had made her feel better. Wonderful in fact. “I can’t say I do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Blacknight casually crossed his arms over his chest as his lids hooded his eyes just enough to make her wonder what he was thinking and feeling.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Neither do I,” he said. “So that rule doesn’t apply to us, right? Like kissing doesn’t apply.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Kissing?</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His comment sounded so sincere it struck a nerve. There seemed to be several things that didn’t apply to them. Brina wanted to be upset with him, but try as she might, she simply wasn’t. She had been very close to feeling sorry for herself when she stepped out of the school and was glad he’d arrived and stopped that useless and weak emotion from taking hold.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Never mind kissing. What will the neighbors think if they see you here in my garden?” she asked, feigning more annoyance.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That you have a visitor?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina laughed at the truth of his statement and shook her head as she looked into the depths of his brilliant blue eyes. “It just so happens my neighbor across the street has a spyglass and a good friend who is a known gossip. No doubt it will be in tomorrow’s edition of some scandal sheet that you were seen walking into my garden unaccompanied by me or anyone else. I’m supposed to be helping you remember your upbringing and how to behave so your family will be comfortable you have changed your rakish ways.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And you are,” he said softly. “You have already helped me with many things.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her brows rose. “Doubtful.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He chuckled softly. “I want to take you for a ride. In a carriage this time. It seems the former earl recently had a well-sprung curricle built. I’ve taken it out a couple of times. The horses are well-matched and handle it with uncommon ease. It’s warmed since our last outing and the afternoon is pleasant.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina hesitated. Not because she wouldn’t enjoy a relaxing afternoon ride in one of the parks or about Town. She would. The day was beautiful. It was the idea of sitting next to him on a carriage seat, feeling the warmth of his body so close, and watching him smile at her that worried her. She hesitated and folded her arms together behind her back and pretended to study on his invitation, trying hard not to look so eager to go with him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But she was.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“My uncles, solicitor and accountants have had me cooped up in my book room for three days. I needed to get out and you were the one I wanted to see. Come with me,” he encouraged.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The top of his hair fluttered. His smile was charming.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“We can just sit in the garden if you don’t want to ride.” He lowered his arms and shifted his stance, as if he were getting ready to leave. “But, if you have other plans, we’ll do it another time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was daring her to allow him to leave. And she should. But, just as when he’d brought horses for them to ride, she couldn’t send him away. “No. Of course, I’ll go, but a lady needs a proper invitation. I’m not dressed for an outing. I’ll need to change my clothing and shoes, and get a—” He was shaking his head and smiling so sweetly she didn’t finish her sentence.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He stepped closer to her. “You are beautiful just as you are. What you’re wearing is perfectly acceptable for a ride with me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His compliment made her feel as if she were glowing. She swallowed hard and looked down at her simple day dress. The neckline of the bodice was a respectable height for a widow, but she wore no collar, no jewelry, and no frills of any kind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yet, he said she looked beautiful.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Once you put on your cape,” he added, “no one will know if you are wearing a morning dress, carriage dress, or evening dress, will they?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I suppose not,” she conceded quickly. “I’ll get my things and meet you out front.” Brina turned and rushed inside.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Less than five minutes later, wearing a black cape, bonnet, and soft cotton gloves, she took the earl’s hand so he could help her step into the curricle.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I have a blanket if you think you need it,” he offered, settling his body beside hers.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not right now.” She knew from their last ride that being next to him would make her warm.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded, and with a light tap of the ribbons on the horses’ rumps, a slight jerk, and a familiar rattle of harness the carriage started rolling down the street lined with cozy houses and perfectly kept lawns. There was something comforting about the familiar sounds of the wheels and harness, the smell of new and old leather, and horses lingering in the air, and there was something infinitely satisfying about sitting beside a man. No, she corrected her thought, sitting beside this man.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Mr. Inwood’s attention had made her even more aware of how different she felt when she was with the earl. Like it or not, he was the one she was attracted to.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They rode in silence for a few moments before the earl looked over at her and asked, “What do you think?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Smooth as a hand gliding across silk,” she said with a smile. “Your uncle had an excellent carriage built, my lord.” Almost as soon as the words were out of her mouth, they hit a bump. She laughed and added, “If only the roads were as even as the wheels.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He laughed, too as the horses clopped along. “I am getting used to being called 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">my lord</i>
      but I’m not sure I’ll ever like it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I would assume most peers appreciate and like the respect it shows.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“The problem is that I’m finding it hard to give up a name I’ve used for close to thirty years.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she said. “I know exactly how you feel. Women do it when they marry.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He glanced at her and grinned. “I didn’t think about it that way, but you’re right. However, women don’t change their first names and I don’t want to change mine. It’s difficult that it’s not my choice but I will comply. I will be 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">my lord</i>
      or Blacknight to family, peers, and to the ton, but I want you to call me Zane.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina blinked rapidly as she contemplated what that meant and she felt as if a shield suddenly protected her. She would be giving up some of the distance Society had put between them if she agreed to his suggestion. She didn’t need to do that close to him. It was an intimate endearment to call a man by his first name unless he was a childhood friend.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I couldn’t possibly do that. It wouldn’t be right.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not always,” he said in casual tone. “Only when we’re alone together.” He glanced back to the road as they passed a carriage on the other side. “To others you will continue to be Mrs. Feld. I’ll call you Brina and you call me Zane.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The set of his strong jaw told her he was serious, but how could she possibly agree to something that simply wasn’t done? Once a man gained a title his first name was all but forgotten.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You go too far, my lord. That would make us too familiar with each other.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m all right with that.” He turned toward her again, his expression serious, but not somber. “We can be ourselves with each other. Not a name someone else has given us. No Mrs. No lord. No title for either of us.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her heart started racing at the thought. As horrific as it seemed, she liked that idea. She didn’t want to be Mrs. Feld when she was with him. She wasn’t married, yet she was a Mrs. She wanted to be Brina. But how could she agree to something so unacceptable to the elite of Society? Especially when she had promised to do all she could to see that Blacknight handled everything the proper way.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are you pondering?” he asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she answered honestly.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Fair enough. Think about it. In the meantime, I’ll call you Brina.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her name sounded nice coming from him. Proper or not. She settled more comfortably into the expensive leather-covered cushion and enjoyed the ride for a short time before saying, “You’re suspiciously quiet. I hope you’re not thinking about more rules you can break,” she asked with a mischievous grin.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I suppose I’ll always break a rule once in a while, but I’ll be careful which ones I do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Be sure that you do,” she answered playfully. “I’m watching you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“So is all of London it seems,” he mumbled under his breath, before turning to look over his shoulder again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You might like to know I saw your cousin Robert at a party.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Was he behaving himself?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“As far as I could tell. He was with Harper again. Both are quite accomplished young men and handle themselves well. They didn’t stay very long which surprised me. Apparently, they were eager to rush through the buffet and get to a card game.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl seemed to think on that for a few moments as he looked straight ahead, but for some reason it caused him to frown. “Did either of them happen to say where it was? The game they were joining?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. But they seemed more interested in it than the bevy of young ladies who were there hoping one, if not both, would pay them some notice. Which neither did. They spoke, but I didn’t see either one giving the ladies serious attention. It’s the Season, and belles want to be courted by such handsome, sought-after gentlemen as they are. Perhaps when you stopped Mr. Browning from marrying in Paris it put him off romance for a time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Blacknight shrugged. “It does appear the two are more interested in their games right now but that’s not so unusual. All men want to be good at the tables.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Their behavior hadn’t seemed normal to Brina. Certainly not Harper’s anyway. He’d always enjoyed flattering the ladies with his cheerful smiles, and he’d never really been into cards and gambling—until he befriended Mr. Browning. For a moment she thought she might tell the earl but decided against it. She was sure he didn’t want to hear his cousin was a bad influence on Harper. Blacknight was probably just as fond of his cousin as Brina was of hers.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When they turned toward the business district of St. James, the earl glanced at her and said, “Look behind us and tell me if you see a cabriolet in the distance.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She peered over her shoulder nearest Zane and caught the scents of his clean-shaven face and the fine wool coat and it distracted her for a moment. “Yes. Why do you ask?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I saw it out of the corner of my eye when we made the turn. It’s the same one that was parked on the street when we left your house.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How can you know that?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A man knows carriages, Brina. Especially ones that aren’t well-maintained.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She smiled at him, accepting the simple answer. “Is there something wrong with him falling in line behind us?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not if that is all he’s doing.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Perhaps like us, he’s going nowhere specific and simply riding around to enjoy the lovely day.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s unlikely. If I slow down, he does. When I speed up. He does. I’m going to turn at the next street which will put us going back in the direction we were coming from. Watch and tell me if he does the same.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That had her interest. After they made the turn, she strained her neck to keep looking and suddenly the cabriolet came into sight. “Yes,” she said, growing more intrigued by what was happening. “It’s still behind us.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Glancing her way, he frowned again, and said, “I think we’re being followed. I’ve had that feeling for the past couple of days. I’ve started watching my surroundings. In addition to spyglasses, as you mentioned, tailing people is one of the ways scandal sheets get the information they publish.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">An uneasy feeling stole over Brina. Suddenly, she wanted to scoot closer to Zane. She wanted to reach over and lay her hand on his shoulder or his knee, anywhere as long as she felt his strength and comfort. But, if whoever was in that carriage was actually followed them, it was best she not move.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve heard some people will go to extraordinary lengths to get gossip for their columns,” she said, remembering some of the outlandish stories that had been written over the years, such as gentlemen having been seen jumping out of bedroom windows. “It’s abhorrent really.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Men have wagered a lot of money on whether or not you will accept my proposal by the end of the Season,” Zane said. “Whether they win or lose depends on what I do or don’t do.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Because of the demands I put on you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No,” he said firmly. “You share no blame in this. It started by me making that first wager.” He glanced over to her. “You have no need to worry that you are being watched when I’m not with you. It’s not you they’re worried about.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You think someone is trying to catch you playing cards, having a sip of wine or—” She didn’t want to think about him being with a woman.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes. All of it. That’s the way some men are. Unscrupulous men. It’s no longer only the members of White’s who have entered into the gaming of the original wager and the one between us. Others have taken them and made their own bets. I’ve heard a few will either win or lose small fortunes depending on the outcome.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I heard that, too. It’s appalling that so many people are gaming on the outcome of our situation. You’ll probably have someone watching you every day now. I didn’t think about that.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He smiled. “I can handle the tailing, Brina. It matters not to me that I’m shadowed. But if anyone should start bothering you, I’ll have to get involved.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She believed he would.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They rode in silence for a few minutes. Long enough for her thoughts to expand on how outrageous people were being and for apprehensiveness to morph into outrage. She didn’t like the idea of anyone invading her privacy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Their privacy.</i>
    </p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She looked over at him and said, “It’s true you started this wager, but now we are in it together. The nerve of some gossip-seeking scoundrel wanting to spy on us, no matter the reason, is beyond the pale. And for their own gain.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It could be someone who only wants to write about where we’re going and what we’re doing. It may not have anything to do with whether or not I take a drink or slip in a hand of cards.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s still wrong to spy on us. Speed up and we’ll lose him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane glanced at her and gave a wiry grin. “I can’t believe you said that. Gentlemen are not supposed to drive fast when a lady is with them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was right, of course. She was being quite scandalous for a lady of the ton. “No. However, as you and I have established, some rules don’t apply to us. Not today anyway. I’m not happy we are being followed.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You aren’t afraid to go fast?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She thought about that. “No. I don’t think so. I can’t say I’ve ever been in a curricle that has been driven very fast. A coach once when Stewart and I were traveling to his brother’s estate. We were running late and he told the driver not to hold the leather. I don’t remember it as being frightful.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Speeding along in this lightweight carriage would be nothing like a fast jostling ride on a coach loaded with people and trunks.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She glanced over her shoulder again. The cabriolet was still behind them. Though he wasn’t close, she could see there was only one man in the carriage. His hat and cloak were black, but she couldn’t tell much else about him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina gave him a defiant stare. “Let’s lose him, Zane.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He angled his head toward her, his expression pensive. “I like your idea, but it would be too dangerous. Curricles can turn over easily.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Are you not skillful with them and horses?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“One of the best,” he answered without sounding the least bit boastful.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Then forget chivalry and let’s do it. You are absolved of any responsibility that may happen, Zane.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He seemed to study on that for a moment before sighing and then saying, “It won’t be the first time I’ve done something dangerous. First, you have to secure yourself. Feet flat to the floor. Take off your gloves and grab hold of the seat handle and—” He took his elbow and pushed his coat aside. “Grab hold of the waistband of my trousers.” He stopped and smiled. “Don’t worry. I’ll be managing the reins so I’m not likely to accost you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s not what I was thinking,” she said, and then added, “I was wondering why I should take off my gloves.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It’s necessary. Your gloves aren’t leather. The fabric might slip on the handle causing you to lose your grip. You need a firm, solid hold. Don’t be shy. If we’re going to do this, we have to do it right and with all caution for your safety.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She quickly took off her gloves, stuffed them into the pocket of her cape and looked back to him for more instructions.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“One hand on the arm of the seat and with the other slide your fingers about two inches past my waistband. Make a fist and don’t let go for anything. We’ll be taking some corners fast. I don’t want you to get hurt.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Excitement built inside her. Instead of flee down underground tunnels in an old chateau with him, she would be speeding down the streets of London in a carriage with him.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Without further thought, she reached over and lifted the tale of his waistcoat and slid all four of her fingers between his shirt and trousers. His body firm, lean, and warm as a winter fire. Closing her thumb around the outside of the fabric she made a tight fist. She then steadied herself with her feet. She realized this was as intimate and as outrageous as calling an earl by his first name. It simply wasn’t done. But for some reason, it felt freeing to make the decision to do them anyway.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane spread his legs. From the bottom of her hip to her knee his thigh pressed tightly against hers. His warmth made her want to slip closer to him and snuggle deep into his strong, protective embrace.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His hands tightened on the reins. “Don’t let go of me for any reason.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina gripped his trousers and the handle tighter and smiled at him. “I’ll manage myself. You handle the horses.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“One. Two. Three.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl brought the reins down hard and yelled. The curricle lurched, and then jolted violently. She was thrown backward and then forward as the horses took off galloping. Wind whipped her face and tore at her and bonnet. The road suddenly became bumpier, at times lifting Brina out of her seat. They came up quickly behind two riders. Zane didn’t slow his pace but pulled on the reins and directed the horses around them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Slow down, you bloody jug-bitten hell-bounder!” one of the men shouted with his fist raised and pumping in the air.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina looked back at him and yelled, “Have some heart you pickle-head! We’re in a hurry!”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She heard Zane laughing and she looked at him again. His concentration was on the horses, but he said, “Did you yell at that man and call him a pickle-head?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Yes. She did. It surprised her, too. It was so unlike her to be adventurous in her attitude. Being with Zane made her thinking and doing things she wouldn’t have done or said before.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">And it all felt natural.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“He deserved it,” Brina said and braved another glance over her shoulder as the curricle raced along. Through the space between the angry riders she could see the cabriolet. “Faster,” she exclaimed excitedly. “He’s still chasing us.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Not for long.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane drew back hard on the reins working them back and forth, pulling hard to the right, slowing the horses quickly. Brina’s heart was raced as fast as the horses. She should have been scared out of her wits, but she was enjoying the bumpy, thrilling race to escape the person trying to spy on them.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They turned the corner and the horses almost careened into a parked milk wagon. Brina’s heart thundered. The action threw her against Zane’s shoulder, but she held on as seconds later she was thrown in the other direction.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She gasped.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane paid her no mind but kept his attention on the horses and maneuvered them out of harm’s way and sped them up again. In no time, they were galloping as fast again, flying past the buildings, more riders, a closed chaise, and a wagon loaded with baskets of vegetables.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did he make the turn?” Zane asked, the wind taking away some of his words.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She twisted around to look. “I don’t see him—no wait!” Exhilaration bubbled in her chest. “Yes, it’s him.” The driver’s arms were beating up and down as he let the reins slam against his horses. “He’s still following. What are we going to do?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Don’t worry and don’t let go!”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane guided the horses to the far lane to bypass a mule and wagon and a very important looking barouche with a fancy family crest on the door. Brina heard more shouts but the earl paid no mind to them and kept his attention on manning the horses. She decided not to respond to the angry men either and break Zane’s concentration.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">When Brina couldn’t see the cabriolet, she started to relax but suddenly a landau pulled into traffic and headed directly toward them. Her heart felt as if it jumped to her throat and was strangling her. The horses’ hooves pounded the earth like drums in her ears, the harness sounded as if it rattled deeply in her chest. She squeezed her eyes shut, certain the carriages were going to crash together and kill everyone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">But then Zane’s warm leg pressed tighter against her. She felt his solid strength, heard his labored breathing, and sensed his concentration and capabilities. A calm settled over her. She opened her eyes and sat upright in the seat again, watching as Zane pushed the horses to go faster and expertly pulled in front of the barouche just before colliding with the landau’s horses.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Both drivers shouted obscenities.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane paid them no mind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Caught up in the excitement, Brina was tempted to hurl insults right back at them, but once again refrained.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">They were coming up fast behind a hackney. Zane slowed the horses and took another turn. At the very next street crossing he took another, and then another. He seemed to know when to let the horses have their head and when to pull tight.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">After taking several different roads, they came upon one with no traffic and much smaller buildings. Zane slowed the horses even more as another turn took them into a housing district. Brina loosened her grip on the seat handle and let go of his trousers and flexed her fingers. Her breathing calmed perceptibly, and she started relaxing again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Zane turned and smiled at her. She smiled, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She realized that sometime during their wild ride, he’d lost his hat. His dark hair was tousled and wild. Her bonnet had fallen to the back of her shoulders. Her hair must look as windblown as his. She didn’t care. She’d had the most stimulating experience of her life. And she didn’t know how or why but it was downright sensual, too.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Twisting and turning around, she stared down the long empty street behind them. They had left the populated section of London. She had no idea where they were, but it wasn’t near Mayfair or St. James. The houses were small and farther apart, the lawns not as well-maintained. Rather than tall crisply cut yew there were small uneven hedges and fences that needed mending.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you see him?” Zane asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. I think we lost him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I think so, too but best we find a place to park and get out of sight for a while.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He went a little farther and then turned the horses down a tall brush-covered trail and maneuvered them up and over a small slope, coming to a stop under a budding tree. He set the brake and immediately jumped down to check the horses. She watched him pat their necks and check their hooves before climbing back onto the seat beside her.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Your cheeks are flushed and you’re smiling,” he offered. “I think you and the horses need a rest.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How are they?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He nodded and started taking off his gloves. “Winded, but all right. I’ll see they have a good rub-down when I get them back to the stable. I thought you were going to be frightened, but I don’t think you ever were.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Frightened? No. Well, maybe for a few seconds,” she answered truthfully, still feeling the intensity and madness of what had happened and very much protected by him, too. “The ride was so exhilarating! You were so daring at times and masterful in the way you handled the horses with strength, yet care for their well-being. They followed your lead perfectly.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He placed his gloves on the seat between them and started untying his neckcloth.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’ve never seen or been a part of anything so unbelievably thrilling.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His gaze stayed on her face. “That’s because it’s dangerous and shouldn’t be attempted often.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He unfastened his collar and loosened his shirt and neckcloth. Watching him heated Brina and she pulled off her bonnet and placed it on top of his gloves.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I understand now why young men like to race curricles,” she said in an exuberant tone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Horse and curricle racing are something most men learn to get good at if they don’t want to lose a lot of money or their self-esteem.” He gave her a tweak of a grin. “Am I now forgiven for wanting to wait for you to return from the school so you could join me today?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes, you are,” she maintained firmly. “Completely.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina continued to assess him. His windswept hair, brightness of his eyes and look of strength in his face drew her. Time seemed to be suspended. The longer she looked, the more her senses whirled. Tightness bound her chest. Zane’s confidence and skill had been incredible.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He was incredible.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Without thinking about what she was doing or why she might be doing it, and despite every ounce of sanity she had, she threw herself into his arms and her lips came down on his with a demand she didn’t know she was capable of issuing.</p>
  </body>
</topic>