<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA 1.3 Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic class="- topic/topic " ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.2" domains="(topic hi-d)       (topic indexing-d)      (topic d4p_formatting-d)      a(props d4p_renditionTarget)      (topic d4p_math-d)      (topic d4p_variables-d)      (topic d4p_verse-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d learning2-d+learning-d)      (topic learningBase+learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase-d)      (topic learningInteractionBase2-d)      (topic xml-d)      a(base rsuiteIdAtt)      (topic sdClassification-d)      a(base semantic)     " id="pre-edited_Grey_HowToTrainYourEarl_9781250218803_converted_topic_11" outputclass="Section-ChapterSCP" xml:lang="en-US" xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/">
  <title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 9</title>
  <body class="- topic/body ">
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="TitleTtl">Chapter 9</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The mention of Stewart startled Brina. She swallowed hard and slowly lowered her lashes, hoping Blacknight wouldn’t see how affected she was by his question. She supposed it was a reasonable inquiry, but not one she expected. Still, she didn’t want to overreact, but had to take a moment to collect herself.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">That meant not looking at the earl. She watched a carriage roll past them in the distance. A lone rider had his horse cantering, and a couple walked arm-in-arm. Life was carrying on. Just as she’d had to do.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She settled the cup back on the saucer. After sucking in a deep breath of the cold, windy air, she cleared her throat and answered, “No, Stewart wasn’t a man with many vices. He seldom drank anything other than tea. He did enjoy horse racing but if he ever made wagers, he didn’t speak of them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Did I disturb you by mentioning him?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She lifted her gaze back to the earl’s. Not sure what, if anything, she should say. Talking about her husband wasn’t improper, though it had been a while since she’d discussed Stewart with anyone.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Blacknight stared at her long enough for her to know silence wasn’t an answer. She had to shake off her mild uneasiness that he was the one to mention Stewart in a very long time and continue.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right, no. I mean yes. In a way, I suppose. Oh, who am I trying to persuade? Yes, of course, it did. How could it not?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That wasn’t my intention,” he offered gently.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I know,” she answered in a controlled voice. “It’s just that people seldom speak of him anymore. He’s been gone so long. It’s hard to—. Everyone still calls me Mrs. Feld, but no one seems to remember Mr. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I didn’t know him,” the earl admitted. “But I’ll talk with you about him anytime you want.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His soft expression, somber, sincere words suddenly made her feel like crying, and she was suddenly thankful the chilling wind kept her eyes dry. Reflecting on her short marriage to Stewart wasn’t something she wanted to do with the very desirable man sitting across from her. The sadness of losing Stewart would never completely go away. She believed that was the way it was supposed to be for a man who had been as good as her husband.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She swallowed, and then took another sip of the quickly chilling chocolate. “Thank you, but no. I wouldn’t want to do that. The chocolate is still warm and delicious. Not too sweet.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He made no comment but looked in the basket again. Grateful he wasn’t going to press her to say more, she watched him pull out another napkin, open it, and display little fruit-topped biscuits. They looked delicious but was sure she couldn’t eat a bite right now.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“How is your cousin, Robert?” she asked, wanting only to change the subject.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">The earl kept his gaze concentrated on hers. “Did you forget we talked about Robert on the ride over here?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">Oh, my.</i>Yes, she had. In her haste to forget about Stewart she’d asked the first thing that came to her mind.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“But, I’m glad you did,” Blacknight said, not giving her time to respond to his question. “It gives me the chance to say I do think he appeared restless last night when I saw him at the club even though he was winning when I left him. London has a much slower and more determined pace than Paris or Vienna. The people here are sometimes rigid in their outlook on life. I’m assuming that was the reason for his impatient behavior. It may take a while for him to settle down to Society’s ways again.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“And what about you?” hoping her cup remained steady in her hands. “Restless, too in tired old, stodgy London? Are you yearning to race through underground tunnels in Vienna again?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shrugged blithely and then chuckled as he made himself more comfortable by leaning on his elbow and stretching his long, powerful legs out on the blanket, crossing his booted feet at the ankles. It was highly irregular for a man to be so relaxed in front of a lady he wasn’t married to. Should anyone they know pass by and see them there could be talk enough to turn into a scandal. Still, Brina couldn’t bring herself to remind him of the indiscretion he was exhibiting. Looking at him was simply too tempting to deny herself the joy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“There’s no time now for such idle thinking as was my pastime in France,” he told her. “I’m still trying to make sense of the evils of fate.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Ah, is that all? Well, my lord, let me assure you that can’t be done. I’ve tried it myself.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m sure you have.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her gaze held a moment too long on his, so she cleared her throat and finished off the last sip of chocolate before placing her cup on the napkin in front of her. She hadn’t meant to return their conversation to such a troubling one.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He saved her from having to reply to his softly spoken sentence adding, “It’s more than just I never 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">wanted</i>
      to be an earl.” He absently opened the chocolate, poured more into her cup, and handed it to her. “The thought of ever being the earl and head of my family never entered my mind. There were too many male relatives in line for the title for it to have been possible. If not for that cruel stroke of fate. I’ve been Zane Browning, the black sheep of the family for as long as I can remember. It’s hard to stop being him.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">From experience, Brina knew no one could help him settle his issues with how his life had changed and the reasons for it. She’d tried it for years. She could be a buttress, but not an anchor, nor an answer.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“That’s why you wanted to court me, was it not? To help you adjust to the proprieties of being an earl rather than a rake.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“If only that had turned out the way I had planned.” He chuckled again good-naturedly. “You have not made my way easier. You have made it even harder.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She smiled. “As was my intention. Now, tell me, what did you do today?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He looked at her as if she was asking him a trick question. “Are you thinking I might have mumbled a coarse curse or two when my uncles and solicitor arrived at the door before my morning coffee?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Of course not.” She twitched him a smile. “But I do expect that if you do, you’ll let me know so we can end our bargain. In the meantime, if you are going to insist we spend some time together we must have something to talk about or things will become quite boring.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I could never get weary looking at you, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You say that now, but I doubt you would be three weeks from now, if you by chance make it that long, and we had nothing to talk about.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“All right. My uncles, solicitors, and accountants continue their long list of instructions for all the things I’m now responsible for, decisions I have to make concerning businesses, tenants, contracts, families, allowances. Frankly, Mrs. Feld, I was happy for them to rush me out to make sure I wasn’t late to your house.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Speaking of lists. It just so happens I have something for you.” Picking up her reticule, she pulled it open and reached inside. She took out a small book and folded sheet of vellum. She handed the book to him. “It’s a little worn because I’ve read it several times. It’s small and will fit very nicely in your coat pocket.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He glanced down at the front of it before catching her gaze again. “It’s poetry.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she said as seriously as possible considering the confused expression of his face made her want to smile. “Every gentleman, especially earls, should always have a little book of poetry with them. For you, specifically, whenever you feel the need to gamble, drink, or whatever—pull it out of your pocket instead. You’ll find it will quiet you and help curb your urges.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Wrinkles formed in his forehead and around his eyes. “That sounds very much like a prison sentence to me, Mrs. Feld.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Good, she thought. He was making it difficult for her not to laugh. “Poetry strengthens the mind, the heart, and the soul. You can’t absorb too much of it. You’ll find it sustaining.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You are a clever one,” he chided lightly, and pointed to the sheet of paper in her lap. “So, what’s this? You give me an entire book to read, but you only have one piece of paper. That hardly seems fair.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His attitude was perfect, and she was enjoying it. He needed to be a little irritated with her. It was far better for her. “That’s because these are my notes, and I am going to be studying them while you read on this windy day. Imagine how delighted your uncles would be if they came riding or walking by and saw you sitting in the park reading the much-maligned poet, John Keats.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He gave her such a seductive smile she shivered and pulled his scarf tighter about her shoulders.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“They would indeed be shocked. No doubt about that, Mrs. Feld. They’ve never forgiven me for not being a better student of subjects such as poetry when I was at Oxford.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“You had things other than your studies on your mind, did you?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His expression was relaxed. “Always, but they were happy to know I did well enough to comprehend all the intricate notations and explanations of numbers in the account books they have thrown in front of me. It shouldn’t have surprised them. I’ve always been good with numbers. They seem to stay in my mind without me trying to make them.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m sure that’s been helpful for you when playing cards.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Immensely. The natural talent added with the skills I’ve learned has helped me develop has been good to me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It sounds like authority and responsibility weren’t the things you wanted fate to gift you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No, but now that it has, I will do my dam—duty and my best to be good at them.” His brow wrinkled, and his head tilted just a fraction.” That was only a small slip of the tongue.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She gave him a knowing smile. “I suppose I can say you caught yourself in time—this time.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He shifted his position and asked, “What kind of notes will you be studying?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Things I had planned to do in the coming weeks. I doubt you’d be interested as none of them included you appearing in my life and wanting me to help you be a better gentleman, but I will manage.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He sucked in a low chuckle. “Being with me today hasn’t been all bad, has it?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“No. It hasn’t.” 
      <i class="+ topic/ph hi-d/i " outputclass="itali">It had been pleasurable.</i>
      Brina gave herself an internal shake. That was dangerous thinking. She needed to avoid getting too comfortable with him. “I enjoyed the ride over here and chocolate. Tell me, do you really want to know my plans or are you only wanting to avoid reading poetry?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He seemed to debate that, then said, “Both.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Fair enough.” She unfolded the paper. “The top of my list is to start a weekly art class at the girls’ school. Julia and Adeline have agreed. I don’t know how much you know about the school, but the students are being taught how to read, write, and add their numbers as well as the seamstress trade so they can earn a living for themselves and their families one day. I think it will also be nice for them to have an appreciation of creating beauty with paints as well as fabrics. Lyon, Adeline’s husband gave the school a pianoforte and they love singing. I hear them every morning. So, this will just be another way for them to express themselves in a way that doesn’t have to do with a form of labor.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I can see this idea makes you happy.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“It does. The girls are eager to learn all that’s put before them. It’s refreshing to talk with them. I received so many flowers this week that I took some of the bouquets over to the school for the girls to enjoy. One of them reached out and touched a velvety rose. I could tell how much she appreciated the velvety smooth petal and delicate beauty of it, and I thought, she needs to learn how to paint a flower.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I suppose the more good things one can be exposed to, the better life they will have,” he offered as an observation.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Yes,” she said heartened that even this rake thought her idea a good one. “I feel the same way. I was going to spend some time getting things ready for art lessons this afternoon, but now, I’ll do that tomorrow. So, you see, I simply won’t be able to see you every day.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What else is on your list?” he asked, making no comment about her declaration.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">A gust of wind whipped around the tree and she pulled his scarf higher on her neck. “I have some weekly things I do for the Sisters Of Pilwillow Crossings. I help with their charitable efforts. And I want to walk around town and look at some buildings.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He stood up and reached down for her hand. “Let’s move around. I can see you’re getting cold.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Oddly, she hadn’t noticed the chill. She took his hand and stood up. Even though his gloves had been off for some time when his fingers closed around hers, she felt his warmth, but quickly slid her hand out of his grasp.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Strolling down Town is something we can do together,” he said but made no move to start walking so they stood in front of the tree.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m afraid you would find it quite boring. I won’t be doing it to admire the architecture. The girls will need a place to open a seamstress shop one day. They will have to do an apprentice with someone, but I want them to eventually have their own building. It’s never too early to start looking for options in different sections of Town. Not only that, I’ve noticed there’s a small building directly behind the abbey. I want to look into the possibility of buying that for the sisters one day.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What would that be for?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“A chapel. They don’t have a real one—well, that’s not to say it isn’t real. Of course it is, but it’s just a small room inside the abbey. I thought a larger space for their relics, prayer books and gatherings of quiet reflection time would be nice.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He stared into her eyes for a long time, as if he were taking stock of her. His smile was curiously tender as it had been when they spoke about Stewart.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I’m not sure I’m at all comfortable with the way you are staring at me, my lord.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I was just trying to merge the soft, compassionate lady you are now with the magnificent lady who had the command of everyone in the ballroom last night.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her breaths became shallow and short. “It wasn’t my intention to make our conversation so public. I meant for only you to hear me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“I heard you loud and clear. Every man there was wishing he was in my shoes and had the opportunity I have.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“What do you mean?” she asked quietly, caught under the sensual spell he was casting over her and wondering how she was going to break free. “That’s ridiculous. No man wants to be told he can’t drink, swear, gamble or indulge in other manly pursuits. Most of all you.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">He moved closer to her and lowered his head toward hers. “No, but every man saw and felt your raw, determined passion. It’s in a man’s nature to be drawn to that, to want to seize it for their own, and possess it.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina felt a flush rising in her cheeks. “You talk nonsense at times, my lord. You should pay calls on other ladies and not be so fixated on me.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His gaze swept up and down her face, lingering on her lips for a few seconds before capturing her eyes again. “You are the one I want.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Perhaps the earl had already read the romantic poets. His intense gaze, his genuine expression of wanting her were beguiling even though she was fighting it.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His eyes narrowed and he leaned even more toward her. “Tell me, Mrs. Feld, did you read the scandal sheets this morning?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Heavens, no,” she answered, looking out over the spacious park. “I couldn’t bring myself to read them. I suppose I don’t want to know what they are saying about me. I heard enough whispers last night.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“They were kind to you.” He smiled sweetly. “The one I read had only high praise for you and your ultimatums. Though it was clear the author of the gossip column had not a hope in hel—heaven that you or my family could change me and make me worthy of the title earl.”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">She didn’t know why, but her gaze fell to the sensuous curve of his lips and she imagined them on hers again.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">“Do you think you can change?” she asked.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">In the blink of an eye, he caught her shoulders in his hands, pulled her up to him, closed his eyes, and pressed his lips against hers.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina expected the same wild, short kiss he’d given her in Paris. Instead, his lips landed softly on hers with infinite care. They were warm, pliant with merely a hint of delicate pressure against hers. The back and forth movement was a light, feathery teasing sensation that caused her abdomen to tighten in response to the gentleness of his caress.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For a fleeting second, she thought to make a feeble attempt to resist him, but the mindless pleasure of held so tightly and kissed again—and so thoroughly it put a stop to the idea almost instantly. With little effort, his mouth gently coaxed her lips apart and the kiss continued with a sweetness she wouldn’t have thought possible from this man who had wagered at a club for her hand. Any notion of this not continuing faded as quickly as resistance had and in its place was the very selfish thought that after so long, she deserved this tender embrace.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">There was really no other choice. Brina wanted to join in the pleasure he was giving. She didn’t want to deny herself these few brief moments in his arms even though at the back of her mind she knew they were standing under a tree in a park where anyone could happen by, see them and blab to the world.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Not even that mattered. This moment with this man was worth the chance of getting caught, being disgraced.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Though on occasion she chose to deny it, there had always been an inexplicable, unrelenting attraction between them since the moment they’d met and right now it was sizzling hot.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Her lips parted farther, a sigh of wanting escaped as passion flared brightly inside her. The sheer intensity of how fast a deep longing for more filled her, almost overwhelmed her. Without forethought, her hands flattened against his hard chest and skimmed up the buttons on his waistcoat to grasp the warmth of his neck and pull him closer.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">His fingers squeezed on her shoulders, digging into her soft flesh beneath her clothing. He held on to her possessively, as if she were something too precious to let go. In response, her fingers meshed into the length of his black hair, holding his head, and clinging to him as if he were her nourishment. The kiss deepened, their tongues met, played, and sought. The taste and thrill of his mouth on hers was exciting.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">Brina forgot everything but his touch until slowly, he raised his head and looked down into her eyes with a penetrating gaze that left her dizzy.</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">On a ragged breath with a raspy voice, he whispered, “I don’t know if I can change, Mrs. Feld. What do you think?”</p>
    <p class="- topic/p " outputclass="Body-TextTx">For reasons she had no desire to contemplate, she couldn’t answer. After their kisses, she wasn’t sure she wanted him to change. She had no doubts about not wanting to marry him, but his kisses—yes.</p>
  </body>
</topic>